<add>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">63016</field>
		<field name="title">Waukegan</field>
		<field name="main">attractions</field>
		<field name="name">attractions</field>
		<field name="content">Genesee Theatre, 203 North Genesee St. Waukegan, IL 60085. The Genesee Theatre is Lake Countys premier entertainment venue. Productions include comedy acts, musicals, classical movies, and concerts. It is located in historic downtown Waukegan. Jack Benny Center for the Arts, 39 Jack Benny Drive Waukegan, IL 60087. Lake Countys only opera company, costumed and fully staged. Featuring Waukegan Symphony Orchestra and Concert Chorus. The Jack Benny Center for the Arts is located in magnificent Bowen Park. Bonnie Brook Country Club, 2800 N. Lewis Ave., Waukegan, IL 60087. Greenshire Golf Course, 38727 N. Lewis Ave., Waukegan, IL 60087. Midlane Golf Resort, 4555 Yorkhouse Rd., Waukegan, IL 60087. Waukegan BMX Track, 2785 Yorkhouse Rd., Waukegan, IL 60087. Glen Flora Country Club, 2200 N. Sheridan Rd., Waukegan, IL 60087 Bertrand’s Bowling Lanes Inc., 2616 Washington St. Waukegan, IL 60085. Brunswick Lakehurst Bowl, 631 Lakehurst Rd. Waukegan, IL 60085. Sunset Lanes, 2015 N. Lewis Ave. Waukegan, IL 60085. Lighthouse Mini-Golf Arcade, 2126 N. Lewis Ave. Waukegan, IL 60085. Peoples Choice Family Fun Center, 2411 Grand Ave. Waukegan, IL 60085. Bowen Park Theater Opera Companies, 39 Jack Benny Dr. Waukegan, IL 60085. Ganster Pool, 2000 Belvidere Rd. Waukegan, IL 60085. Lake County Ice Sports and Fittness Center, 351 Oakwood Ave. Waukegan, IL 60085. Waukegan Fishing Charter Boat Association,  Waukegan Harbor,55 Harbor Pl. Waukegan, IL 60085. Waukegan Municipal Band, 410 Robert V. Sabonjian Pl. Waukegan, IL 60085. Waukegan Park District, 2000 Belvidere Rd. Waukegan, IL 60085. Waukegan Symphony Orchestra Concert Chorus, 39 Jack Benny Dr. Waukegan, IL 60085. Waukegan Visual Arts Center, 533 Grand Ave. Waukegan, IL 60085. Waukegan Yacht Club, 199 Harbor Pl. Waukegan, IL 60085.</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">63017</field>
		<field name="title">Solebury</field>
		<field name="main">attractions</field>
		<field name="name">attractions</field>
		<field name="content">There are many fun outdoor types of activities to do while in Solebury, for instance, the infamous, New Hope-Lambertville Winter Festival. Solebury includes a landscape of a tremendous amount of historical sites that are easily located by simply walking, such as, Magills Hill. This hill is a 5-acre site that consists of steep sloped hills which can be used for sledding or any other type of winter activities. The Solebury Township includes something that is called the Trail which has a connection to the electric company power line. This line is along U.S. Route 202 which provides outdoors activities for nighttime so people can see where they are going while enjoying the scenery. This also allows baseball games and athletic teams to play during the night. With Solebury being so close to the Delaware River it makes it much easier to do outdoor water activities, such as, fishing, tubing, and canoeing. On the side of the Delaware River it contains a 60 mile long path to ride on with a bike, walk or run, while enjoying the view of historical villages. Solebury also contains the Washington Crossing State Park. Near this park you are able to visit the house of Thompson-Neely house, the old Grist Mill, and Bowman’s Tower. The following is a list of restaurants that are close by to Solebury for those who are interested. There is also something that Solebury is very famous for, and that is their Solebury Orchards. Although they are closed Monday, Tuesday, and Wednesday, they are open on Thursday from 9am to 5pm. At this market you are able to pick your own berries, flowers, and Apples. Solebury Orchards has a goal and that goal is, to show "how nature faithfully cycles through the seasons, and how we in turn work with her to provide care and nourishment so she may produce the gifts we are able to share with all of you. Through beautiful photographs and a lively presentation well take you on a journey of apples as they begin, develop, are harvested and prepared for their final destinations. We’ll show you how things work here from the equipment we use to the products we make. We will introduce you to over 20 varieties of apples that parade through our orchard from early August right on into November.  By the time we are finished you too will be amazed by one thing or another, just as we are. Then we pile you onto our wagon and allow you to experience the orchard first hand. Into the trees youll go to pick your very own bag of apples, and of course don’t forget one to munch on for the ride back. It just may be an experience that lasts a lifetime!"   This orchard is located right in the middle of Solebury, 3325 Creamery Road, New Hope PA 18938 Another attraction that is near by in New Hope, Pennsylvania is a theatre called the "Bucks County Playhouse" they offer plays of various famous musicals, schools, tourists and residents are all welcomed there to watch shows. http://www.buckscountyplayhouse.com/</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
</add>