<add>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">63096</field>
		<field name="title">Lakewood (Colorado)</field>
		<field name="main">by car</field>
		<field name="name">renting</field>
		<field name="content">With Auroras considerable sprawl, car rentals are the most convenient form of transportation for visitors. Local companies tend to offer better prices, but national chains might be more convenient as far as return policies and hours.Rental companies include most major car rental chains  Weather Conditions Drivers who are used to warmer climates should be advised that the colder weather months (Nov-Feb) often bring snow and ice to area roads. Visitors who park their cars should be prepared in case their car is "snowed in" by snow removal trucks. Also, strict attention to parking rules and snow emergencies is recommended to avoid being towed away at the car owners expense. During the winter months, a snow brush, ice scraper, and plenty of windshield washer fluid is essential, and many natives opt to carry a shovel, some sand, and a bag of ice melt/road salt in the trunk just in case.</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">63097</field>
		<field name="title">Hudson (Massachusetts)</field>
		<field name="main">by car</field>
		<field name="name">by car</field>
		<field name="content">I-290 West ends in Hudson, intersecting with route 85.  You can also take exit 25A off of I-495.  Route 62 and route 85 intersect at the center of town, so these are also good ways in.</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">63098</field>
		<field name="title">Hockessin</field>
		<field name="main">by car</field>
		<field name="name">by car</field>
		<field name="content">Hockessin is only accessible by car or bus, due to the fact that it has no airport  or train stations. A short commute by automobile from the City of Wilmington, which  boasts a bustling train station, and a roughly 45 minute drive from Philadelphia, mass  forms of transportation are within a short distance. Also working their way through  the town on a daily basis are DART buses, which travel throughout Delaware.</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">63099</field>
		<field name="title">Forestville</field>
		<field name="main">by car</field>
		<field name="name">by car</field>
		<field name="content">Driving around Forestville is the easiest mode of transit. Traffic is rarely busy, and parking is abundant. A car will allow you to explore the mostly rural, but beautiful areas. One should take care along Pocket Canyon, and Maribel Rd though, as logging trucks are known for speeding around the very tight turns.</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">63100</field>
		<field name="title">St. Michaels</field>
		<field name="main">by car</field>
		<field name="name">by car</field>
		<field name="content">US-50 is the main route to St. Michaels, which lies about 30 miles south of the Bay Bridge. Heading south from the bridge, take a right on MD-322, then another right on MD-33/St. Michaels Rd. From  D.C. , the ride is about two hours; from  Annapolis , one hour; from  Baltimore , one and a half hours.</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">63101</field>
		<field name="title">Decatur (Illinois)</field>
		<field name="main">by car</field>
		<field name="name">by car</field>
		<field name="content">Interstate 72, U.S. 51 and 36 and Illinois Routes 48, 121 and 105, all connect Decatur.  Cities such as Springfield, Bloomington and Champaign are all a quick 45 minutes drive away, while larger cities, such as St. Louis, Chicago and Indianapolis are only a short 2.5 hours away.</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">63102</field>
		<field name="title">West Bend (Wisconsin)</field>
		<field name="main">by car</field>
		<field name="name">by car</field>
		<field name="content">Again, the easiest way to get around is to drive. The roads are wide and there are few one-way streets. Traffic is usually not an issue.</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">63103</field>
		<field name="title">Gorst</field>
		<field name="main">by car</field>
		<field name="name">by car</field>
		<field name="content">Gorst, located at the end of Sinclair Inlet, is a Kitsap crossroads. Hwy 3 leads north to  Bremerton  and beyond, and south to Belfair. Hwy 16 leads to  Port Orchard ,  Gig Harbor  and the  Tacoma  Narrows Bridge.</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">63104</field>
		<field name="title">West Bend (Wisconsin)</field>
		<field name="main">by car</field>
		<field name="name">by car</field>
		<field name="content">The easiest and most common way to get to West Bend is to drive. Highway 45 comes up from the south. Highway 33 runs east and west through the city and across Wisconsin. Highway 144 enters the city from the north.</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">63105</field>
		<field name="title">Fond du Lac</field>
		<field name="main">by car</field>
		<field name="name">by car</field>
		<field name="content">This is the most popular way to enter the city. U.S. 41 (soon to be an Interstate) runs through the Western part of the city. To the South is Milwaukee, to the North is Green Bay. Hwy 151 runs along the Southern and Eastern edge of the city. To the South-West is Madison, to the North-East is Manitowoc. Hwy 23 runs through the center of the city. To the East is Sheboygan, to the West is Ripon.</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">63106</field>
		<field name="title">Keyport (Washington)</field>
		<field name="main">by car</field>
		<field name="name">by car</field>
		<field name="content">Keyport is located just off Highway 3, between  Silverdale  and  Poulsbo .</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">63107</field>
		<field name="title">Indianola (Washington)</field>
		<field name="main">by car</field>
		<field name="name">by car</field>
		<field name="content">Located between  Kingston  and  Suquamish  on S Kingston Rd NE.</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">63108</field>
		<field name="title">Dothan</field>
		<field name="main">by car</field>
		<field name="name">by car</field>
		<field name="content">U.S. Highways 231, 431 and 84 all intersect in Dothan, as do several state highways.  No interstate service currently exists in this part of Alabama, but the three highways named above are all four-laned for several miles beyond the Dothan city limits.  U.S. 231 is four-laned all the way north to  Montgomery , and all the way south to  Panama City .  The city is encircled by a four-lane bypass, known as the "Ross-Clark Circle."</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
</add>