<add>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">91448</field>
		<field name="title">Tunica</field>
		<field name="main">casinos</field>
		<field name="name">casinos</field>
		<field name="content">Ballys Casino, 1450 Ballys Blvd, (662) 357-1500, 1-800-38BALLY,   .  Conveniently located in the heart of Tunica. Opened since December 18, 1995.  Offers 40,000-square feet of gaming space with over a thousand slots and twenty six table games in a rustic western-themed hotel casino. Three restaurants offer a wide range of choices.  Fitzgeralds Casino, 2120 Lucky Lane, (662) 363-5825, 1-800-522-4700,   . Remodeled rooms recently, with castle fascade. Next to Tunica Riverpark Museum and Riverboat attraction.  Gold Strike Casino Resort, 1010 Casino Center Drive, 1-888-24K-PLAY (1-888-245-7529),   .  The 317 foot tall, 31-story, facility is one of the tallest buildings in the State of Mississippi. Over 1,400 reel and video slot machines, over 40 table games and a twelve-table poker room. The 1,200 room resort with a variety of rooms and suites, several of which are complemented by views of the majestic Mississippi River. Indoor pool, spa with massage therapy and tanning available by appointment. Business services provided by the front desk include photocopies, fax services and Federal Express shipping. Fine to informal dining can be found in three stand-alone restaurants and food court, including a seafood buffet on Fridays.  Harrahs Tunica, 13615 Old Highway 61, (662) 363-2788, (800) 946-4946 (toll-free),   . Formerly Grand Casino Tunica, this Harrahs is the largest casino resort between Las Vegas and Atlantic City. Offers three hotel towers, convention center, state-of-the-art event and entertainment center, RV resort, full-service Bellissimo Spa Salon, Hale Irwin-designed Cottonwoods Golf Course, Willows Trap, Skeet Sporting Clays, 2 outdoor pools, 1 indoor pool, tennis courts, shuffle board and a series of restaurants. Dining options include LBs Steakhouse or Muranos Italian Restaurant. 24-hour gaming action with 140,000 square feet of gaming in four themed gaming areas including slots, table games, poker room, a non-smoking gaming area, and the Total Rewards Center. Voted Best Blackjack, Best Roulette Best Baccarat by the 2004 Casino Players Awards.  Hollywood Casino Tunica, 1150 Casino Strip Resort, (800) 871-0711, (662) 357-7700,   . Located 35 miles south of Memphis in the heart of Tunicas Casino Strip. With a 54,000 square foot gaming floor, a 494-room luxury hotel, a 123-space RV Park, three award-winning restaurants and access to a championship golf course at River Bend Links. Theres also a movie memorabilia collection, including the biplane from Hitchcocks famed thriller, "North by Northwest," the Harrier jet from "True Lies," the "Batmobile" and a 6,000 pound scale model of "Titanic."  Voted "Best Place to Play" by Casino Player Magazine.  Horseshoe Hotel Casino, 1021 Casino Center Drive, (662) 357-5500, 1-800-303-7463,   . Located in the three-property, centrally located Casino Center. 65,000 square foot casino with more than 2,000 slot machines, more than 70 table games, including craps, roulette, Caribbean stud, and poker in the poker room. Hotel with more than 500 room in a 14 story tower with 311 suites, a health spa, swimming pool, meeting rooms, restaurants and retail shops. Dining options include Jack Binions Steak House, around-the-globe variety at the Village Square Buffet, seafood cuisine at Cafe Sonoma and a 24-hour snack bar. New Orleans Cuisine available at Nawlins Louisiana Cuisine. Fresh Gulf coast fish flown in daily. Horseshoe guests may use amenties at Grand Casino including Bellissimo Spa Salon, Willows Trap, Skeet Sporting Clays, and Cottonwoods Golf Course.  Resorts Tunica Casino Hotel, (662) 363-7777,   . 35,000 square foot casino with slots, video poker, and table games. 200 room hotel and suites offer a variety of amenities.  In addition to the hotel/casino offerings, guests of Resorts Tunica and Ballys Tunica can enjoy a round of golf at the pristine River Bend Links. Four dining outlets.  Sams Town, 1477 Casino Strip Resorts Blvd., 1-800-456-0711, (662) 363-0711,   . Two floors of table games and slots, plus live poker and live keno, three restaurants including The Great Buffet, Corky’s BBQ Buffet and Twain’s Casual Fine Dining, 18-hole golf course, pool, hot tub, gym and sauna. 1600-seat River Palace Entertainment Center featuring entertainment every weekend.  Sheraton Casino, 1107 Casino Center Drive, 1-800-391-3777, (662) 363-4900,   .  1,300 of the latest slot and video machines and 42 table games, including Blackjack, Craps, roulette, Caribbean Stud, Let-It-Ride, Pai Gow, and Three Card Poker. Non-smoking gaming areas are also available for both slot and table games. Hotel with 134 all king suites with spas in every room.  Sheraton guests may use amenities at Grand Casino including Bellissimo Spa Salon, Willows Trap, Skeet Sporting Clays, and Cottonwoods Golf Course. Dining options includ Louies Steakhouse, Big Kitchen Buffet, Renos Café or TJ Cinnamons.</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">91449</field>
		<field name="title">Black Hawk</field>
		<field name="main">casinos</field>
		<field name="name">casinos</field>
		<field name="content">Modern Casino Hotel, Black Hawk, Colorado</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">91450</field>
		<field name="title">Black Hawk</field>
		<field name="main">casinos</field>
		<field name="name">Fitzgeralds Casino</field>
		<field name="phone">+1 303  271-1441</field>
		<field name="address">101 Main Street</field>
		<field name="url">http://www.majesticstar.com/blackhawk/</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
</add>