<add>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">51307</field>
		<field name="title">Shelbyville (Kentucky)</field>
		<field name="main">events</field>
		<field name="name">spring</field>
		<field name="content">May Classic Horse Show Shelby County Fairgrounds Mid-May. Shelby County Fair Shelby County Fairgrounds Mid-June.</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">51308</field>
		<field name="title">Shelbyville (Kentucky)</field>
		<field name="main">events</field>
		<field name="name">summer</field>
		<field name="content">Shelbyville Horse Show Jubilee Shelby County Fairgrounds Late July-Early August. Shelbyville Horse Show  Shelby County Fairgrounds Early August. Four night show featuring the finest American Saddlebred horses from around the country.  Bluegrass Festival by the Lake Clear Creek Park September. Long Run Massacre Reenactment September. Kentucky State Championship Horse Show Shelby County Fairgrounds Mid September.</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">51309</field>
		<field name="title">Shelbyville (Kentucky)</field>
		<field name="main">events</field>
		<field name="name">fall</field>
		<field name="content">Trims Whims Crafts Show Wright Elementary School, 500 Rocket Ln. 633-5222. First week of November.  Celebration of Lights Downtown Shelbyville Mid November.  Christmas Parade Downtown Shelbyville First Saturday of December.</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">51310</field>
		<field name="title">Ferndale (California)</field>
		<field name="main">events</field>
		<field name="name">events</field>
		<field name="content">Humboldt County Fair,    Held annually since 1869, has a lot of country feel to it and a good time for the family</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">51311</field>
		<field name="title">Franklin (Kentucky)</field>
		<field name="main">events</field>
		<field name="name">events</field>
		<field name="content">Red River Meeting and Rendevous  About 1.3miles west of Schochoh  586-7632. October 12-14, 2007. Enjoy living history at the Red River Meeting House; celebrate the commemoration of the "Second Great Awakening" in America in the early 1800s, beginning in Logan Co., KY. Camp in a place of rare beauty and peace. Participate in a variety of camp activities including reenacting the time period of 1800 with period clothing, cooking over open fires, music, games, and traders with wares for sale. There will be church services, history lessons, exhibits, cemetery tours, and various demonstrations. This is a great place and time for children to learn and play. No camp fee; service animals only; no water or electric hookup for modern tents and campers. Firewood and water furnished.  Franklin KY. Music Festival  Jim Roberts Community Park 586-0288 or (866) 221-5700. September 7-8, 2007. Fourth Annual Franklin KY Music Festival hosted by Williams and Clark Expedition will again be at the Jim Roberts Community Park under the giant tent, rain or shine so plan to bring your lawn chair and come to Franklin for some great country and bluegrass music. Some of the groups slated to appear in 2007 are Rhonda Vincent, Bobby Osborne, Cherryholmes, Marty Rabon, John Cowan, Steep Canyon Rangers, The James King Band, and hunger Mountain Boys. As the time nears, other acts will be added. The premier sponsor is the Simpson County Vietnam Veterans organization. There will be food and vendors. Both camping hookups and rough camping will be available. The section with hookups fills early. Come in time for the jam sessions on Wednesday and Thursday. Ticket prices: Friday $20, Saturday $25, 2 day ticket $40 Children under 12 with adult free.   Bill Monroe Memorial Birthday Celebration  1/4 mile north of I-65 Exit 2 on US 31W  586-7100. September 13, 2007.    Southern Kentucky Region Antique Car Show / Arts Crafts Fair  Courthouse Square Car Show: 842-9221 or 586-3334; Crafts: 586-7609. September 14 15, 2007. 45th Annual Antique Auto Show in conjunction with Festival on the Square. Cruise-in on the square on Friday night begins 6 pm. No admission charge to public Over 100 trophies awarded All entries must be at least 25 years old -1982 and older Arts and Craft Show featuring Quality Handmade Items.   Small Town Christmas  Courthouse Square 586-7609. Dec. 8, 2007. Activities on the square before and following the Christmas parade: food, fun, entertainment.</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">51312</field>
		<field name="title">Brandenburg (Kentucky)</field>
		<field name="main">events</field>
		<field name="name">events</field>
		<field name="content">Guston Days Guston Second Saturday in June. River Heritage Bluegrass Festival July. Threshing Days Second weekend in July. Meade County Fair Meade County Fairgrounds Late July. Christmas by the River Last Saturday November-December 31.</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">51313</field>
		<field name="title">Rockford</field>
		<field name="main">events</field>
		<field name="name">events</field>
		<field name="content">During March, the Midway Village Museum Center hosts the Sock Monkey Madness Festival featuring vendors, crafts, make-your-own-monkeys, activities, and information on sock monkey history.  Relatively new to the area, the  Screw City Beer Festival  occurs every September. Come and eat food, hangout, hug a stranger, and most importantly try some delicious craft beer.</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">51314</field>
		<field name="title">Eugene</field>
		<field name="main">events</field>
		<field name="name">Lane County Fair</field>
		<field name="content">An annual celebration held every August featuring food, music and other entertainment.</field>
		<field name="directions">Just west of downtown</field>
		<field name="phone">+1 541  682-4292</field>
		<field name="price">$6-$9</field>
		<field name="address">Lane Events Center, 796 W. 13th Avenue</field>
		<field name="url">http://www.atthefair.com/</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">51315</field>
		<field name="title">Chelsea (Michigan)</field>
		<field name="main">events</field>
		<field name="name">events</field>
		<field name="content">Chelsea offers residents and visitors many local events and activities to choose from on any given day. These events are listed on the Things To Do In Chelsea    website. The major annual events include:   Sounds and Sights on Thursday Nights, Main Street, +1 734 475-1145,   . Held for 11 weeks from late June through late August, on Thursday nights from 6:30PM-8:30PM. Local musicians, street performers, food vendors, downtown shops open late.   Chelsea SummerFest, Main Street, +1 734 475-1145,   . Held during two days in late July. Artisans and craftspeople, live entertainment, childrens activities, merchant booths, special guest appearances, specialty foods, classic cars and more.   Chelsea Community Fair, 20501 Old US-12 Hwy and Old Manchester Road, +1 734 475-1270,   . Held during one week in late August. Fairground rides, juried exhibits, contests, demolition derby, horse shows, wheel drive pulling.    Hometown Holiday, Main Street, +1 734 475-1145,   . Held the first weekend in December. Tree lighting ceremony, visits with Santa, storytelling, live nativity scene, live entertainment and sing-a-longs, concerts, luminaries, light parade, crafts workshops and more.</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">51316</field>
		<field name="title">Pittsburg (California)</field>
		<field name="main">events</field>
		<field name="name">events</field>
		<field name="content">Pittsburg Seafood Festival,    held annually its been going on for over 2 decades, a lot of great food and fun, family atmosphere</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">51317</field>
		<field name="title">Rio Vista (California)</field>
		<field name="main">events</field>
		<field name="name">events</field>
		<field name="content">Bass Festival, is held during the second weekend of October</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">51318</field>
		<field name="title">Trinity County</field>
		<field name="main">events</field>
		<field name="name">events</field>
		<field name="content">Trinity County Fair,    your typical county fair, held in Hayfork, California, see website for times and dates</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">51319</field>
		<field name="title">Eugene</field>
		<field name="main">events</field>
		<field name="name">events</field>
		<field name="content">Oregon Country Fair  (Second weekend in July)  One of the biggest "hippie" gatherings. Tons of great food, great hand made products sold by local vendors, and live music to be had.     Eugene Celebration  (Early Fall) A multi-day community gathering, covering a city block of downtown. Features live music, street performers, vendors and a parade on the Sunday morning of the Celebration. Parade entrants represent the entire diverse Eugene community.   Clayfest  (October) A three-day ceramics only show and sale featuring over 60 local artists. Clay Fest draws artists from all over Oregon. This is a great opportunity buy unique handmade pieces directly from the artists who make the work.</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">51320</field>
		<field name="title">San Angelo</field>
		<field name="main">events</field>
		<field name="name">events</field>
		<field name="content">San Angelo Stock Show and Rodeo,    Its the one of the largest livestock shows in the State of  Texas  and fourth largest in the  United States   Running of the Sheep, held in September</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">51321</field>
		<field name="title">Hodgenville</field>
		<field name="main">events</field>
		<field name="name">events</field>
		<field name="content">Lincoln Days Celebration  Celebrated the first weekend in October, this years Festival will be October 6 7.  Lincolns Loft Bookstore on the square</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
</add>