<add>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">63021</field>
		<field name="title">Busch Gardens Williamsburg</field>
		<field name="main">history</field>
		<field name="name">history</field>
		<field name="content">Busch Gardens opened in 1975, near the colonial capital of Williamsburg, Virginia. Originally called “The Old Country,” planning for this park began in the mid-1960’s when the company started looking for a place to build a new brewery. In 1969, the company purchased a 3,000-plus acre tract of land just east of Williamsburg on the James River. According to a Sept. 17, 1969 Wall Street Journal article, the tract would be used to build a brewery, a residential development and recreation attraction. Company officials were quoted as saying the company “has been actively studying the land development business for the past 12 months as part of its long-range diversification program.” As a condition of the sale, Busch Gardens could not use an “early American” theme, since it could detract from the historical site located in Williamsburg. Construction of the brewery began soon afterward and was completed in 1971. Then in April 1973, the company’s board of directors approved plans for a 300-400 acre theme park on the site adjacent to the brewery.   On May 10, 1975, “The Old Country” opened to the public after many months of planning and construction. A formal dedication ceremony was held on May 16, 1975 and was described in detail in the May 17, 1975 edition of the Richmond Times-Dispatch. The article stated, “More than 6,000 guests led by Governor Mills E. Godwin, Jr. and television personality Ed McMahon dedicated and officially opened The Old Country as Busch Gardens.” When Busch Gardens opened, it featured England, Scotland, France, and Germany. Today, Busch Gardens features England, Scotland, Ireland, France, Germany, and Italy.   It was clear after the first season that Busch Gardens was successful and plans for future expansion were implemented. Today, Busch Gardens has been voted the world’s “Most Beautiful Park” for 20 consecutive years by the National Amusement Park Historical Association. More than 50 thrilling rides, attractions and shows fill the park, 40 of which are kid-friendly.</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">63022</field>
		<field name="title">Medicine Park</field>
		<field name="main">history</field>
		<field name="name">history</field>
		<field name="content">The community has a rich and colorful history. Originally founded on the 4th of July 1908 by Elmer Thomas, a young lawyer who had just become the first Senator of Oklahoma, Medicine Park was Oklahoma’s first planned tourism resort.  In the spring of 1906, just five years after the establishment of the Wichita Mountains National Forest, Elmer Thomas envisioned the need not only for a recreational area but also the need for a permanent water source for the budding and newly founded City of Lawton. Over a period of a few years, he and a partner, Hal Lloyd from Altus, quietly purchased approximately 900 acres of what is now the cobblestone community of Medicine Park.  When the resort first opened, it consisted merely of a large surplus Army tent with a wooden floor where hot meals were served. Two dams were constructed on Medicine Creek to form Bath Lake Swimming Hole and a limited number of campsites were built. Over a period of approximately 4 years, numerous improvements were added, and the area began to take on the look and feel of a bona fide resort.  About this same time period, numerous such resorts were opening near the entries of other newly founded National Parks and National Forests all across the country. The American public held a remarkable fascination with nature. The coming of the automobile gave unprecedented access to our country’s natural wonders. Resorts began springing up nationwide to provide these new found "tourists" with food, lodging and entertainment.  Tourists flocked to the area from around the state and North Texas to enjoy the mountains, wildlife, swimming, good food and lodging. Soon, there were two inns -- the Outside Inn and the Apache Inn (which was formerly the Press Association Clubhouse) -- Baird’s Health Sanitarium (which featured clay tennis courts and a spa) -- a Dance Hall, The Medicine Park Lodge (atop Mount Dunbar), a Canteen, Petting Zoo, Bath House, General Store, School, Bait Shop, Hydro Electric Power Plant and the infamous Dam Café. Bob Wills and The Texas Playboys (the kings of western swing) became regulars at the Dance Hall from 1929 through the late 1930s. Numerous other famous bands of the day made their way through Medicine Park in route to big city venues in Oklahoma City, Dallas and Fort Worth.  The entire Bath Lake Park was landscaped with beautiful gardens, large trees, foot bridges and grassy areas for visitors to lounge around, sunbathe and enjoy the natural beauty. The area flourished during the late teens to the 1940s as the “Jewel of the Southwest.”  The nearby Wichita Mountains Wildlife Refuge and Lake Lawtonka attracted thousands of people each weekend and throughout the seasons. Medicine Park became the “playground” for the State’s rich, famous and notorious. Folks would come to town for the weekend and leave their “work-a-day” world, troubles and reputations behind them. Outlaws and horse thieves mixed with noted politicians and businessmen, soldiers and officers from Fort Sill, families and socialites in this new cobblestone community. The pages of the Town’s colorful history are filled with the likes of Will Rogers, Wiley Post, Frank Phillips, Bob Wills, Al Capone, Bonnie and Clyde, Pretty Boy Floyd, Lil Hardin, Colonel Jack Abernathy, Les Brown, Roy Rogers and Dale Evans and countless others.</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">63023</field>
		<field name="title">Merrimack</field>
		<field name="main">history</field>
		<field name="name">history</field>
		<field name="content">The town of Merrimack was originally part of the 1673 Dunstable grant. In 1734, Massachusetts granted the town organization as Naticook, which was made up of Litchfield and part of Merrimack. In 1746 the boundary line between Massachusetts and New Hampshire was revised and the land which was originally part of Massachusetts now became part of New Hampshire. April 2nd, 1746 Governor Benning Wentworth signed a charter establishing that the land from Pennichuck Brook to the Souhegan River became the Town of Merrymac. At that time less then 50 families lived here. Pawtucket, Nashuaway and Penacook Indians camped along the banks of the Merrimack and Souhegan Rivers. The Penacooks were greatest in numbers and their chief, Passaconaway, was the ruler of all the tribes in the Merrimack Valley. June 5th, 1750 the towns charter was ratified giving the town an additional three miles to the north. The added a portion called Souhegan East was made up of the land north of the Souhegan River. Merrimack has the distinction of having two birthdays, April 2, 1746 when it was first incorporated and June 5, 1750 when it was expanded. Just prior to incorporation it was part of two states and four townships: Dunstable, Massachusetts, and Litchfield, Bedford, and Amherst, New Hampshire. In the beginning, stores were few and there were no schools. Industry consisted of saw and grist mills. Most of the residents were farmers. The original meetinghouse was built at the exact center of town. There were two cemeteries. Turkey Hill on Meetinghouse Road is the first mentioned in the town records, but Thornton Cemetery on Route 3 has the oldest gravestone. The Nineteenth century saw much growth in Merrimack. The meetinghouse was too small and too far from what had become the center of town. The church and government became separate and two new churches were built in more convenient locations, one in South Merrimack and the one on Baboosic Lake Road. A new town hall was built to replace the meetinghouse. The need for schools was seen and soon Merrimack had eight one room schoolhouses. That number later increased to twelve. Near the end of the century, a form of higher education came to Merrimack. McGaw Normal Institute, a teachers college was built in Reeds Ferry. It later became the high school, only to be torn down when a new high school was built on Baboosic Lake Road. This school is now the Mastricola Middle School. Industry changed to brick yards and bricks were floated down the Merrimack River to be sold in Lowell Mass. In Reeds Ferry, a cooper shop was built by Fesseden and Lowell Company. The Old White Mill, on Main Street, saw many changes over the years. Built as a woolen mill, it became a tannery shoe shop and then several small businesses occupied the building. It is now a chemical company. The railroads came to Town and stopped in four locations. The depot on Railroad Avenue is still standing. Merrimack Flourished in the twentieth century. The population increased. The small neighborhood school closed and three elementary, a middle and a high school were built. Farms were replaced with developments, apartments and condominiums. Industry changed once again, modern facilities housed manufacturers of paper products, furniture and electronics. The brewery and hamlet were opened and the famous Budweiser Clydesdales moved to Merrimack. Many larger stores and shopping malls were built along Route 3 and on Route 101A in South Merrimack. The one time volunteer fire department grew to a full time force with three fire stations. The police department increased and got its own facilities. Town Hall, the library and the schools all had additions built. The existing roads were improved and more were built, making it necessary to form a Highway Department. The Everett Turnpike and toll booths were constructed, changing much of the landscape of the town. Merrimack has seen many changes since its incorporation in 1746.</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">63024</field>
		<field name="title">Deep Creek Lake</field>
		<field name="main">history</field>
		<field name="name">history</field>
		<field name="content">Over eighty years ago, the idea was conceived to harness the water powers of the Youghiogheny (pronounced “yock-a-gain-ee” or locally referred to at the “yock”) River, Maryland’s only designated “wild” river and Deep Creek, a tranquil stream situated between Roman Nose Ridge and Marsh Hill Ridge, for the production of electricity.  Planning began as early as 1908 but early attempts fell through. In 1921 the Youghiogheny Hydro-Electric Corporation was granted the right to construct dams across Deep Creek and the Youghiogheny River, a subsidiary of the Pennsylvania Electric Corporation (PENELEC).  Preliminary surveys were conducted in 1922 to determine the water power possibilities by measuring the running levels of the Youghiogheny River and establishing gauging stations to determine the amount of water flow. The concept that resulted from these surveys proposed the construction of four dams and three power houses. One of the dams would be located near the confluence of Deep Creek and the Yough, another in the Yough north of Deep Creek, and 2 dams south of the Deep Creek project. Because it would be financially self sufficient, feasibility studies showed that the Deep Creek dam and powerhouse should be completed first. In the end, it was the only dam from the original concept to be constructed.  As the project began in November of 1923, the first step was the acquisition of land. The Eastern Land Corporation was licensed by the state to handle the real estate transactions. The price per acre ranged from $5.00 to $2,500, with an average cost of about $55.00. Entire farms were purchased even when just a portion of the land would be flooded. Many farms were purchased not because they would be flooded but because the roads leading to them would be cut off by the rising water. In total, about 140 farms were purchased to make up the 8,000 acres acquired for the project, with only 4500 acres actually inundated. When possible, buildings were moved to higher ground including private homes and 2 school houses.  The dam and powerhouse were built by Mr. Charles Hawley Company, Inc., of Washington, DC. The 1,000 men employed for the purpose of construction were housed in 2 large buildings close to the location of what is now Red Run Lodge. Various other projects resulted from the construction process including: connecting the BO Railroad at Oakland and extending it to the dam and power sites, relocation of nearly 15 miles of highway, relocation of 2 steel bridges, the opening of a quarry to prepare stone for the dam and roadways.  Taking almost 2 years to complete, the plant opened for operation at 4 p.m. May 26th, 1925. Eighty years later, the earth and rock fill dam remains much as it was then. It is about 1,340 feet long and crosses Deep Creek about 1.75 miles upstream from its confluence with the Yough. Water from the lake is transported to the powerhouse through a 7,000 foot power tunnel. The brick powerhouse is capable of producing about 18 megawatts of electric power with its 2 Francis type turbines and 2 generators. Both of the original steel bridges have been replaced with more modern concrete structures.  As word spread about the fishing and boating opportunities during the 1950’s and 60’s, the area saw more visitors from Pittsburgh. In the 1980’s, with the opening of Interstate highways from the East, an increased number of visitors came from the Baltimore/Washington population centers.  Today Deep Creek Lake is owned by the state of Maryland and managed by the Department of Natural Resources. Holding the title of Maryland’s largest freshwater lake, it is 13 miles long with 65 miles of shoreline and covers about 3,900 acres. With an average depth of about 25 feet, maximum depth reaches about 75 feet near the breast area of the dam. A fortunate by-product of man’s need to generate power, the resulting natural beauty of Deep Creek Lake cannot be denied.  Written by.Mountain Lake Quarterly</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">63025</field>
		<field name="title">Swarthmore</field>
		<field name="main">history</field>
		<field name="name">history</field>
		<field name="content">When this town was first founded it was originally named Westdale. It was named in honor of painter Benjamin West, who was one resident of the early  of the town. When Swarthmore College was established the name was changed to Swarthmore.</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">63026</field>
		<field name="title">Sharon (Massachusetts)</field>
		<field name="main">history</field>
		<field name="name">history</field>
		<field name="content">Home of Deborah Sampson, an American heroine who impersonated a man in order to serve in the Continental Army during the American Revolutionary War.</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">63027</field>
		<field name="title">Fairplay</field>
		<field name="main">history</field>
		<field name="name">history</field>
		<field name="content">The town was named by gold prospectors who settled it in 1859 when they were driven from nearby Tarryall by miners who had staked more claims than they could work. In "Fair Play" every man would have an equal chance to stake a claim. Visitors aware of the towns gold-mining roots will find it impossible to miss the remains of the industry that mark the surrounding country side. Anyone interested in the history of the old west and western mining should visit the South Park City Museum in Fairplay.</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">63028</field>
		<field name="title">Bushkill Falls</field>
		<field name="main">history</field>
		<field name="name">history</field>
		<field name="content">Charles E. Peters purchased the land surrounding the falls and opened the area to public in 1904. Over the years, Charles developed further the area of attraction by building trails and bridges to make the falls more accessible. Bushkill Falls is owned and operated by the Peters family.</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">63029</field>
		<field name="title">Ellsworth</field>
		<field name="main">history</field>
		<field name="name">history</field>
		<field name="content">According to the history of the Passamaquoddy Indians, the Ellsworth area was originally inhabited by members of the Passamaquoddy and/or Penobscot tribes.  In 1773 the first schooner was built at Ellsworth. This was the Susan and Abigail, named after the daughters of the two most prominent citizens and original 1763 settlers from southern Maine, Benjamin Milliken and Benjamin Joy. The vessel carried pine shingles and oak staves in annual voyages to the West Indies. In the years that followed, up to the beginning of the 20th century, a great many schooners of various sizes were built in Ellsworth shipyards along the Union River.  Historian Albert Davis records that in the latter part of the 18th century, Ellsworth was known as the Union River Settlement and was adjacent to the settlements of Surry (to the east) and Trenton (to the south). In 1798 the local inhabitants petitioned to be formally incorporated under the name Sumner. That name having been already taken by a settlement in Oxford County, Maine, the town was finally incorporated by the Commonwealth of Massachusetts in 1800 as Ellsworth, named for Oliver Ellsworth, 3rd Chief Justice of the US Supreme Court and thought to be the person who first suggested the name "United States of America" for the newly formed country.  Davis also reports that in the late 1770s there were British raids on the Union River Settlement, with attempts to appropriate the local cattle. However, there were no formal battles in the Ellsworth area during the Revolutionary War.  In 1838 Ellsworth became the county seat of Hancock County, replacing Castine in that role. The original 1838 county buildings still stand, west of the Union River, on Bridge Hill.  Between 1860 and 1865 Ellsworth sent 653 soldiers to fight in the Civil War, according to historian Albert Davis. This was at a time when there were only 847 (male) voters in the area. Military training was held in front of the old county buildings on Bridge Hill, west of the Union River, at the triangular park site of the present Civil War Monument.  In 1869 Ellsworth was incorporated as a city by the Maine Legislature. The first City Hall was Hancock Hall, which stood at the corner of Main Street and School Street. It was destroyed by the Great Ellsworth Fire of 1933.  Work on the famous Ellsworth hydro-electric dam was begun in 1907, at the site of one of the original Benjamin Milliken Union River dams at the lower falls. This led to the creation of the present Leonards Lake just to the north of the city.  Ellsworths first great disaster of the 20th century was the Great Flood of 1923. A spring freshet rushed over the dam and carried off the metal Union River Bridge, along with many buildings located along the river, such as the well-known Dirigo Theater, the Foundry and many wharves and warehouses. This event marked the end of Ellsworths prominence as a shipping center. The present concrete bridge was finished in 1924.  The Great Fire of 1933 destroyed most of Ellsworths Downtown commercial district, on the east side of the Union River. New buildings were re-built in brick, mainly in the Art Deco style. The unique Ellsworth City Hall dates from this period. Fortunately, many of the old houses outside the business district survived the conflagration.  The 1960s and 70s saw the development of a new Ellsworth business district on High Street, which is the direct route to and from  Bar Harbor (town), Maine  and  Acadia National Park . This area is now the largest shopping district in Hancock County, with several shopping centers and many large stores, stretching nearly to the Ellsworth-Trenton boundary. Congested traffic during the summer months has led to attempts in recent years to change the road network, especially at the busy intersection of Route 1 and Route 3, known as "The Triangle."</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">63030</field>
		<field name="title">Lincoln (New Hampshire)</field>
		<field name="main">history</field>
		<field name="name">history</field>
		<field name="content">Lincoln New Hampshire was established in 1782.  The landscape was filled with rivers, mountains, and forests, which made it perfect for logging.  Soon after, sawmills began to appear throughout the town and were powered by the rivers.  The population was extremely low in this town for about one hundred years until trains began bringing tourists to Lincoln to view the mountains.  Although the population has not grown tremendously, Lincoln attracts thousands of tourists each year.</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">63031</field>
		<field name="title">Wayne (Pennsylvania)</field>
		<field name="main">history</field>
		<field name="name">history</field>
		<field name="content">Originally, a small quaker town in the early 1600s, Wayne has become a bustling community in the heart of the Main Line. Started as a rural farming community, over time affluent families moved to the area.</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">63032</field>
		<field name="title">Morganton (Georgia)</field>
		<field name="main">history</field>
		<field name="name">history</field>
		<field name="content">Morganton was the county seat of Fannin county, Georgia in the 1800s.  The county seat was moved to the town of Blue Ridge due to the train establishing a depot in Blue Ridge.</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">63033</field>
		<field name="title">Lummi Island</field>
		<field name="main">history</field>
		<field name="name">history</field>
		<field name="content">Deer on Lummi Island  The island was originally called Sa nam a o ("High Mountain") and Skallaham by the native Indians. In 1792 Spanish explorers dubbed it Isla de Pacheco, and it was later known as McLoughlin Island. In 1853, the U.S. National Geodetic Survey charted the island as Lummi, naming it after the tribe. It is believed the name comes from luminara, referring to the bonfires the Spanish saw upon arrival and whence the tribe also took their name, though there are also theories that it is derived from a native word or phrase. The Island post office came into existence in 1882. At that time mail was addressed to "Beach Washington" which was the name of the town. Today Island mail is addressed to "Lummi Island Washington", though the Beach School and Beach Store Cafe retain the Beach community name.</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">63034</field>
		<field name="title">Milledgeville</field>
		<field name="main">history</field>
		<field name="name">history</field>
		<field name="content">In 1803 a group of commissioners set out into the wild frontier in search of a place to build Georgia’s new capitol city. The search carried them across the Oconee River and into the deep woods of middle Georgia. Soon the group became exhausted and thirsty as they spotted a gushing spring beneath a large oak tree. There they took their rest as their leader, John Clarke, mixed the spring water with some whisky, which he had in his coat pocket. After quite a few drinks the men were convinced that  they had reached their destination. Milledgeville had its start.  The site for Milledgeville was chosen for its central location in the state and its ample water supply.  The town was planned to follow the design of Washington D.C. and Savannah, Georgia and included four public squares designated specific purposes, the remaining streets   were laid out in a checkerboard style. Located on the fall line of the Oconee River, Milledgeville is the only city in the U.S., with the exception of Washington D.C., actually designed to be a Capital city. Milledgeville served as the State Capital from 1803 until 1868, when the capital was moved to Atlanta during Reconstruction.  As the political center of Georgia during her reign as State Capital, Milledgeville attracted many notable Georgians and renowned visitors.  In 1861, secession was declared and Gov. Joe Brown directed Georgias war efforts until 1864 when General Sherman of the Union Army passed through Milledgeville on his way across Georgia to Savannah.  For two days his Army seized the town, burning government buildings and documents, but sparing most of the areas homes.  With the removal of the Capital to Atlanta, Milledgeville experienced an economic downturn.  But by the late 19th and early 20th century, improved lighting, streets, telephone and water supply encouraged new building and commerce.  This slow economic growth contributed to a wealth of well preserved Federal-style architecture, enhanced by noteworthy Greek Revival, Victorian, and Classic Revival houses that can be found throughout the city today.  Milledgeville is proud today to be a Main-Street City and a center of attraction on Georgias Antebellum Trail.</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">63035</field>
		<field name="title">Waco</field>
		<field name="main">history</field>
		<field name="name">history</field>
		<field name="content">Founded in 1849 near the site of an abandoned agricultural village of Waco Indians, Waco rose to prominence in the 1870s as a major junction for the transport of cattle; by 1871 between 600,000 and 700,000 head of cattle had passed through the city. As time progressed, Wacos location at the crossroads of major railroads and its location on the Brazos River helped the city grow and thrive. It is now home to approximately 125,000 residents, with 260,000 in the greater Waco MSA area. Waco has a number of worthwhile attractions.  Elite Circle Grille: The Colias Brothers founded the downtown Elite Café in 1919, which was open twenty-four hours a day, seven days a week. This original café partly burned in 1929 then closed in 1961. Between 1929 and 1961, the Colias brothers opened a second Elite Café on Waco’s famous Circle, the famous roundabout in town. The roundabout connects Interstate 35, LaSalle, Valley Mills, and Highway 77. The café was as busy as ever at its new location and eventually turned into the Elite that we know and love today.  Waco came to the worlds attention, and is still remembered by many people, for the February 28, 1993 stand-off between federal agents (FBI, ATF) and the Branch Davidians, a Seventh Day Adventist offshoot religious group, led by David Koresh, the sects leader. It resulted in the deaths of 86 people. The incident took place 15 miles outside of Waco, though - not in the city itself. When asked about the incident, most residents will answer; just realize that generally Wacoans are tired of the subject and would rather talk about something else.   Waco is best known in Texas for being the home of Baylor University, the largest Baptist university in the world, chartered during the Republic of Texas.</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">63036</field>
		<field name="title">Long Beach Island</field>
		<field name="main">history</field>
		<field name="name">history</field>
		<field name="content">Barnegat Lighthouse on the northern tip of Long Beach Island  Long Beach Island, famous Exit 63 off the Garden State Parkway, is an 18 mile long barrier island located in Ocean County, New Jersey.  The Island derives its name from its white sand beaches that stretch the entirety of the 18 miles.  LBI was discovered in 1614 by Captain Cornelius Jacobsen May, a Dutch explorer and tradesman.  After discovery, the island evolved from important fishing hub to playground for well-to-do men and women.  During its history, the island was rattled by a few major hurricanes, including the largest in 1944.  A famous photograph of a home slowly falling victim to this hurricane is hung in many stores, restaurants, and hotels on the island today. Nowadays, Long Beach Islands numerous tourists attractions and white sandy beaches make LBI a huge tourist spot.  The summer months are busiest, "the season" ranging from mid-May through Chowda Fest in October.  The majority of the island shuts down during the winter months.  Although evolved from the 1950s days of full-coverage bathingsuits, LBI is certainly still a playground of sorts.</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">63037</field>
		<field name="title">Waldron Island</field>
		<field name="main">history</field>
		<field name="name">history</field>
		<field name="content">During a Spanish expedition in 1791, Francisco Eliza named the Island "Lemos." However the current name of the island was set in May 1841 when Wilkes Expedition officer Lieutenant Case of the Vincennes and his party "made a careful survey of Puget Sound from Vashon Island southward". During this survey, one of the San Juan islands was named after one or other of a pair of Waldron brothers, Richard Russell Waldron or Thomas Westbrook Waldron.  In the nineteenth century Waldron Island sandstone was mined for use in various buildings. Coal deposits were also discovered on Waldron Island. Homesteaders settled the island in the nineteenth century.</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">63038</field>
		<field name="title">El Paso</field>
		<field name="main">history</field>
		<field name="name">history</field>
		<field name="content">El Paso was formerly known as El Paso del Norte (The Pass of the North) and was named by Spanish travelers in 1581. The area wasnt colonized by Europeans until 1598 when Don Juan de Oñate led an expedition into the territory. In 1848, El Paso formally became part of the United States and a military post was erected there which eventually became Fort Bliss. The city was actually incorporated in 1873. El Paso Public Library    was the first Public Library in Texas.</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">63039</field>
		<field name="title">Surry</field>
		<field name="main">history</field>
		<field name="name">history</field>
		<field name="content">From George J. Varneys A GAZETTEER OF THE STATE OF MAINE, published in Boston, MA in 1886:  "Surry is situated on the west bank of Union River bay, in Hancock County. On the north-east it is bounded by Ellsworth, on the south-west, by Blue Hill, on the west, by Orland and Penobscot. The town has an area of about 21,025 acres. Toddy Pond forms part of the boundary between Surry and Penobscot, and on the line between Surry and Ellsworth are the two Patten ponds whose outlet is Patten Stream Fishways were constructed to these ponds in 1872, and the ponds have since been stocked with alewives and salmon. The surface of the town is considerably broken. The land generally is valuable for tillage. The most of the surface soil is so intermingled with comminuted quartz, or siliceous sand, that cranberries grow in the grass fields. The cultivation of this crop is receiving increased attention. A large deposit of nearly pure silica in the town may prove of much value for glass and other ware. Over miles of surface on the Toddy Pond road lay, a few years ago, a bleak profusion of granite bowiders. To-day those bowlders are seen in every stage of ruin. On every hand they are smitten with decay, and here and there a patch of unworn gravel is all that remains of a once great bowider. A few miles beyond. these, is a field of immense bowlders, still uncrumbled, lying in wild confusion bowlder on bowlder,-  The manufactories of Surry are a lumber, shingle, spool and two stave mills. Formerly there was a large business done in building small vessels, but it is now very much reduced. Surry has two mining companies, the Blue Hill Bay and the East Surry Company.  Surry was Township No. 6, in the grant to Marsh and others. It was first occupied by the French at Newbury Neck. The first English settlers were Symonds, Weymouth and James Flye. The next settlers were John Patten, a Mr. Hopkinson, Andrew Flood, Wilbrahim Swett, Matthew and James Ray, Samuel Joy, Isaac Lord, Hezekiah Coggins and Leonard Jarvis. Mr. Jarvis represented the eastern district in Congress from 1831 to 1837.  Up to 1820, about 13,000 acres had been secured to settlers and by quiet possession titles, when Mr. Jarvis bought the remainder. In 1800, Surry included that portion of Ellsworth known as Ward 5; but in 1829 it was re-annexed to Ellsworth. There was a population of 289 as early as 1790. In 1874, a small quantity of silver coin was found at Weymouth Point. Surry furnished 135 men to the Union cause in the war of the Rebellion.  The Baptist, Free Baptist and Methodist denominations have churches in town. There are nine public schoolhouses, and the school property is valued at $3,400. The valuation of estates in 1870 was $207,137. In 1880 it was $177,534. The population in 1870 was 1,242. In 1880 it was 1,185."   WikiPedia:Surry, Maine         Dmoz:Regional/North_America/United_States/Maine/Localities/S/Surry/</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">63040</field>
		<field name="title">Lawrenceville</field>
		<field name="main">history</field>
		<field name="name">history</field>
		<field name="content">Lawrenceville came into being on December 15, 1821 and is the county seat of  Gwinnett  County, which was formed exactly 3 years prior. Lawrenceville was the second city founded in the greater  Atlanta  area. The location for the original town square was chosen due to its close proximity to multiple springs  .  Lawrenceville was named after Captain James Lawrence who was commander of the frigate Chesapeake. During a battle with H. M. S Shannon on June 1, 1813, off the coast near Boston, Massachusetts captain Lawrence was mortally wounded. His dying words were, "Dont give up the ship."  In 1978 Larry Flynt, publisher of Hustler Magazine, was shot on the Lawrenceville courthouse square allegedly by Joseph Paul Franklin.</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">63041</field>
		<field name="title">New Harmony</field>
		<field name="main">history</field>
		<field name="name">history</field>
		<field name="content">New Harmony was the site of two attempted utopian communities during the early 19th century. The first was founded in 1814 by the Harmony Society and their leader, George Rapp. In 1825, their town was bought by social philosopher Robert Owen for his communitarian experiment, continuing the work he started in  New Lanark ,  Scotland .</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">63042</field>
		<field name="title">Solebury</field>
		<field name="main">history</field>
		<field name="name">history</field>
		<field name="content">Solebury has had history lining its borders since the 17th century, ever since the Europeans have settled here in America. It contains historical sites that are visited everyday by many. From the pre-revolutionary America, to colonial times, and finally, the industrial revolution. Prior to the "Americans" taking over this town it was owned by a Native American Tribe, the "Lenni-Lenape". This in English means, "original people". After the "Turtle Tribe" occupied this land it later became known as Solebury. In 1686 Solebury was finally signed over to the American settlers by 13 Native American tribe leaders. http://www.soleburytwp.org/categoryIndex.aspx?p=21</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">63043</field>
		<field name="title">Beaufort (South Carolina)</field>
		<field name="main">history</field>
		<field name="name">history</field>
		<field name="content">Visitors arriving in Beaufort are usually enchanted by the beauty of this small city, tucked off the beaten path on the banks of the Intra-Coastal Waterway. Despite its seeming isolation, Beaufort’s position has long been one of strategic importance, with the town playing a part in and witnessing many of the nations most significant events. 	Following its discovery in 1520 by Spanish explorers, the region changed hands frequently as the Spanish, French and British battled to colonize in New World. By the early 1700s, English planters and traders had established a foothold in the area and the Lords Proprietors established a seaport town, Beaufort Town, in honor of Lord Proprietor Henry Somerset, Duke of Beaufort. The original town plan, similar in concept to the Grand Modell of Charles Town (Charleston) established some 40 years earlier, was comprised of 397 lots and a public square. 	By the eve of the Revolution, the populations of Beaufort had increased to approximately 4,000. The wealthy planters and merchants of the region frequently traveled to London and sent their sons to England for an education. These close commercial and social ties meant many Beaufortonians were loyal to the Crown. In the end, however, King Georges huge increase in taxes crippled the local economy and, thereby, brought most locals over to the Revolutionary side. These colonial Beaufortonians who had remained loyal to the Crown were compelled to leave the area, never to return. The remaining Beaufort Revolutionaries of a powerful political band known as Lowcountry Federalists shy; went on to play a crucial role in the adoption of the present United States Constitution. 	By the early 19th Century, the slave trade had transformed farming into large plantations cultivating huge quantities of cotton, rice and indigo. The wealth that ensued created an elite class of planters and merchants. The heat of summer and the pestilence of mosquitoes eventually led these planters to build grand summer homes in town where they could move their families to enjoy the cool breezes along the coast. As slavery and commerce in general became contentious issues, two prominent Beaufortonians served on a seven-member committee charged with drafting the Ordinance of Secession in December 1860. The beginning of the resulting Civil War found the Federal Government searching for a naval post of the south Atlantic for blockading Confederate ports. They decided that Beaufort would be an ideal location. Completely unprepared for the invasion in November of 1861, the white inhabitants of Beaufort abandoned plantations and town houses, leaving behind their slaves and half-eaten meals. The loss of this rich center of trade in the heart of the Confederacy was both a financial and psychological blow to the South. Slaves were freed immediately. Homes in the area were quickly commandeered as offices, hospitals, and residences of Union officers shy; sparing them the fate of destruction seen elsewhere in the South. Other properties were placed on the auction block (and frequently bought by former slaves) for failure to pay Federal taxes. 	During the period of reconstruction, Beaufort again turned to farming. IN addition, phosphate mining became a huge industry. Rich industrialists from the North wintered in the region. In 1893, however, the town suffered another setback through the destruction of a major hurricane that struck the area. Coming ashore at high tide, the storm completely covered the Sea Islands. Many thousands of people and livestock were drowned, numerous buildings were damaged, and the local phosphate mining industry was destroyed. 	The early 20th Century found the seafood industry, truck farming, and tourism (with many antebellum mansions turned into guesthouses) providing income for local families. Long recognized for its strategic location, Beaufort experienced significant military growth during World War II, providing much needed economic infusion to the area. The latter part of the 20th Century also witnessed a major growth in tourism luring vacationers to enjoy the beaches, Northerners to establish second homes to escape cold winters, and retirees to carve out new lives in the pleasant, affordable region.Today, Beaufort bridges a long, colorful history and a promising future. Rich in archeological and cultural treasures from its Native American, colonial and antebellum past, Beaufort also possesses priceless resources in its verdant coastal terrain. Writers have referred to the string of barrier islands that hug the southeast coast of the United States as a strand of pearls. To those who know it, Beaufort is the treasured jewel at the center.</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">63044</field>
		<field name="title">Eleven Point National Scenic River</field>
		<field name="main">history</field>
		<field name="name">history</field>
		<field name="content">44.4 miles of the Eleven Point River are designated as a National Wild and Scenic River.</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">63045</field>
		<field name="title">East Brunswick</field>
		<field name="main">history</field>
		<field name="name">history</field>
		<field name="content">When sections of  North Brunswick  and  Monroe  split away in 1860, East Brunswick was formed. It was a quiet, sleepy town until a century later when it became a bedroom community for commuters.</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">63046</field>
		<field name="title">Factoryville</field>
		<field name="main">history</field>
		<field name="name">history</field>
		<field name="content">Factoryville got its name from having a wool factory in town where people came from miles to have their wool woven into cloth. After only a few short years the factory closes and was never to open again. There are no factories left in Factoryville to this day but the name remains.   The first settlers of Factoryville came in the early 1800s from Rhode Island, Captain Robert Reynolds and Stephen Capwell. They journeyed three weeks by foot with their sons with only enough supplies to find new farming land and a better life for their families. After returning to Rhode Island to bring back their families, other families soon joined them. They established churches and school houses.   Many years later the town was very well known and soon had seven general stores, two hotels, three doctors, a tannery and a grist mill. The people of Factoryville saw a need for higher education and organized the Keystone Academy which was one of three higher education institutes of Pennsylvania.</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">63047</field>
		<field name="title">Rose Valley (Pennsylvania)</field>
		<field name="main">history</field>
		<field name="name">history</field>
		<field name="content">Rose Valley was founded by William Price in 1901, and was originally created as part of an imagined utopia following the Arts and Crafts movement.</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">63048</field>
		<field name="title">Old Orchard Beach</field>
		<field name="main">history</field>
		<field name="name">history</field>
		<field name="content">Old Orchard Beach has an incredible past, dating back to 1653. Its first settler, Thomas Rogers established "Garden by the Sea" in 1657. The "old" apple orchard from which the town got its name Old Orchard Beach, was a landmark to sailors for many years, it was on high land above the long sand beach. The owner of the orchard saw the potential for a summer resort and built the first Old Orchard Beach boarding house.  That was just the beginning. As more people found leisure time, and wanted to escape the rat race pace of big city life, they looked to Maine, and specifically to Old Orchard Beach. Accommodations and attractions of all sorts were built to bring in the tourists. Stores, amusement parks, a racetrack and various other attractions were built to attract the masses, which came to include entertainers like Duke Ellington, Guy Lombardo and public figures like Charles Lindbergh and wealthy families like the Fitzgeralds and the Kennedys.  The town has preserved some of the towns history, a conscious effort to revitalize the downtown area and its immediate surrounding Historic District buildings such as the Thomas L. Cleaves Home (now the Atlantic Birches Inn Bed and Breakfast) was built in 1902 by renowned architect John Calvin Stevens.   This re-vitalization effort a  has resulted in new Victorian lighting, wide, brick, tree-lined sidewalks and an outside dining courtyard complete with fountain in Town Square and a newly renovated Town Hall.   Old Orchard Beach is a community in which residents and tourists alike may take full advantage of a restful day on our seven-mile stretch of wide-open beach. Enjoy any of the 25 rides and arcade games at Palace Playland, our seaside amusement park. Funtown/Splashtown USA is home to one of the largest wooden roller coasters in the country as well as a new ride featuring a 200 feet free fall descent.   If one is looking for the "quieter side" of Old Orchard Beach, try camping, hiking or biking in the nearby Ferry Beach state park in Ocean park, canoeing and bird watching in the saltwater marsh nature center area of Scarborough/Pine Point. There are few experiences that can compare to the peacefulness and privacy of strolling the sands of Old Orchard Beach looking for seashells and then coming back to relax and revitalize yourself at the Atlantic Birches Inn bed and breakfast.</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">63049</field>
		<field name="title">Clayton (Georgia)</field>
		<field name="main">history</field>
		<field name="name">history</field>
		<field name="content">Clayton was incorporated on December 18, 1823, as a part of Rabun county, founded 4 years earlier and named after the present Governor of Georgia, William Rabun. Clayton was previously known as The Dividings and later changed to the name Claytonville  .</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
</add>