<add>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">75191</field>
		<field name="title">Solebury</field>
		<field name="main">hospitality resources</field>
		<field name="name">hospitality resources</field>
		<field name="content">Solebury offers many clubs and activities for residents and even tourists to do. They have sport recreations such as, baseball/softball, soccer, and even wrestling.          There is a main link that discusses the reason why Solebury set up park and recreations, "Solebury Township Parks and Recreation embraces the philosophy that leisure time activities enhance the quality of life by offering an abundant variety of both passive and active recreational opportunities at our local and State parks.  We have a reputation as an innovative leader in recreational offerings. The Pennsylvania Recreation and Parks Society has recognized our efforts with Excellence in Programming awards for our support of the construction of the Track Facility and Sports Complex located on the grounds of the New Hope-Solebury high school, our CPR/AED Community Outreach Training Program, our partnership participation in the New Hope-Lambertville Winter Festival and our Summer Adventure Camp.  Unique to Solebury’s recreational offerings is Magills Hill, a 5-acre site of steeply sloped hills ideally suited for sledding and other winter activities. The Solebury Trail traverses a portion of the electric company power line along U.S. Route 202, providing an excellent walking, bicycle and jogging path that connects to the athletic fields at New Hope-Solebury high school. The Solebury Trail is currently undergoing plans for expansion."   There are two parks that are known widely through Solebury, Laurel Park and Pat Livezey Park. They contain recreation baseball/basketball/soccer fields for visitors to play on. Laurel park is located behind the township municipal building. Not only does Solebury offer these parks but they also offer, Canal park, Solebury Trail</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
</add>