<add>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">15256</field>
		<field name="title">Chincoteague</field>
		<field name="main">ice cream</field>
		<field name="name">ice cream</field>
		<field name="content">The sweet treat followup to your delicious meal. Or whenever you want to!  Mullers Old Fashioned Ice Cream Parlour. The name says it all! In this old fashioned house that not only provides an adequate amount of seating inside but outside on the screened-in porch as well you will find your taste buds watering for more. Their most requested concoction is a Belgian waffle served with ice cream, fresh fruit and plenty of whipped cream. However, the old classics can still be found here which consist of ice cream cones to ice cream sodas and everything in between including, though certainly not limited to, fresh fruit sundaes, banana splits, malts, and frozen yogurts. Conveniently located on Main Street, to the right of the T-Shirt Factory, this house has been around since 1875 when it was built by William F. Cropper. A great place to enjoy some ice cream and chat with anyone you wish; during the in-season from around nine pm till closing, it is positively packed! Opened from 11 am until 11 pm.  Mister Whippys. Located on Maddox Boulevard, this ice cream spot is a guaranteed must for locals and tourists alike. Order a famous Mister Whippys cyclone, or any other of their fabulous treats which range from ice cream scoops in homemade waffle cones to thick milkshakes, and enjoy it on the front porch in a rocking chair, or inside at the tables if the weather is poor. What could be better? The drive-thru window that is conveniently located on the side of the establishment for those times when you want a sweet treat but have no time to spare. However, if you do have time, be sure to check out the gift shop that is located inside the parlor by the bathrooms. It offers a great selection of shirts, hats, and souvenirs alike.  The Island Creamery located on Maddox Boulevard has the islands only homemade ice cream and more. Smell the waffle cones cooking as you enter the building and choose from a wide variety of ice cream, yogurt, sorbet, and slushes. If your stomach is empty enough, order the Round-Up. The creamery also features coffee drinks, homemade fudge, a gift shop amd free WiFI</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
</add>