<add>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">105389</field>
		<field name="title">Olalla (Washington)</field>
		<field name="main">know</field>
		<field name="name">know</field>
		<field name="content">Olalla has some small claim to fame as the location of an early 20th century health retreat (Sanitarium) called Wilderness Heights a.k.a. "Starvation Heights", The sanitarium was owned and operated by Dr. Linda Burfield Hazzard. Dr. Hazzards practice of starvation to cure ones ills resulted in the death of a visiting English heiress in 1911, and the conviction of Dr. Hazzard for her murder. The original bathtub where Hazzard performed autopsies is still in the house, which has a family residing there. However, she also maintains a strong following, in the US, Europe and Australia, that testify to her fasting techniques as having cured them of many ills and believe she was ahead of her time, both then and now, in her methods.</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">105390</field>
		<field name="title">Bonners Ferry</field>
		<field name="main">know</field>
		<field name="name">know</field>
		<field name="content">On September 20, 1974, the Kootenai Tribe, headed by chairwoman Amy Trice, declared war on the United States government. Their first act was to post soldiers on each end of the highway that runs through the town and they asked people, to pay a toll to drive through what had been the tribe’s aboriginal land. The money would be used to house and care for elderly tribal members. Most tribes in the United States are forbidden to declare war on the U.S. government because of treaties, but the Kootenai Tribe never signed a treaty. The dispute resulted in the concession by the United States government and a land grant of 10.5 acres (42,000 m2) that is now the Kootenai Reservation.</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">105391</field>
		<field name="title">Waldron Island</field>
		<field name="main">know</field>
		<field name="name">know</field>
		<field name="content">In 1941 Waldron resident June Burn featured Waldron prominently in her autobiography Living High and described her familys experience building a log cabin on the island. Her daughter-in-law, Doris Burn, also wrote several books while living on the island. The last store on Waldron closed in 1942 and no regular ferry service has been offered to the island. Since 1976, Waldron has been a limited development district. No large-scale mining of natural resources is allowed. No marinas or breakwaters can be built. No large homes or paved roads or public utilities, residents declared in the early 1990s with a lopsided vote (82 percent)</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">105392</field>
		<field name="title">Purdy (Washington)</field>
		<field name="main">know</field>
		<field name="name">know</field>
		<field name="content">The area was settled in the 1880s. Isaac Hawk purchased the land from the Washington Territorial Government. Horace Knapp purchased 19 acres (77,000 m2) of this land from Hawk in 1884 for the price of $23.75. These acres were made into the town of Purdy (with lots and blocks). In 1885, Josephine Fuller, the first white woman in the area, married Horace Knapp. In 1886, the mill in Purdy secured the first contract to provide lumber for nearby Puget Sound Naval Shipyard in Bremerton. This put Purdy on the map. The mills success also brought conveniences to the area like a grocery store, and a post office. There was a long chute along present-day 144th Street that brought the logs down the hill to the water.</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">105393</field>
		<field name="title">Gorst</field>
		<field name="main">know</field>
		<field name="name">know</field>
		<field name="content">The hamlet of Gorst was the birthplace of Gorst Air Transport, a tiny carrier that was the basis upon which United Air Transport was built.  Aviation magnate William Boeing turned the small air service into the legendary company that now bears the United Air Lines name.</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">105394</field>
		<field name="title">Port Gamble</field>
		<field name="main">know</field>
		<field name="name">know</field>
		<field name="content">The village streets of historic Port Gamble havent changed much since Puget Mill Company founded the town in 1853.  The original New England Victorian-style homes have been lovingly preserved, along with the several other historic buildings in the area. Since 1966 the Port Gamble Historic District is a registered U.S. National Historic Landmark and a popular destination for tourists.  In 1856, the USS Massachusetts was sent from Seattle to Port Gamble, Washington Territory on Puget Sound, where indigenous raiding parties from British and Russian territories had been raiding and enslaving local Native Americans. When the warriors refused to hand over those among them who had attacked the Puget Sound Native American communities, Massachusetts landed a shore party and a battle ensued in which 26 natives and 1 sailor were killed. That sailor was the first US Navy man killed in the Northwest and his grave can still be seen at the hilltop cemetery.</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
</add>