<add>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">63173</field>
		<field name="title">Chattanooga</field>
		<field name="main">learn</field>
		<field name="name">universities and colleges</field>
		<field name="content">University of Tennessee at Chattanooga, 615 McCallie Avenue,   .  A public university, UTC is the second largest campus in the University of Tennessee system. Chattanooga State Technical Community College,   .  A publicly funded junior college. Covenant College,   .  A private Christian college. Tennessee Temple University,   .  A private Christian college. Southern Adventist University,   . A Seventh-day Adventist university.</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">63174</field>
		<field name="title">Chattanooga</field>
		<field name="main">learn</field>
		<field name="name">continuing/community education</field>
		<field name="content">212 Market Restaurant, 212 Market Street, +1 423 265-1212,   . Cooking classes. Mia Cucina, 345 Frazier Ave Chattanooga TN  37405,  +1 423 648-4208,   . Cooking classes.</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">63175</field>
		<field name="title">Decatur (Georgia)</field>
		<field name="main">learn</field>
		<field name="name">higher education</field>
		<field name="content">Agnes Scott College , 141 E. College Ave, is an independent national liberal arts college for women affiliated with the Presbyterian Church (USA). It has approximately 900 students, and is located south of downtown Decatur.     Art Institute of Atlanta - Decatur , 1 West Court Square (Decatur Square).  The Art Institute of Atlanta (6600 Peachtree Dunwoody Rd., Sandy Springs) has opened a campus in downtown Decatur.      Columbia Theological Seminary , 701 S. Columbia Dr. Columbia is a seminary affiliated with the Presbyterian Church (USA). It is located south of downtown Decatur.    DeVry University , 1 West Court Square.  Private, for-profit university with over 20 campuses nationwide that offer Associates to Masters level courses in business administration and professional studies.   Emory University , 201 Dowman Dr., located northwest of downtown Decatur. Emory is one of Americas top universities, and is home to nine major academic divisions.  The University also includes a graduate school of arts and sciences; professional schools of medicine, theology, law, nursing, public health, and business. It was founded by the Methodist Church in 1836.</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">63176</field>
		<field name="title">Des Moines</field>
		<field name="main">learn</field>
		<field name="name">other</field>
		<field name="content">World Food Prize .  The Prize has been awarded to individuals from all over the world who contribute their talents to help sustain vital crop land, food resources and technologies, and introduce new methods to help end poverty and maintain crop development—anything to further assist the world food supply.  First awarded in 1986 and is the brainchild of former Nobel Peace Prize recipient Dr. Norman E. Borlaug.  The symposium is held in October.</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">63177</field>
		<field name="title">Fort Payne</field>
		<field name="main">learn</field>
		<field name="name">community college</field>
		<field name="content">Northeast Alabama Community College.  Located in nearby Rainsville, AL, about 10 miles north of Fort Payne on Sand Mountain.</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">63178</field>
		<field name="title">Fort Payne</field>
		<field name="main">learn</field>
		<field name="name">public library</field>
		<field name="content">DeKalb County Public Library - 504 Grand Avenue NW</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">63179</field>
		<field name="title">Greenwood (Indiana)</field>
		<field name="main">learn</field>
		<field name="name">university</field>
		<field name="content">Indiana Baptist College 1301 W. County Line Rd.</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">63180</field>
		<field name="title">Lee's Summit</field>
		<field name="main">learn</field>
		<field name="name">history/museums</field>
		<field name="content">Missouri Town 1855, 8010 E Park Rd, (816) 503-4860,   , A reconstructed small Missouri village made of 25 buildings dated from 1820 to 1860 makes this up. The regions finest living history museum on the shores of Lake Jacomo!  - Parts of the documentary "Bad Blood   " were shot here.  Battle of Lone Jack Battlefield and Civil War Museum, 301 S Bynum Rd (south of US 50), Lone Jack, (816) 697-8833,   , A small but important civil war battle took place here in 1862. It remains one of the few National Civil War cemeteries where soldiers who died that day are still buried on the battlefield.  - Parts of the documentary "Bad Blood   " were shot here.  Freedoms Frontier National Heritage Area,     Lees Summit Historical Society Museum, 220 SE Main St, (816) 525-9440,     Inside the downtown train depot, a small but informative museum about Lees Summits history and the importance of the railroad await you.</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">63181</field>
		<field name="title">Lee's Summit</field>
		<field name="main">learn</field>
		<field name="name">wildlife</field>
		<field name="content">James A. Reed Memorial Wildlife Area, 13101 SE Ranson Rd, 1 1/2 miles south of US 50, (816) 622-0900,   , forests, grassland, wetlands, prarie, lakes, fishing, and archery are just a few reasons to visit James Reed.  Jim Bridger Urban Conservation Area, (816) 622-0900, check website for directions,   , Great deer hunting and forest hiking make this enjoyable. Near Lake Jacomo.  Lone Jack Conservation Area, (816) 622-0900,     Kemper Outdoor Educational Center, 8201 Jasper Bell, (816) 229-8980,   , An outdoor paradise with reptiles, rock fossil displays, nature hikes, wildlife exhibits, and a gift shop! Theres a lot to do here.   Savanhland Educational Park, Pleasant Hill,    , Over 200 exotic animals and critters are here for you to learn about. Included: Zebras, Monkeys, Kangaroos, Chimps. Open on the fourth Saturday of each month to the public, 12 to 4.  Native Hooved Animal Enclosure, at Lake Jacomo,   , The big draw being the wild buffalo (bring some carrots to feed them!), but other interesting animals lurk here too, like Elk and Deer. Its near to MO-7 and Lake Jacomo/Missouri Town. P.S. - A brand new baby buffalo has just recentaly been born!</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">63182</field>
		<field name="title">Lee's Summit</field>
		<field name="main">learn</field>
		<field name="name">colleges</field>
		<field name="content">Longview Community College, 500 SW Longview Rd, (816) 672-2050,   , The first U.S. Community College to win Time Magazines "College of the Year" Award, Longview (located on Longview farm and lake) has a wide variety of classes programs. It houses a new performing arts center and the Frank White Jr. Baseball Complex.  University of Central Missouri-Summit Campus, NE Corner of Chipman Rd Blue Pkwy,   , This award-winning schools first campus outside of Warrensburg, Summit Center offers flexible city hours in a state-of-the-art facility.  Baker University-Lees Summit, 1278 NE Windsor Dr, (816) 347-0559,     Unity Institute, at Unity Village,   , With several classes to promote your understanding within, the Unity Institute is a peaceful to sit and study an afternoon away.</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">63183</field>
		<field name="title">McAllen</field>
		<field name="main">learn</field>
		<field name="name">universities and colleges</field>
		<field name="content">University of Texas - Pan American (UTPA) is in nearby Edinburg, TX.      South Texas College (STC) has five campuses in the Rio Grande Valley.  Three of them are located in McAllen.   Pecan Campus - 3201 W Pecan Blvd. Dr. Ramiro R. Casso Nursing and Allied Health Campus - 1101 E. Vermont Ave. Technology Campus - 3700 W Military Hwy. Mid-Valley Campus - Weslaco, TX  Starr County Campus - Rio Grande City, TX</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">63184</field>
		<field name="title">McAllen</field>
		<field name="main">learn</field>
		<field name="name">public libraries</field>
		<field name="content">McAllen has three public libraries, including the main library and two branch libraries.     Main Library - 4001 N 23rd St. Lark Branch Library - 2601 Lark Ave. Palm View Branch Library - 3401 Jordan Ave.</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">63185</field>
		<field name="title">Newark (New Jersey)</field>
		<field name="main">learn</field>
		<field name="section">libraries</field>
		<field name="name">Newark Public Library</field>
		<field name="content">A great facility to explore, pick up a book, and learn a little something in the city.</field>
		<field name="url">http://www.npl.org/</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">63186</field>
		<field name="title">Saint Paul</field>
		<field name="main">learn</field>
		<field name="name">private</field>
		<field name="content">College of Visual Arts .   Macalester College .   University of St. Thomas .   Hamline University .   St. Catherine University .   Concordia University .   McNally Smith College of Music .</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">63187</field>
		<field name="title">Saint Paul</field>
		<field name="main">learn</field>
		<field name="name">public</field>
		<field name="content">Metropolitan State University .   Saint Paul College .   University of Minnesotas St Paul campus .</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">63188</field>
		<field name="title">Spartanburg</field>
		<field name="main">learn</field>
		<field name="section">schools</field>
		<field name="name">south carolina school for the deaf and the blind</field>
		<field name="content">The South Carolina School for the Deaf and the Blind (SCSDB) is a specialized instructional and resource center. It provides services statewide for individuals who are deaf, blind or sensory multidisabled (children and adults), their families and the professionals who work with them. SCSDB offers programs for preschool, elementary, middle school, high school, sensory multidisabled, and vocational educational students, as well as a variety of outreach and support services. The main campus is in Spartanburg, and regional centers are located throughout the state.</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">63189</field>
		<field name="title">Spartanburg</field>
		<field name="main">learn</field>
		<field name="section">colleges</field>
		<field name="name">converse college</field>
		<field name="content">Converse College is many things: rich in history and tradition; a place with the faculty, resources, and reputation to get you where you’re headed in life; and a community where people matter most of all. Converse College has been preparing women to be strong leaders in their professions and in their communities for over 100 years. Here, women come first – in the classrooms, science labs, and music rehearsal halls; on our playing fields and in our student organizations. This commitment to our students ensures that throughout their Converse experience and beyond, they will be involved, prepared, and accomplished.</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">63190</field>
		<field name="title">Spartanburg</field>
		<field name="main">learn</field>
		<field name="section">colleges</field>
		<field name="name">sherman college of straight chiropractic</field>
		<field name="content">A Sherman education gives students a distinct advantage. They have the ability to integrate the duties of a primary care chiropractic provider from a modern-day health care perspective with an appreciation for vitalistic principles – mainly that the body is a self-regulated, self-healing organism.</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">63191</field>
		<field name="title">Spartanburg</field>
		<field name="main">learn</field>
		<field name="section">colleges</field>
		<field name="name">spartanburg methodist college</field>
		<field name="content">Spartanburg Methodist College (SMC) is one of the few colleges in the South devoted exclusively to the freshmen and sophomore years of college. The purpose of Spartanburg Methodist College, a two-year, coeducational institution related to the United Methodist Church, is to develop the worth and abilities of each individual through programs relevant to academic and personal needs. The College strives for a values-oriented atmosphere in the Christian tradition in which students can develop a sensitivity to the needs of others and from which they can assume responsible positions in society.</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">63192</field>
		<field name="title">Spartanburg</field>
		<field name="main">learn</field>
		<field name="section">colleges</field>
		<field name="name">spartanburg community college</field>
		<field name="content">Spartanburg Community College is a public, suburban, two-year comprehensive, open-admission institution of higher education serving the citizens of the upstate counties of Spartanburg, Cherokee and Union in South Carolina. The College advances economic development of the region through programs, services and partnerships that address emerging and continuing employment needs in a rapidly changing global environment. Through excellence in teaching and learning, the College promotes lifelong learning and helps students reach their personal and professional goals.</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">63193</field>
		<field name="title">Spartanburg</field>
		<field name="main">learn</field>
		<field name="section">colleges</field>
		<field name="name">univerity of south carolina upstate</field>
		<field name="content">University of South Carolina Upstate aims to become one of the Southeast’s leading “metropolitan” universities … a university that acknowledges as its fundamental reason for being its relationship to expanding populations along the I-85 corridor.  It aims to be recognized nationally among its peer metropolitan institutions for its excellence in education and commitment to its students, for its involvement in the Upstate, and for the clarity and integrity of its metropolitan mission.</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">63194</field>
		<field name="title">Spartanburg</field>
		<field name="main">learn</field>
		<field name="section">colleges</field>
		<field name="name">wofford college</field>
		<field name="content">Wofford offers distinctive learning opportunities that set it apart from other liberal arts colleges. They provide students with meaningful study-abroad experiences, exciting and socially useful service opportunities, career-related and experiential learning possibilities, interaction with great academians from across the world, and exposure to renowned authors, artists, and business and professional leaders.</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">63195</field>
		<field name="title">Summit County (Ohio)</field>
		<field name="main">learn</field>
		<field name="name">career centers</field>
		<field name="content">Portage Lakes Career Center,</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">63196</field>
		<field name="title">Summit County (Ohio)</field>
		<field name="main">learn</field>
		<field name="name">colleges and universities</field>
		<field name="content">The University of Akron,   .</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">63197</field>
		<field name="title">Volusia County</field>
		<field name="main">learn</field>
		<field name="name">colleges and universities</field>
		<field name="content">Bethune-Cookman University (Daytona Beach)  Daytona State College (Campuses in multiple locations around the County)  Embry-Riddle Aeronautical University (Daytona Beach)  Keiser College (Daytona Beach)  Stetson University (DeLand)  University of Central Florida, Daytona Beach Campus</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">63198</field>
		<field name="title">Volusia County</field>
		<field name="main">learn</field>
		<field name="name">vocational</field>
		<field name="content">Advanced Technology Center (Daytona Beach)  Florida Technical College    (DeLand)  International Academy Beauty School    (South Daytona)  Palmer College of Chiropractic (Port Orange)  Phoenix East Aviation (Daytona Beach)  The Airline Academy (Daytona Beach)  WyoTech (formerly AMI)    (Daytona Beach)</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">63199</field>
		<field name="title">Charlotte/Elizabeth</field>
		<field name="main">learn</field>
		<field name="name">learn</field>
		<field name="content">Central Piedmont Community College    - The main branch is located just southeast of I-277, though there are others scattered around the area. CPCC has been noted as a relatively high-quality community college, and has increasingly integrated itself into the life of the city (though the central campus itself is still a bit bland). Recently, the college constructed a major new theater building, with a landmark statue on its front lawn.</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">63200</field>
		<field name="title">Iowa City</field>
		<field name="main">learn</field>
		<field name="name">learn</field>
		<field name="content">The University of Iowa,   , Iowas first university, founded in 1847, UI is a large, public university that offers over 100 programs of study and has a student body of over 30,000 students.   Kirkwood Community College,   , 1816 Lower Muscatine Rd, two-year community college with a small campus in Iowa City, and a main campus 20 miles north in  Cedar Rapids .</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">63201</field>
		<field name="title">Princeton (West Virginia)</field>
		<field name="main">learn</field>
		<field name="name">learn</field>
		<field name="content">Concord University, Vermillion Street in Athens, 304-384-9188 or 888-384-5249,   . A four-year public university established in 1872, offering associates, bachelors and masters degrees in business, education, liberal arts, social sciences, travel and tourism, public administration and entrepreneurial studies.</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">63202</field>
		<field name="title">Easton (Pennsylvania)</field>
		<field name="main">learn</field>
		<field name="name">learn</field>
		<field name="content">Easton is home to Lafayette College   , which was founded in 1826.</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">63203</field>
		<field name="title">Cambridge (Massachusetts)</field>
		<field name="main">learn</field>
		<field name="name">Massachusetts Institute of Technology</field>
		<field name="content">At MITs main entrance. Tours leave weekdays at 10:45AM and 2:45PM.</field>
		<field name="phone">+1 617 253-4795</field>
		<field name="address">77 Massachusetts Avenue</field>
		<field name="url">http://web.mit.edu/visit/</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">63204</field>
		<field name="title">Houston</field>
		<field name="main">learn</field>
		<field name="name">learn</field>
		<field name="content">Houston is home to one of the top universities in the country, Rice University. Its beautifully wooded campus is ideal for an afternoon stroll or jog with loved ones. It is also home to the University of Houston and St. Thomas.</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">63205</field>
		<field name="title">Huntsville (Alabama)</field>
		<field name="main">learn</field>
		<field name="name">learn</field>
		<field name="content">University of Alabama in Huntsville,   . A mid-sized university that specializes in engineering and science. Part of the University of Alabama system. Located off Sparkman Drive near Research Park.   Alabama AM University,   . A historically black college located in Normal in Northeast Huntsville.   Oakwood University,   . A small Seventh Day Adventist school located in Northwest Huntsville.  JF Drake State Technical College,  . A small public technical school in Northeast Huntsville.   Calhoun Community College,   . The largest community college in Alabama, with campuses in Huntsville, Decatur, and Redstone Arsenal.   Athens State University,   . The states only 2-year upper-level university. Located in Athens, which is about 20 miles west of Huntsville.  Florida Institute of Technology,    . Campus located on Redstone Arsenal serving the local high tech community.</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">63206</field>
		<field name="title">Roseville (Minnesota)</field>
		<field name="main">learn</field>
		<field name="name">learn</field>
		<field name="content">Northwestern College</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">63207</field>
		<field name="title">Elizabeth</field>
		<field name="main">learn</field>
		<field name="name">learn</field>
		<field name="content">Elizabeths General Post Office  Most child residents of Elizabeth attend the Public School System. Elizabeth High School has various academies that were newly renovated to gear high school students toward their specific career goals. An alternative to the High School are other private schools in the Elizabeth area. St. Patricks Academy and High School is located in the downtown area of Elizabeth. The academy teaches grades 5-8 while the high school teaches 9-12. St. Patricks High School is well known for their basketball program, with a great success rate of students being offered to play for different colleges. Another private school is St. Benedictines which is located on the border of Elizabeth and Hillside, New Jersey.  For college or for higher learning, Union County College has a campus on the border of North Elizabeth and Midtown Elizabeth. The Drake School of Business is also located on Broad St in Midtown. Kean University is located right on the border of Elizabeth and Union, New Jersey.</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">63208</field>
		<field name="title">Davenport</field>
		<field name="main">learn</field>
		<field name="name">Eastern Branch</field>
		<field name="phone">+1 563 326-7832</field>
		<field name="fax">+1 563  888-4894</field>
		<field name="address">6000 Eastern Ave.</field>
		<field name="hours">M,W 12:00PM-8PM; Tu,Th-Sa 9:30AM-5:30PM</field>
		<field name="alt">East side</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">63209</field>
		<field name="title">Guadalupe (Arizona)</field>
		<field name="main">learn</field>
		<field name="name">learn</field>
		<field name="content">South Mountain Community College Guadalupe Center 9233 S. Avenida Del Yaqui Guadalupe, AZ 85283  Guadalupe Branch Library 9241 S Avenida del Yaqui Guadalupe, AZ 85283 602-652-3000</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">63210</field>
		<field name="title">Concord (New Hampshire)</field>
		<field name="main">learn</field>
		<field name="name">New Hampshire Technical Institute</field>
		<field name="phone">+1 800  247-0179</field>
		<field name="address">31 College Drive</field>
		<field name="url">http://www.nhti.edu</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">63211</field>
		<field name="title">Miami</field>
		<field name="main">learn</field>
		<field name="name">Florida Memorial University</field>
		<field name="content">– A largely African-American student body can be found on this private Baptist co-ed college campus (formerly known as Florida Memorial College). The university has over 1,950 students and majors such as business administration, commerce management, elementary education and criminal justice studies.</field>
		<field name="phone">+1 800 822-1362</field>
		<field name="fax">+1 305 625-4141</field>
		<field name="address">15800 Northwest 42nd Ave</field>
		<field name="url">http://www.fmuniv.edu/</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">63212</field>
		<field name="title">Bemidji</field>
		<field name="main">learn</field>
		<field name="name">learn</field>
		<field name="content">Bemidji State University  Concordia Language Village</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">63213</field>
		<field name="title">Bloomington-Normal</field>
		<field name="main">learn</field>
		<field name="name">Lincoln College-Normal</field>
		<field name="content">An extension of Lincoln College-Lincoln offering bachelors and associates degrees.</field>
		<field name="address">715 W, Raab RD</field>
		<field name="url">http://www,lincolncollege.edu/normal</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">63214</field>
		<field name="title">Sierra Vista</field>
		<field name="main">learn</field>
		<field name="name">Cochise College</field>
		<field name="content">A two-year college with another campus in Douglas.</field>
		<field name="phone">+1 520-515-0500</field>
		<field name="store">31.564605,-110.246476</field>
		<field name="address">901 N Colombo Ave</field>
		<field name="tollfree">+1 800-966-7943</field>
		<field name="url">http://www.cochise.edu/contact/sierra-vista-campus/</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">63215</field>
		<field name="title">Wellesley</field>
		<field name="main">learn</field>
		<field name="name">Wellesley College</field>
		<field name="content">One of the esteemed "Seven Sisters" schools.</field>
		<field name="phone">+1 781 283-1000</field>
		<field name="address">106 Central Street</field>
		<field name="url">http://www.wellesley.edu</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">63216</field>
		<field name="title">Fuquay-Varina</field>
		<field name="main">learn</field>
		<field name="name">learn</field>
		<field name="content">The local newspaper is the Fuquay-Varina Independent, 209 E Vance Street, +1 919 552-5675,   . Daily newspaper.</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">63217</field>
		<field name="title">High Point</field>
		<field name="main">learn</field>
		<field name="name">learn</field>
		<field name="content">High Point University  - High Point University is a private liberal arts university with approximately 3000 undergraduate and graduate students. It is affiliated with the United Methodist Church</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">63218</field>
		<field name="title">Dayton</field>
		<field name="main">learn</field>
		<field name="name">National College - Dayton</field>
		<field name="content">National College is a health care training college.</field>
		<field name="phone">+1 937 299-9450</field>
		<field name="address">1837 Woodman Center Dr, Kettering</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">63219</field>
		<field name="title">Annapolis</field>
		<field name="main">learn</field>
		<field name="name">learn</field>
		<field name="content">Annapolis is home to St. Johns College    (which also has a campus in Santa Fe). St. Johns has an undergraduate and graduate studies programs in the Great Books tradition. All are welcome to attend the free, weekly lecture series    during the school year, or to visit the Greenfield Library   . The school also hosts Saturday Seminars    and a Continuing Education and Fine Arts program   .</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">63220</field>
		<field name="title">Akron</field>
		<field name="main">learn</field>
		<field name="name">University of Akron</field>
		<field name="content">The University of Akron is one of the best schools in the country for engineering and polymer science.</field>
		<field name="phone">+1-330 -972-7077</field>
		<field name="fax">+1-(330)-972-7022</field>
		<field name="address">302 Buchtel Common</field>
		<field name="url">http://www.uakron.edu/</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">63221</field>
		<field name="title">Berkeley (California)</field>
		<field name="main">learn</field>
		<field name="name">Berkeley City College</field>
		<field name="directions">on Center St</field>
		<field name="address">2020 Milvia St</field>
		<field name="alt">formerly Vista Community College</field>
		<field name="url">http://www.vistacollege.edu</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">63222</field>
		<field name="title">Grand Marais</field>
		<field name="main">learn</field>
		<field name="name">learn</field>
		<field name="content">Take a class at North House Folk School   , teaches traditional northern crafts, everything from wooden boat building to knife making to baking.    Grand Marais Art Colony , Begun in 1947, it is Minnesotas oldest art colony.  Offers classes in oil, water colors, ceramics, glass, print and more.  Special events include the Grand Marais Art Festival, held in the middle of July, and the Plein Aire Painting Competition at the end of August.</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">63223</field>
		<field name="title">La Mirada</field>
		<field name="main">learn</field>
		<field name="name">learn</field>
		<field name="content">Biola University   , Private Christian Liberal-arts College. Home to 6 graduate schools. They offer adult certification programs that dont have all the stipulations of a standard degree. Auditing classes is also an option for those looking to learn, but with less commitment than a full four-year degree. For those interested in a full program, Biola has a good academic reputation. Go Eagles!   The Community Center across the parking lot from Regional Park, behind the Firehouse, offers a variety of classes and workshops open to the public. Everything from Jazzercise to memoir-writing. You must register for classes, so if you arent here for at least a semester, its not likely theyll let you join for one class session (unless you have a friend in the class).</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">63224</field>
		<field name="title">Waltham</field>
		<field name="main">learn</field>
		<field name="name">learn</field>
		<field name="content">Bentley College, 175 Forest St., +1 781-891-2000,   . Brandeis University, 415 South St., +1 781-736-3500,    .</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">63225</field>
		<field name="title">Jersey City</field>
		<field name="main">learn</field>
		<field name="name">learn</field>
		<field name="content">New Jersey City University, 2039 Kennedy Boulevard,   . Saint Peters College, 2641 Kennedy Boulevard,   . Hudson County Community College, 70 Sip Avenue,   .</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">63226</field>
		<field name="title">Dayton</field>
		<field name="main">learn</field>
		<field name="name">Sinclair Community College</field>
		<field name="address">444 W Third St</field>
		<field name="tollfree">+1 800-315-3000</field>
		<field name="url">http://www.sinclair.edu/</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">63227</field>
		<field name="title">Newark (New Jersey)</field>
		<field name="main">learn</field>
		<field name="name">New Jersey Medical School</field>
		<field name="alt">UMDNJ</field>
		<field name="url">http://www.umdnj.edu/</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">63228</field>
		<field name="title">Cincinnati</field>
		<field name="main">learn</field>
		<field name="name">Hebrew Union College-Jewish Institute of Religion</field>
		<field name="content">HUC-JIR is the oldest "new world" Jewish seminary, founded in 1875 by Cincinnati Rabbi Isaac M. Wise.  Since Rabbi Wise was one of the key rabbis in the development of Reform Judaism, the school follows in his footsteps preparing its students for services in the Reform community.</field>
		<field name="address">3101 Clifton Avenue</field>
		<field name="url">http://www.huc.edu/</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">63229</field>
		<field name="title">Troy (New York)</field>
		<field name="main">learn</field>
		<field name="name">learn</field>
		<field name="content">Rensselaer Polytechnical Institute, 110 8th Street     Hudson Valley Community College, 80 Vandenburgh Avenue    A part of the State University of New York (SUNY) system</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">63230</field>
		<field name="title">Kansas City</field>
		<field name="main">learn</field>
		<field name="name">Downtown Library</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">63231</field>
		<field name="title">Smithfield (Rhode Island)</field>
		<field name="main">learn</field>
		<field name="name">Bryant University</field>
		<field name="content">Bryant University was established in 1863. The schools of academics include: College of Arts and Sciences, College of Business, and The Graduate School of Business. Both bachelor and master degrees are offered and part-time degree programs are available. In 2008, The university has 3,364 undergraduates with 90% of the students from out of state.</field>
		<field name="phone">+1-800-622-7001</field>
		<field name="address">1150 Douglas Pike</field>
		<field name="url">http://www.bryant.edu</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">63232</field>
		<field name="title">Trenton</field>
		<field name="main">learn</field>
		<field name="name">learn</field>
		<field name="content">The College of New Jersey (TCNJ)  Thomas Edison State College</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">63233</field>
		<field name="title">Van Wert (Ohio)</field>
		<field name="main">learn</field>
		<field name="name">Vantage Career Center</field>
		<field name="content">Vantage Career Center is proud to provide diverse opportunities for high school and adult education for the members of Van Wert County and the surrounding area.</field>
		<field name="phone">+1 -800-686-3944 or +1 419-238-5411</field>
		<field name="address">818 N. Franklin St.</field>
		<field name="url">http://www.vantagecareercenter.com/</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">63234</field>
		<field name="title">Alliance (Ohio)</field>
		<field name="main">learn</field>
		<field name="name">Mount Union College</field>
		<field name="content">Mount Union is a private, liberal arts college.</field>
		<field name="phone">+1 800 992-6682</field>
		<field name="address">1972 Clark Ave</field>
		<field name="email">info@muc.edu</field>
		<field name="url">http://www.muc.edu</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">63235</field>
		<field name="title">Cambridge (Massachusetts)</field>
		<field name="main">learn</field>
		<field name="name">Harvard Events and Information Center</field>
		<field name="content">Holyoke Center Arcade, 1350 Massachusetts Avenue. Student-led free tours of campus originate from here. It also has interactive computer displays, a print library, a video room, and you can pick up flyers for all of the free lectures, films, and classes at University museums, such as the Harvard Museum of Natural History, and the Harvard Art Museum.</field>
		<field name="phone">+1 617 495-1573</field>
		<field name="fax">+1 617-495-0905</field>
		<field name="url">http://www.harvard.edu/community/visitors.html</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">63236</field>
		<field name="title">Columbia (Maryland)</field>
		<field name="main">learn</field>
		<field name="name">learn</field>
		<field name="content">American Career Institute,   . A career training school with a campus in Columbia, Maryland.</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">63237</field>
		<field name="title">Murray (Kentucky)</field>
		<field name="main">learn</field>
		<field name="name">learn</field>
		<field name="content">Murray State University  is one of the highest rated liberal arts schools in the Southeastern United States, brings a unique cultural element to the city.  The school supports athletic teams, known as Racers   , in six mens sports, eight womens sports, and one coeducational sport (rifle shooting). The best-known Racers team is the mens basketball team, a perennial invitee to the NCAA basketball tournament.</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">63238</field>
		<field name="title">Oakland</field>
		<field name="main">learn</field>
		<field name="name">California College of the Arts</field>
		<field name="content">As the name implies, a large art college with a variety of disciplines. One caveat - the school is split into two locations, this listing is for the Oakland campus. The other is in  San Francisco .</field>
		<field name="directions">At College Ave.</field>
		<field name="phone">+1 510 594-3600</field>
		<field name="address">5212 Broadway</field>
		<field name="tollfree">+1-800-447-1278</field>
		<field name="url">http://www.cca.edu</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">63239</field>
		<field name="title">Chicago</field>
		<field name="main">learn</field>
		<field name="name">learn</field>
		<field name="content">Several major and minor universities call Chicago home. The  University of Chicago  and  Northwestern University  are undoubtedly the most prestigious among them. The University of Chicagos Gothic campus is in  Hyde Park , which is, famously, "home to more Nobel Prizes per square kilometer than any other neighborhood on Earth." Further north, in the  Bronzeville  area, is the Illinois Institute of Technology, which has notable programs in engineering and architecture. Northwestern University has its main campus in  Evanston , just north of Chicago, but it also has campuses in the  Near North  off Michigan Ave, including its medical, law, and business schools.  On the North Side, there are two major Catholic universities with over a hundred years in Chicago: DePaul University, in  Lincoln Park , and Loyola University, in  Rogers Park . Both schools also have campuses in the  Loop . Rush University Medical School, on the Near West Side, traces its roots back even further, to 1837.  Dating back to 1891, North Park University serves as another fine private liberal arts university in  Albany Park  on the Northwest Side.  A handful of schools in the  Loop  attract students in the creative arts. Columbia College has an enviable location on Michigan Avenue, and its programs in film are continually noted as one of the top in the nation, along with its programs in creative writing and photography which are also are well-regarded. The School of the Art Institute is generally regarded as one of the top three art and design schools in the country and is one of the few art schools that does not require its students to declare majors. The Illinois Institute of Art specializes in different fields of art and design, with a top-notch culinary program. The main campus of Roosevelt University, former home to Chicago heavyweights like Harold Washington and Ramsey Lewis, is in the Auditorium Theatre building.  To the west of the Loop, built over the remains of Little Italy and Maxwell Street neighborhoods is the brutalist  Near West Side  campus of the University of Illinois at Chicago (UIC), the second-largest member of the Illinois state university system.  The  City Colleges of Chicago  are scattered throughout the city. They include Harold Washington College ( Loop ), Harry S. Truman College ( Uptown ), Malcolm X College ( Near West Side ), Wright College ( Humboldt Park ), Kennedy-King College ( Englewood ), Daley College ( Southwest Side ), and Olive-Harvey College ( Far Southeast Side ).</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">63240</field>
		<field name="title">Wheeling</field>
		<field name="main">learn</field>
		<field name="name">learn</field>
		<field name="content">The local newspaper is The Intelligencer and Wheeling News-Register, 1500 Main Street, +1 304-233-0100 or +1 800-852-5475 (both local),   .   Wheeling Jesuit University, 316 Washington Avenue, +1 800-624-6992,   . A Jesuit, Catholic, liberal arts university offering over 30 majors.</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">63241</field>
		<field name="title">Lawrence (Kansas)</field>
		<field name="main">learn</field>
		<field name="name">learn</field>
		<field name="content">University of Kansas.  Home of the Spencer Museum of Art   , the Museum of Natural History (Dyche Hall   , including the Panorama of North American Mammals and Comanche, the "Lone Survivor" of the Battle of Little Bighorn), and the Dole Institute of Politics   .</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">63242</field>
		<field name="title">Fort Smith</field>
		<field name="main">learn</field>
		<field name="name">learn</field>
		<field name="content">University of Arkansas—Fort Smith, 5210 Grand Ave., +1 479 788-7000    Fort Smiths local university branch.</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">63243</field>
		<field name="title">Austin</field>
		<field name="main">learn</field>
		<field name="name">learn</field>
		<field name="content">Austin is one of the premier educational areas in the nation.  The University of Texas at Austin is one of the best universities in the world, public or private.  The flagship institution of the University of Texas System, it is also one of the largest universities in the world, both in terms of endowment, and in terms of student population.  UT has been the largest university in the United States, but has intentionally limited enrollment and now ranks in the top five nationally.  The red-tiled roofs of the "Forty Acres," as it is known, shelter many cultural and entertainment institutions.  The campus is beautiful and vibrant, and visitors are welcome.  Austin is a college town as well as a government and high-tech center.  It draws its population from all over, and many students decide to stay.  This gives Austin a high level of general education and a diverse cultural scene.   Austin Community College   Concordia University Texas   Huston-Tillotson College   St. Edwards University   University of Texas</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">63244</field>
		<field name="title">Davenport</field>
		<field name="main">learn</field>
		<field name="name">Fairmount Branch</field>
		<field name="phone">+1 563 326-7832</field>
		<field name="hoursextra">Su 1PM-4PM (October–April)</field>
		<field name="fax">+1 563 326-7806</field>
		<field name="address">3000 N. Fairmount St.</field>
		<field name="hours">M,W,F 9:30AM-5:30PM, Tu,Th 12PM-8PM, Sa 9:30AM-5:30PM</field>
		<field name="alt">West side</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">63245</field>
		<field name="title">Philadelphia</field>
		<field name="main">learn</field>
		<field name="name">learn</field>
		<field name="content">Philadelphia is rich with educational opportunities. Universities include Temple University,  Philadelphia University ,  Drexel University  with the only co-op program in the area, the Ivy League  University of Pennsylvania ,  La Salle University  a major Catholic university,  Saint Josephs University  a Jesuit university, and  The Lutheran Theological Seminary at Philadelphia  a divinity school; as well as  "Westminster Theological Seminary"  in Glenside.  The  Community College of Philadelphia  is Philadelphias premier community college.   Art schools include the  University of the Arts , one of the most prestigious art schools in America,  Pennsylvania Academy of Fine Arts ,  Moore College of Art and Design  an all women college,  Hussian School of Art , and the  Art Institute Philadelphia .   Trade schools include  The Wine School of Philadelphia  which offers professional sommelier winemaking diplomas, along with  wine tasting classes .</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">63246</field>
		<field name="title">Cincinnati</field>
		<field name="main">learn</field>
		<field name="name">University of Cincinnati</field>
		<field name="content">UC is a public university located in the Uptown neighborhoods of Avondale, Corryville, Clifton Heights, and University Heights. Ranked as one of America’s Top 25 public research universities and in the Top 50 of all American universities, UC has an annual enrollment of approximately 40,000 students, making it one of the largest universities in the U.S. Though many incorrectly refer to the main Campus of the University as its "Clifton Campus", the University is not located within the Clifton neighborhood. In 2010, Forbes Magazine listed the University of Cincinnati as one of the worlds most beautiful college campuses alongside prestigious company like Oxford University and Yale University.</field>
		<field name="phone">+1-513 -556-6000</field>
		<field name="address">2600 Clifton Avenue</field>
		<field name="url">http://www.uc.edu/</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">63247</field>
		<field name="title">Volusia County</field>
		<field name="main">learn</field>
		<field name="name">learn</field>
		<field name="content">Public primary and secondary education is handled by Volusia County Schools. Some of the larger private schools include Father Lopez Catholic High School.  The life-sized Wright Flyer statue at Embry-Riddle Aeronautical Universitys Daytona Beach, FL, USA campus.</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">63248</field>
		<field name="title">Buffalo/North Buffalo</field>
		<field name="main">learn</field>
		<field name="name">learn</field>
		<field name="content">Located on 154 acres (62 ha) of land in University Heights, the South Campus is the oldest of the three campuses of the  University at Buffalo , the largest school in the State University of New York (SUNY) system as well as the largest public university in the Northeast. Founded in 1846 as a private medical college with future U.S. President Millard Fillmore as its first chancellor, the University at Buffalo moved to the former site of the Erie County Alms House in 1912, where the preeminent local architectural firm of the time, E. B. Green Son, built a lovely Georgian-Revival style campus modelled after Trinity College in  Dublin . Though most of the academic departments were transferred to UBs sprawling new North Campus in Amherst in the late 1960s and early 1970s, the South Campus still contains UBs Schools of Dentistry, Nursing, and Architecture and Planning, as well as the Health Sciences Library, Biomedical Science Research Complex, and student housing. UB Medical School is currently in the process of moving to the new Downtown Campus located in the  Medical Corridor .   Medaille College  is a small private college located at the southern end of Parkside, on Agassiz Circle. Founded in 1875 as a Catholic girls school by the Sisters of St. Joseph, Medaille has been coeducational and nonsectarian since 1968, and boasts about 3,000 students and a full range of courses emphasizing the liberal arts and sciences. Medaille also has branch campuses in  Rochester  and the nearby suburb of Amherst, the fruits of a rapid expansion of the school that began in the 1990s and continues through the present day.</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">63249</field>
		<field name="title">Roseburg</field>
		<field name="main">learn</field>
		<field name="name">learn</field>
		<field name="content">Umpqua Community College 1</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">63250</field>
		<field name="title">Allentown</field>
		<field name="main">learn</field>
		<field name="name">learn</field>
		<field name="content">Allentown is home to  Muhlenberg College ,  Cedar Crest College  and the Donley Center, the downtown Allentown campus of Lehigh Carbon Community College (LCCC). Other colleges are located throughout  Lehigh Valley .</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">63251</field>
		<field name="title">Miami Beach</field>
		<field name="main">learn</field>
		<field name="name">learn</field>
		<field name="content">Miami-Dade Community College    Barry University    Florida International University    University of Miami</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">63252</field>
		<field name="title">Portland (Oregon)</field>
		<field name="main">learn</field>
		<field name="name">learn</field>
		<field name="content">The Multnomah County Library (see " Connect " below) hosts language study groups.   Reed College  is a top small liberal arts college with a beautiful campus. The college frequently hosts educational events and lectures. The campus is worth checking out if not only for the nuclear reactor that is located there.   Lewis Clark College ,  in Southwest Portland, is the other small liberal arts college with a beautiful campus. For information about upcoming events and lectures, check the  campus events calendar .  The library hosts the  Roger D. Wendlick collection  of Lewis and Clark Expedition literature.   Oregon Health and Science University  is arguably the most prestigious research institution and hospital in Oregon. The site looks like a fortress from a distance. For fun, you can take the aerial tram from downtown to OHSU. The institution is the largest employer in Oregon.   Portland State University  lies Downtown. PSU is the most popular university in Portland, boasting a population of nearly 30,000 attending students. Both the CL and NS Portland Streetcar lines, as well as the MAX Green and Yellow lines, are vital transit connections between PSU and outlying areas of Portland metro.</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">63253</field>
		<field name="title">Overland Park</field>
		<field name="main">learn</field>
		<field name="name">learn</field>
		<field name="content">Johnson County Community College is located at the intersection of College Blvd. and Quivira Rd.  With 35,000 students, JCCC offers both 2-year and 4-year programs.  Also, the campus is host to the Nerman Museum of Contemporary Art, as well as an on-site food court and several coffee-shops.</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">63254</field>
		<field name="title">Oakland</field>
		<field name="main">learn</field>
		<field name="name">Laney College</field>
		<field name="content">Located south of Lake Merritt, one of the citys two community colleges through the Peralta Community College District.</field>
		<field name="directions">Between E 8th St. and 10th St.</field>
		<field name="phone">+1 510 834-5740</field>
		<field name="address">900 Fallon St.</field>
		<field name="url">http://www.laney.edu</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">63255</field>
		<field name="title">Lowell (Massachusetts)</field>
		<field name="main">learn</field>
		<field name="name">Blaine Beauty School</field>
		<field name="phone">+1 978 459-9959</field>
		<field name="address">231 Central St</field>
		<field name="alt">Lowell Campus</field>
		<field name="url">http://www.blainebeautyschools.com/</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">63256</field>
		<field name="title">Modesto</field>
		<field name="main">learn</field>
		<field name="name">Modesto Junior College</field>
		<field name="content">One of the oldest community colleges in the state.  Many buildings date back to the 1920s and 30s.  Famous alumni include George Lucas and Jeremy Renner.</field>
		<field name="phone">+1 209 575-6498</field>
		<field name="address">435 College Ave</field>
		<field name="hours">8AM-5PM</field>
		<field name="url">http://www.mjc.edu</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">63257</field>
		<field name="title">Davenport</field>
		<field name="main">learn</field>
		<field name="name">Main Library</field>
		<field name="phone">+1 563 326-7832</field>
		<field name="fax">+1 563 326-7809</field>
		<field name="address">321 N. Main St.</field>
		<field name="hours">M 12PM-8PM, Tu-Sa 9AM-5:30PM</field>
		<field name="alt">Downtown</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">63258</field>
		<field name="title">Martinsburg (West Virginia)</field>
		<field name="main">learn</field>
		<field name="name">learn</field>
		<field name="content">The local newspaper is the Journal News, 207 W King Street, 304-263-8931 or 800-448-1895,   .</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">63259</field>
		<field name="title">Stockton (California)</field>
		<field name="main">learn</field>
		<field name="name">learn</field>
		<field name="content">Stockton is home to University of the Pacific   and Delta College   , a part of the California Community College system as well as an extension branch of CSU Stanislaus  .</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">63260</field>
		<field name="title">Medford (Massachusetts)</field>
		<field name="main">learn</field>
		<field name="name">learn</field>
		<field name="content">Tufts University, Phone: +1 617 628-5000,   .</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">63261</field>
		<field name="title">Newark (New Jersey)</field>
		<field name="main">learn</field>
		<field name="name">New Jersey Institute of Technology</field>
		<field name="url">http://www.njit.edu/</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">63262</field>
		<field name="title">Phoenix</field>
		<field name="main">learn</field>
		<field name="name">Maricopa Community Colleges</field>
		<field name="content">Largest system of community colleges in the United States, with 10 campuses in the metro Maricopa County area; numerous community and adult education programs.</field>
		<field name="url">http://www.maricopa.edu</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">63263</field>
		<field name="title">Traverse City</field>
		<field name="main">learn</field>
		<field name="name">learn</field>
		<field name="content">Traverse City Record-Eagle, 120 W Front Street, 231-946-2000,   . Daily morning newspaper.   Grand Traverse Herald, 616-933-1412,   . Weekly community newspaper.   Northwestern Michigan College, 1701 E Front Street, 231-995-1135 or 800-748-0566,   . A community college since 1951, offering associates degrees and professional certificates, as well as baccalaureate and graduate degrees from 10 partner universities.</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">63264</field>
		<field name="title">Harrisonburg</field>
		<field name="main">learn</field>
		<field name="name">learn</field>
		<field name="content">The community is a major educational center.    James Madison University,   .  A public university that was found in 1908 and has approximately 16,000 students with a 630 acre campus.  Offers both undergraduate and graduate level degrees.  Eastern Mennonite University,   .  A Christian liberal arts university that enrolls approximately 920 students.  It is also the home of the Eastern Mennonite Seminary.</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">63265</field>
		<field name="title">Des Moines</field>
		<field name="main">learn</field>
		<field name="name">learn</field>
		<field name="content">Des Moines is home to a few institutions of higher learning, the largest being Drake University with enrollment around 5,000.   Drake University, 2507 University Ave,   .  Founded in 1881 and today offers more than 70 degrees of study through three colleges and three schools.  DU is the home of the Bulldogs and offers Division 1-A athletic competition for nearly all varsity sports.  Home of the Drake Relays, arguably the nations top track and field event.   Des Moines University (DMU), 3200 Grand Ave   .  The university was originally named Dr. S.S. Still College of Osteopathy in 1898.  Offers six degree programs available through the College of Osteopathic Medicine, College of Podiatric Medicine and Surgery, and College of Health Sciences.   Grand View University, 1200 Grandview Ave,   .  Four-year liberal arts college offering 35 areas of study.  The athletic program is a member of the National Association of Intercollegiate Athletics (NAIA).   Des Moines Area Community College (DMACC), Various locations   .  Iowas largest two-year college program.   AIB College of Business, 2500 Fleur Dr   .  Founded in 1921, AIB is a non-profit, coeducational two-year college of business which offers associate degree and diploma courses of study.   Mercy College of Health Sciences, 928 6th Ave   .  The school was founded in 1899 (then-known as Mercy Hospital Training School) and is a subsidiary corporation of Mercy Medical Center-Des Moines.  Its purpose is to train nurses and allied medical care professionals.</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">63266</field>
		<field name="title">Cambridge (Massachusetts)</field>
		<field name="main">learn</field>
		<field name="name">learn</field>
		<field name="content">The Great Dome at MIT   Many visitors to Cambridge are there to see its two major universities, Massachusetts Institute of Technology (MIT) and Harvard University, either as tourists or as prospective students. Both universities have extensive information for visiting prospects. As this typically varies with type of student (graduate, undergraduate) and program of study (for graduate students), prospectives are best advised to visit the school websites that interest them.         Harvard Yard, located right by the Harvard stop on the Red Line subway, is the center of Harvard College and a favorite of tourists, who can often be seen taking pictures of each other at the statue of John Harvard, located in front of Massachusetts Hall.  In the shadows of these two giants are other fine schools.</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">63267</field>
		<field name="title">Indianapolis</field>
		<field name="main">learn</field>
		<field name="name">learn</field>
		<field name="content">Butler Universitys historic campus hosts Hinkel Fieldhouse, an apothecary garden, observatory, and Clowes Hall (pictured)  Butler University 4600 Sunset Ave. +1 800-368-6852    Located on the near northside this historic campus was founded in 1855 focusing on liberal arts education. Home to the Butler Bulldogs and Clowes Hall.  Herron School of Art 735 W New York St, +1 317 278-9400    One of the top art schools in the country, Herron is attached to IUPUI. 800 students attend full and part-time in the new building on IUPUI campus and other areas of town. From art history to painting, photography to sculpture its all covered here.  MedTech College, 6612 E 75th St, +1 317 845-0100     IUPUI 425 University Blvd, +1 317 274-5555    The citys largest college campus is the home for Indiana University and Purdue University in the city. Mainly a commuter college the school features technical and liberal arts schools. The new campus center has added a stronger form of community, and this campus welcomes all levels of learners.  University of Indianapolis 1400 E Hanna St, +1 317 788-3368</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">63268</field>
		<field name="title">Stamford (Connecticut)</field>
		<field name="main">learn</field>
		<field name="name">University of Connecticut at Stamford</field>
		<field name="content">Located in downtown Stamford this commuter branch of the University of Connecticut serves as a school offering 4-year bachelors degrees in ten majors. Also offers two masters degree programs, and access to internship and job placement programs.</field>
		<field name="phone">+1 203  251-8400</field>
		<field name="address">1 University Pl, Stamford, CT 06901-2315</field>
		<field name="url">http://www.stamford.uconn.edu/</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">63269</field>
		<field name="title">Miami</field>
		<field name="main">learn</field>
		<field name="name">learn</field>
		<field name="content">Island Dreamer Sailing School, 555 NE 15th St, +1 561281-2689    Live aboard sailing and cruising classes specializing in multi-day trips to the Florida Keys for couples and families that want to gain the skills to charter or live on a sailboat. Certified by the American Sailing Association.     New World School of the Arts, 300 Northeast 2nd Second Ave. (in Downtown Miami), +1 305 237-3135   . This institution offers conservatory education to talented high school and college students. Its highly selective in its admissions, and highly intensive in its education. Alumni of New World have gone on to successful careers in Hollywood, on Broadway, and in other prestigious arts venues around the world. In addition, many of todays top talents in commercial arts, advertising, public relations and architecture got their creative foundations at this highly-ranked school. Offers programs in theater, visual arts, dance and music for high school students and college, with joint degrees offered between Miami-Dade Public Schools, Miami-Dade Community College and the University of Florida.        Miami-Dade College,    – With more than 165,000 students, it is the U.S. largest institution of higher learning, and one of the countrys best community college systems. This community college conveniently has locations in Hialeah, Homestead, Kendall, Downtown Miami, and North Miami and also has locations all around Miami proper.</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">63270</field>
		<field name="title">Dothan</field>
		<field name="main">learn</field>
		<field name="name">learn</field>
		<field name="content">Troy University in Dothan    Wallace Community College    Bethany Divinity College and Seminary</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">63271</field>
		<field name="title">Mercer County (New Jersey)</field>
		<field name="main">learn</field>
		<field name="name">learn</field>
		<field name="content">Mercer County Community College, West Windsor  Princeton University, Princeton  Rider University Lawrence Township  The College of New Jersey (TCNJ), Trenton/Ewing Township  Thomas Edison State College, Trenton</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">63272</field>
		<field name="title">Wellesley</field>
		<field name="main">learn</field>
		<field name="name">Massachusetts Bay Community College (Wellesley Hills campus)</field>
		<field name="content">•.</field>
		<field name="phone">+1 781 239-3000</field>
		<field name="fax">+1 781-239-1047</field>
		<field name="address">50 Oakland Street</field>
		<field name="url">http://www.massbay.edu/</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">63273</field>
		<field name="title">Grundy</field>
		<field name="main">learn</field>
		<field name="name">Appalachian School of Law</field>
		<field name="alt">ASL</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">63274</field>
		<field name="title">Norfolk (Connecticut)</field>
		<field name="main">learn</field>
		<field name="name">learn</field>
		<field name="content">Yale University operates a Summer School of Art and a Summer School of Music in Norfolk. Only current Yale students can apply for the art programs, but the music programs select participants by application/audition   .</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">63275</field>
		<field name="title">Oklahoma City</field>
		<field name="main">learn</field>
		<field name="name">learn</field>
		<field name="content">Oklahoma City University   Oklahoma State University - Oklahoma City   Oklahoma City Community College  Downtown College Consortium  Oklahoma Christian University   University of Oklahoma</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">63276</field>
		<field name="title">Elkins</field>
		<field name="main">learn</field>
		<field name="name">learn</field>
		<field name="content">The local area newspaper is The Inter-Mountain, Their offices are located at 520 Railroad Avenue, 304-636-2121,   .  The city directory for Elkins is  WVHome.com  The place to find out about everything thats going on in the Elkins area.</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">63277</field>
		<field name="title">Phoenix</field>
		<field name="main">learn</field>
		<field name="name">Phoenix School of Law</field>
		<field name="content">New law school, relatively open admissions policy.</field>
		<field name="url">http://www.phoenixlaw.org</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">63278</field>
		<field name="title">Toledo (Ohio)</field>
		<field name="main">learn</field>
		<field name="name">University of Toledo</field>
		<field name="phone">+1-419-530-4636</field>
		<field name="address">Dorr Street and Secor Road</field>
		<field name="url">http://www.utoledo.edu/</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">63279</field>
		<field name="title">Sierra Vista</field>
		<field name="main">learn</field>
		<field name="name">University of Arizona South</field>
		<field name="content">A branch campus of Tucsons University of Arizona.</field>
		<field name="phone">+1 520-458-8278</field>
		<field name="store">31.567567,-110.24506</field>
		<field name="address">1140 N Colombo Ave</field>
		<field name="email">webuas@email.arizona.edu</field>
		<field name="url">http://uas.arizona.edu/</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">63280</field>
		<field name="title">Orange County (California)</field>
		<field name="main">learn</field>
		<field name="name">learn</field>
		<field name="content">Cal State Fullerton  UC Irvine  The Fullerton Arboretum offers 26 acres of gardens open to the public featuring a variety of biospheres as well as weekly classes and plant sales at the Potting Shed. Visit www.fullertonarboretum.org for more information.</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">63281</field>
		<field name="title">Arlington (Texas)</field>
		<field name="main">learn</field>
		<field name="name">learn</field>
		<field name="content">University of Texas at Arlington</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">63282</field>
		<field name="title">Cuyahoga County</field>
		<field name="main">learn</field>
		<field name="name">learn</field>
		<field name="content">Baldwin-Wallace College, Berea  Capital University, Cleveland Center  Case Western Reserve University, Cleveland (University Circle) Cleveland College of Jewish Studies, Beachwood  Cleveland Institute of Art, Cleveland (University Circle) Cleveland State University, Cleveland Cuyahoga Community College, Cleveland, Parma and Warrensville Heights campuses  David N. Myers College, Cleveland  John Carroll University, University Heights  Notre Dame College of Ohio, South Euclid  Ohio College of Podiatric Medicine, Cleveland  Ursuline College, Pepper Pike</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">63283</field>
		<field name="title">Peoria (Illinois)</field>
		<field name="main">learn</field>
		<field name="name">learn</field>
		<field name="content">Bradley University  is the largest school in the region, with approximately 6,000 students.</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">63284</field>
		<field name="title">Fullerton</field>
		<field name="main">learn</field>
		<field name="name">Fullerton College</field>
		<field name="content">Fullerton College is a two-year college offering 90 Associate degree programs.</field>
		<field name="phone">+1 714 992-7000</field>
		<field name="address">321 E. Chapman Ave.</field>
		<field name="url">http://www.fullcoll.edu/</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">63285</field>
		<field name="title">Miami</field>
		<field name="main">learn</field>
		<field name="name">Johnson Wales University—North Miami Campus</field>
		<field name="content">(, – One of Johnson Wales’ many campuses across the country, this co-ed, private university offers majors in the culinary and baking and pastry arts, business and hospitality. This campus is also one of Johnson Wales’ largest after the original school in Providence, Rhode Island, with 2,500 students enrolled.</field>
		<field name="directions">in North Miami</field>
		<field name="phone">+1 305 892-7600</field>
		<field name="fax">+1 305 892-7020</field>
		<field name="address">1701 Northeast 127th St</field>
		<field name="email">admissions@jwu.edu</field>
		<field name="url">http://www.jwu.edu</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">63286</field>
		<field name="title">Broken Arrow</field>
		<field name="main">learn</field>
		<field name="name">learn</field>
		<field name="content">Rhema Bible College, 1025 W. 71st Street,    This 4-year religious college puts on the largest Christmas light display in Northeast Oklahoma.  Helicopter Christmas Light Flights, 918-748-1999, 918-299-5030, www.xmasflights.biz</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">63287</field>
		<field name="title">Dayton</field>
		<field name="main">learn</field>
		<field name="name">DeVry University</field>
		<field name="phone">+1 937 320-3200</field>
		<field name="address">3610 Pentagon Blvd, Beavercreek</field>
		<field name="url">http://www.devry.edu/locations/campuses/loc_dayton.jsp</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">63288</field>
		<field name="title">Concord (New Hampshire)</field>
		<field name="main">learn</field>
		<field name="name">St. Pauls School</field>
		<field name="phone">+1 603  229-4600</field>
		<field name="address">325 Pleasant Street</field>
		<field name="url">http://www.sps.edu</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">63289</field>
		<field name="title">Newport (Rhode Island)</field>
		<field name="main">learn</field>
		<field name="name">learn</field>
		<field name="content">Community College of Rhode Island (CCRI Newport Campus),   . Naval War College, 686 Cushing Rd. (on Newport’s Naval Base),   .  Newport is a great place to learn and take classes in a variety of different activities. Scuba diving and sailing are two incredible summer activities that you can learn in Newport. Learn to dive at the Newport Diving Center and learn to sail at the Newport Sailing School.  There are art classes available at the Newport Art Museum.  The classes are offered year round and are an enjoyable option if you find yourself in Newport during the “off” season (September to May).</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">63290</field>
		<field name="title">Sanford (Florida)</field>
		<field name="main">learn</field>
		<field name="name">learn</field>
		<field name="content">Seminole State College</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">63291</field>
		<field name="title">Amherst (New Hampshire)</field>
		<field name="main">learn</field>
		<field name="name">learn</field>
		<field name="content">Colleges-  New Hampshire College (about 17 miles; Manchester, NH; Full-time enrollment: 3,251)  University of Massachusetts-LOWELL (about 20 miles; Lowell, MA; enrollment: 8,373)  Fitchburg State College (about 22 miles; Fitchburg, MA; enrollment: 3,660)  Mount Wachusett Community College (about 28 miles; Gardner, MA; enrollment: 2,023)  Northern Essex Community College (about 28 miles; Haverhill, MA; enrollment: 3,388)  Merrimack College (about 28 miles; North Andover, MA; enrollment: 2,384)  Middlesex Community College (about 30 miles; Bedford, MA; enrollment: 4,501)</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">63292</field>
		<field name="title">Lowell (Massachusetts)</field>
		<field name="main">learn</field>
		<field name="name">learn</field>
		<field name="content">University of Massachusetts Lowell, One University Av., Phone: +1 978-934-4000,   . Middlesex Community College, (Lowell Campus) 33 Kearney Square,   .</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">63293</field>
		<field name="title">Dayton</field>
		<field name="main">learn</field>
		<field name="name">Wright State University</field>
		<field name="phone">+1 937 775-3333</field>
		<field name="address">3640 Colonel Glenn Hwy</field>
		<field name="url">http://www.wright.edu/</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">63294</field>
		<field name="title">Miami</field>
		<field name="main">learn</field>
		<field name="name">Florida International University</field>
		<field name="content">University Park, (. With over 40,000 students enrolled in this public co-ed university spread out over two campuses, Florida International University is one of the largest universities in Florida and the 11th-largest university in the U.S. With over 280 majors in 26 schools in colleges including its top-ranked College of Business, School of Architecture, College of Engineering, College of Law, and College of Medicine, it is one of Floridas top universities.</field>
		<field name="phone">+1 305 348-2863</field>
		<field name="fax">+1 305 348-3648</field>
		<field name="email">admiss@fiu.edu</field>
		<field name="url">http://www.fiu.edu</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">63295</field>
		<field name="title">La Crosse</field>
		<field name="main">learn</field>
		<field name="name">learn</field>
		<field name="content">University of Wisconsin, La Crosse</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">63296</field>
		<field name="title">Vancouver (Washington)</field>
		<field name="main">learn</field>
		<field name="name">learn</field>
		<field name="content">Clark College   Washington State University Vancouver</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">63297</field>
		<field name="title">Bettendorf</field>
		<field name="main">learn</field>
		<field name="name">learn</field>
		<field name="content">Scott Community College   A two-year school it is part of the Eastern Iowa Community College District.</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">63298</field>
		<field name="title">Logan (West Virginia)</field>
		<field name="main">learn</field>
		<field name="name">learn</field>
		<field name="content">The local paper is the Logan Banner, 435 Stratton Street, 304-752-6950,   . Daily newspaper published since 1888.</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">63299</field>
		<field name="title">Providence</field>
		<field name="main">learn</field>
		<field name="name">learn</field>
		<field name="content">Providence is home to many schools. The city is also home to a few notable colleges.  Providence College 1 Cunningham Square, +1 401 865-1000,     University of Rhode Island Providence Campus 80 Washington Street, +1 401 277-5000,     Rhode Island School of Design 2 College Street, +1 401 454-6100,     Community College of Rhode Island 1 Hilton Street, +1 401 455-6000,     Rhode Island College 600 Mount Pleasant Avenue, +1 401 456-8000,     Brown University 71 George Street, +1 401 863-1000,     Johnson Wales University 8 Abbot Park Place, +1 401 598-1000,     Roger Williams University Metro Campus 150 Washington Street, +1 401 276-4800,</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">63300</field>
		<field name="title">New York City</field>
		<field name="main">learn</field>
		<field name="name">learn</field>
		<field name="content">Unsurprisingly, New York City, the largest city in the United States, is home to many colleges and universities. Among these universities,  Columbia University  and  New York University  are undoubtedly the most prestigious (but also the most expensive). See the individual district articles for a complete listing of universities in New York City.</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">63301</field>
		<field name="title">Clermont County</field>
		<field name="main">learn</field>
		<field name="name">UC Clermont College</field>
		<field name="phone">+1-513 -732-5200</field>
		<field name="address">4200 Clermont College Drive, Batavia</field>
		<field name="url">http://www.clc.uc.edu/</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">63302</field>
		<field name="title">Terre Haute</field>
		<field name="main">learn</field>
		<field name="name">learn</field>
		<field name="content">Unlike other cities its size, Terre Haute boasts five institutes of higher education:   Indiana State University. 200 N 7th St.   . Founded in 1865, Indiana State University is a public university with around 10,000 students.  Rose-Hulman Institute of Technology. 5500 Wabash Ave.   . Founded in 1874, Rose-Hulman Institute of Technology is a private college with about 2,000 students. U.S. News World Report consistently ranks it the 1 undergraduate engineering institution in the United States.  Saint Mary-of-the-Woods College. Saint Mary-of-the-Woods, IN.   . Saint Mary-of-the-Woods College is a liberal arts college for women. Founded in 1840 by Indianas first Catholic saint (Saint Mother Theordore Guerin, who is entombed on the campus), it is the nations oldest Catholic college for women.  Ivy Tech Community College of Indiana.  Harrison College.</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">63303</field>
		<field name="title">Eugene</field>
		<field name="main">learn</field>
		<field name="name">learn</field>
		<field name="content">University of Oregon,    Lane Community College,    Eugene Glass School,    Lost Valley Educational Center,    Wellsprings Friends School At Center for Appropriate Transport learn about sustainable transport, cargo bikes, frame building, and bicycle repair.    Northwest Christian University</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">63304</field>
		<field name="title">Charlotte</field>
		<field name="main">learn</field>
		<field name="name">learn</field>
		<field name="content">University of North Carolina at Charlotte  UNC Charlotte is a public research university that is home to over 25,000 graduate and undergraduate students. It is the fourth largest university in North Carolina.    Johnson C. Smith University  - A historically African-American university located just outside Uptown. The centerpiece of the historic Biddleville community, J.C. Smiths campus is a picturesque gateway to the north/west side of the city.    Queens University of Charlotte  Queens University of Charlotte is a private, coed, masters level university with 2,600 graduate and undergraduate students. It is affiliated with Presbyterian USA.    Central Piedmont Community College  - CPCC has been a part of the Charlotte landscape for almost 50 years. It has six campuses located throughout Mecklenburg County and serves more than 70,000 students a year.</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">63305</field>
		<field name="title">Clarksburg (West Virginia)</field>
		<field name="main">learn</field>
		<field name="name">learn</field>
		<field name="content">The Clarksburg Convention Visitors Bureau is located at 208 Court Street  the Harrison County Courthouse on Main Street, 304-622-2157.  TOLL FREE 877-622-2157. Visit them on-line at http://www.cityofclarksburgwv.com, click on Visitors Bureau.   The local newspaper is the Clarksburg Exponent Telegram, 304-626-1400 or 800-982-6034, http://www.cpubco.com/ . Now one morning edition.</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">63306</field>
		<field name="title">Lansing (Michigan)</field>
		<field name="main">learn</field>
		<field name="name">learn</field>
		<field name="content">Michigan State University: Michigan State University (MSU) is a member of the Big Ten athletic conference, and is among the largest universities in the United States, with over 45,000 students. MSU is known for its academics and athletics. US News World Report ranks MSU as a Tier 1 university. MSU is home to 3 medical schools, 1 law school, and the National Superconducting Cyclotron Laboratory (NSCL). The NSCL is the largest nuclear science facility on a university campus, and the nuclear physics graduate program is ranked 2nd to MIT. The campus park, the largest single university campus in the United States, is noted for its collegiate Gothic architecture and campus gardens. MSU is located in East Lansing.  The Thomas M. Cooley Law School located in downtown Lansing is among the nations largest law schools.  The MSU College of Law is located on the Michigan State University campus.  Lansing Community College, with an enrollment of over 20,000 students, is located in downtown Lansing.  Great Lakes Christian College is located in Delta Township, west of Lansing.  Davenport University, Central Michigan University, and Western Michigan University have satellite campuses in and around Lansing.</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">63307</field>
		<field name="title">Somerville</field>
		<field name="main">learn</field>
		<field name="name">learn</field>
		<field name="content">Tufts University is a major American research university. The main campus is located next to the Powderhouse Square area, and includes the undergraduates and most graduate schools, including the Fletcher School of International Diplomacy. The Medical school and several other health sciences graduate programs and laboratories are located in downtown Boston next to Chinatown, while the Veterinary school is halfway across the state in Grafton, Mass.</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">63308</field>
		<field name="title">Kansas City</field>
		<field name="main">learn</field>
		<field name="name">Nelson-Atkins Museum of Art</field>
		<field name="price">Free</field>
		<field name="address">4525 Oak St</field>
		<field name="hours">W 10AM-4PM, Th-F 10AM-9PM, Sa 10AM-5PM, Su noon-5PM</field>
		<field name="url">http://www.nelson-atkins.org/</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">63309</field>
		<field name="title">Miami</field>
		<field name="main">learn</field>
		<field name="name">St. Thomas University</field>
		<field name="content">(, – This private university, affiliated with the Roman Catholic Church, has an enrollment of over 2,600 men and women. Business/management, education and communication majors are popular here.</field>
		<field name="phone">+1 305 628-6546</field>
		<field name="fax">+1 305 628-6591</field>
		<field name="address">16400 32nd Ave</field>
		<field name="email">signup@stu.edu</field>
		<field name="url">http://www.stu.edu</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">63310</field>
		<field name="title">Sacramento</field>
		<field name="main">learn</field>
		<field name="name">learn</field>
		<field name="content">California State University, Sacramento (CSUS),   . This is a major four-year public university in the Sacramento area with 28,000 students.   University of California, Davis (UCD),    The nearest Univeristy of California campus to Sacramento. It is located 16 miles (23 kilometres) west from Sacramento with a satellite campus (UC Davis Extension)in midtown Sacramento.     Los Rios Community College District  is the regions major two-year public college system enrolling 73,000 students with four campuses in the surrounding area. Its campuses include  Sacramento City College ,  American River College ,  Cosumnes River College , and  Folsom Lake College  along with five satellite centers.    Drexel Univerisity  is a private graduate university with its campus in downtown Sacramento.</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">63311</field>
		<field name="title">Garland (Texas)</field>
		<field name="main">learn</field>
		<field name="name">learn</field>
		<field name="content">Stop by Audubon Park on a Saturday afternoon to learn how to sew, make chainmail, or fight with foam-padded swords with the warriors of  Amtgard .</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">63312</field>
		<field name="title">Davenport</field>
		<field name="main">learn</field>
		<field name="name">learn</field>
		<field name="content">Main Library    Davenport Public Library   Davenport has had a library in one version or another since 1839.  The citys public library opened in 1904 with the assistance of Andrew Carnegie.  The present main library downtown was designed by noted architect  Edward Durell Stone. :   :    :   Kaplan University   Founded as the American Institute of Commerce in 1937, the Davenport campus became part of the Kaplan community in the early 2000s.  Palmer College of Chiropractic   Founded in 1897 by Daniel David Palmer and is considered "The Fountainhead," as it was the first school of chiropractic in the world.  St. Ambrose University   Founded by the first Catholic Bishop of Davenport in 1881 it remains an institution of the Catholic Church. It confers bachelors, masters and doctoral degrees in a variety of disciplines.  It has a respected business school.  Scott Community College   A two-year school it is part of the Eastern Iowa Community College District headquartered in Davenport.</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">63313</field>
		<field name="title">Long Beach</field>
		<field name="main">learn</field>
		<field name="name">learn</field>
		<field name="content">Long Beach is home to two major learning facilities, a California State University campus and a Community Junior College.  California State University Long Beach (CSULB) aka The Beach -    1250 Bellflower Boulevard, +1 562 985-4111.  CSULB offer a wide range of Bachelor degrees, as well as Masters degrees in Anthropology, Fine Arts, Business, and Science.  One of the specialities of the campus is International Business.  Long Beach City College (LBCC) -    , +1 562 938-4111. LBCC is a two-year transfer or AA-degree school, including a highly regarded nursing program. The school has two campuses, one focusing on traditional education, the other on vocational training.  LBCC Liberal Arts Campus - 4901 E. Carson Street  LBCC Pacific Coast Campus - 1305 East Pacific Coast Highway Long Beach Museum of Art Healing Children through Creativity: Child Art Therapy Workshop, October 27 and 28, 2008,    2300 E. Ocean Blvd. Long Beach, CA 90803. An introduction to the basic principles and practice of art therapy with children suffering from emotional, behavioral, medical and developmental challenges.</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">63314</field>
		<field name="title">West Windsor</field>
		<field name="main">learn</field>
		<field name="name">learn</field>
		<field name="content">Mercer County Community College, West Windsor  Princeton University, Princeton  Rider University Lawrence Township  The College of New Jersey (TCNJ), Trenton/Ewing Township  Thomas Edison State College, Trenton</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">63315</field>
		<field name="title">Rock Island</field>
		<field name="main">learn</field>
		<field name="name">learn</field>
		<field name="content">Main Library    Rock Island Public Library   The Rock Island Public Library traces its beginnings to 1872, making it the oldest public library in Illinois.  : Main Library: 401-19th St., +1 309 732-7323 : 30/31 Branch: 3059 30th St., +1 309 732-7369 : Southwest Branch: 9010 Ridgewood Rd., +1 309 732-7338   Augustana College   A private liberal arts college affiliated with the Evangelical Lutheran Church in America.</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">63316</field>
		<field name="title">Alamogordo</field>
		<field name="main">learn</field>
		<field name="name">learn</field>
		<field name="content">New Mexico School for the Blind and Visually Impaired - 1900 White Sands Blvd., +1 800 437-3505,   .  Started in 1903 to provide training and support for blind children to so they can lead independent and productive lives.  New Mexico residents are not charged tuition to attend the school and it supports students from birth through 21 years old.  New Mexico State University-Alamogordo Branch - Branch of NMSU in Alamogordo.</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">63317</field>
		<field name="title">Columbus</field>
		<field name="main">learn</field>
		<field name="name">learn</field>
		<field name="content">The Ohio State University    is a large college, bordered on the south by West 9th Avenue, on the north by Lane Avenue, and on the east by North High Street. The university owns most of the property within these bounds, up to Olentangy River Road on the west, and some properties west of Olentangy River Road. Columbus College of Art and Design    is an art school headquartered at 60 Cleveland Avenue in downtown. Columbus State Community College    is a community college located at 550 East Spring Street in downtown.</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">63318</field>
		<field name="title">Detroit</field>
		<field name="main">learn</field>
		<field name="name">learn</field>
		<field name="content">Located in Ann Arbor, about 45 miles west of Detroit, the University of Michigan ranks as one of Americas best. Alumni include President Gerald Ford and Google co-founder Larry Page. Others include Wayne State University (alumni include legendary White House Correspondent Helen Thomas and comedian/actress Lily Tomlin), University of Detroit-Mercy, Lawrence Technological University, Oakland University, Oakland Community College which is one of the largest Community Colleges in Michigan, Eastern Michigan University, Marygrove College, and College for Creative Studies.   The Detroit area has many civic and professional organizations. The headquarters for the Society for Automotive Engineers (SAE), Automotive, is in Troy, MI, the Society of Manufacturing Engineers in Dearborn, MI and the Center for Automotive Research (CAR) is headquartered in Ann Arbor, MI. Others include the Detroit Economic Club, the Detroit Athletic Club, the Greening of Detroit to promote urban forestry (tree planting), the Detroit Riverfront Conservancy, Detroit Renaissance, and Detroit Economic Growth Association (DEGA), and more.   The International Academy, an all International Baccalaureate school (a public, tuition-free consortium high school operated by Bloomfield Hills Schools which consistently ranks among the top 10 public high schools in the nation by Newsweek magazine), Cranbrook Schools (an exclusive private boarding school and academy), the Eton Academy, and Henry Ford Academy are some of outstanding secondary schools that are located in the area.</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">63319</field>
		<field name="title">Dayton</field>
		<field name="main">learn</field>
		<field name="name">Southwestern College - Dayton</field>
		<field name="content">Southwestern College is a computer health care training college.</field>
		<field name="phone">+1 937 224-0061</field>
		<field name="address">111 W First St</field>
		<field name="url">http://www.swcollege.net/</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">63320</field>
		<field name="title">Council Bluffs</field>
		<field name="main">learn</field>
		<field name="name">Iowa Western Community College</field>
		<field name="phone">+1 712 325-3200</field>
		<field name="address">2700 College Rd</field>
		<field name="tollfree">+1 800 432-5852</field>
		<field name="url">http://www.iwcc.edu/</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">63321</field>
		<field name="title">Sutton (West Virginia)</field>
		<field name="main">learn</field>
		<field name="name">learn</field>
		<field name="content">The local newspapers are   Braxton Citizens News, 304-765-5193,   .  Braxton Democrat Central, 304-765-5555, Serving Braxton County, West Virginia since 1883.</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">63322</field>
		<field name="title">Phoenix</field>
		<field name="main">learn</field>
		<field name="name">Thunderbird School of Global Management</field>
		<field name="content">World famous for being the first and oldest graduate school specializing in international management and global business.  Ranked 1 in the world in its field.</field>
		<field name="url">http://www.thunderbird.edu</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">63323</field>
		<field name="title">Birmingham (Alabama)</field>
		<field name="main">learn</field>
		<field name="name">learn</field>
		<field name="content">The University of Alabama at Birmingham (UAB)  Birmingham-Southern College  Samford University  Miles College</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">63324</field>
		<field name="title">Dayton</field>
		<field name="main">learn</field>
		<field name="name">ITT Technical Institute - Dayton</field>
		<field name="phone">+1 937 454-2267</field>
		<field name="address">3325 Stop Eight Rd</field>
		<field name="url">http://www.itt-tech.edu/</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">63325</field>
		<field name="title">Maryville (Tennessee)</field>
		<field name="main">learn</field>
		<field name="name">learn</field>
		<field name="content">Historic Districts  Maryville College  Sam Houston Schoolhouse  Blount County Public Library</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">63326</field>
		<field name="title">Dayton</field>
		<field name="main">learn</field>
		<field name="name">Air Force Institute of Technology</field>
		<field name="content">Located on Wright-Pattseron Air Force Base, this is the Air Forces main technical school for graduate degrees, offering both Masters and Ph.D. courses in fields ranging from Logistics and Program Management to Aeronautical Engineering and Physics.</field>
		<field name="address">2950 Hobson Way</field>
		<field name="url">http://www.afit.edu</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">63327</field>
		<field name="title">Galveston</field>
		<field name="main">learn</field>
		<field name="name">learn</field>
		<field name="content">The University of Texas Medical Branch is the islands major university.  There is a significant "college town" feel to the section of the Strand nearest the university. It provides mostly postgraduate medical education.  Texas AM University at Galveston, located on Pelican Island, is a branch campus of Texas AM University. Its main fields of study include Marine Sciences, Marine Engineering, and Maritime Transportation. It is home to the Texas Maritime Academy.</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">63328</field>
		<field name="title">Cincinnati</field>
		<field name="main">learn</field>
		<field name="name">Cincinnati State Technical and Community College</field>
		<field name="content">Cincinnati State is the technical and community college of choice in the region and nationally recognized for academic excellence and workforce development.</field>
		<field name="directions">located at the confluence of I-75 and I-74, at the intersection of Central Parkway and Ludlow Avenue, technically in the neighborhood of Clifton</field>
		<field name="phone">+1-513 -861-7700</field>
		<field name="address">3520 Central Parkway</field>
		<field name="url">http://www.cincinnatistate.edu/</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">63329</field>
		<field name="title">Smithfield (Rhode Island)</field>
		<field name="main">learn</field>
		<field name="name">learn</field>
		<field name="content">Greenville Public Library- 573 Putnam Pike, Greenville RI 02828. +1 (401) 949-3630. This library consists of a children’s area, a senior citizens area, an adult section, and teen zone. The library has all major reference books and has a computer lab. There are also a variety of programs offered to children and adults including multicultural classes, art classes, and library use classes. East Smithfield Public Library- 50 Esmond Street, Smithfield, RI 02917. +1 (401) 231-5150. This library is in the small village of Esmond offering a good selection of books and quiet place to read.</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">63330</field>
		<field name="title">Orem</field>
		<field name="main">learn</field>
		<field name="name">learn</field>
		<field name="content">Orem is home to Utah Valley University (formerly Utah Valley State College)   . In addition, a number of Orems residents attend Brigham Young University    in neighboring  Provo .</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">63331</field>
		<field name="title">Cleveland</field>
		<field name="main">learn</field>
		<field name="name">Case Western Reserve University</field>
		<field name="content">Tucked inside the University Circle cultural mecca, Case houses Clevelands premier research institutes.</field>
		<field name="phone">+1 216 368-2000</field>
		<field name="url">http://www.cwru.edu/</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">63332</field>
		<field name="title">Columbia (South Carolina)</field>
		<field name="main">learn</field>
		<field name="name">University of South Carolina</field>
		<field name="content">The campus is just south of the Statehouse. The oldest part of campus, known as "The Horseshoe", survived the burning of Columbia and has lovely buildings dating from 1805.</field>
		<field name="email">info@sc.edu</field>
		<field name="alt">USC</field>
		<field name="url">http://www.sc.edu/</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">63333</field>
		<field name="title">Erie County (Ohio)</field>
		<field name="main">learn</field>
		<field name="name">learn</field>
		<field name="content">Bowling Green State University Firelands One University Dr. Huron. +1 419 433-5560</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">63334</field>
		<field name="title">Berkeley (California)</field>
		<field name="main">learn</field>
		<field name="name">University of California, Berkeley</field>
		<field name="content">A world-class university consistently ranked as the number-one public university in the United States. Study abroad programs are available, and international students are housed in the fittingly-named International House at Piedmont Ave. and Bancroft Way. The University also offers summer courses and extension classes available to the general public.</field>
		<field name="url">http://www.berkeley.edu</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">63335</field>
		<field name="title">Fresno</field>
		<field name="main">learn</field>
		<field name="name">learn</field>
		<field name="content">Fresno State University is noted for its agricultural programs, and many Fresno State students and faculty travel to developing nations on agricultural assistance programs.  Fresno also has three school districts: Fresno Unified, Clovis Unified, and Central Unified.</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">63336</field>
		<field name="title">Evansville</field>
		<field name="main">learn</field>
		<field name="name">learn</field>
		<field name="content">Angel Mounds State Historic Site - The visitors Center gives a glimpse of understanding of what life was like from 1100 to 1450, when Angel Mounds was the largest Indian community in what would become the state of Indiana. Walking through the sites 100 acres, visitors view the remains of several Indian mounds and a reconstructed stockade which surrounded the city.   Koch Family Childrens Museum of Evansville cMoe reopened in Fall 2006 in the renovated former Downtown Central Library building with 18,000 square feet of exhibits. It hosts four main galleries, plus a multimedia theater entitled the ’Freedom Gallery.‘ ’Work Smart‘ focuses on engineering skill development and the freedom to build and create. ’Live Big‘ provides inquiry into our bodies and promotes the freedom to make choices. ’Speak Loud‘ is the arts area, encouraging the freedom of self-expression. ’Quack Factory‘ contains serious water play and large-muscle activities as it promotes the freedom to explore. Open Wednesday through Saturday, 9 a.m. to 4 p.m and Sunday, Noon to 4 pm.   Evansville Museum of Arts, History, and Science  The Evansville Museum’s permanent art collection of American and European painting, graphic works, and sculpture dating from the 16th through the 20th centuries is exhibited in thematic galleries highlighting landscape, still life, genre works, and portraiture. Additionally, the museum features permanent and changing history exhibitions at the Museum provide a diverse educational opportunity for visitors of all ages. Such as Rivertown U. S. A. in which a sense of life in the Midwest is explored in the ten detailed shops such as the Doctor’s Office of William M. Elliott--a graduate of Evansville Medical College. Lastly the museum includes the historic Koch Planetarium. Closed on Mondays and Tuesdays. $4 suggested donation. Evansville Museum Transportation Center - The exhibitions of EMTRAC interpret transportation in Southern Indiana from the latter part of the Nineteenth Century through the mid-Twentieth Century. Divided into four areas, visitors first enter River/Rail/Aviation Hall.  Highlights of this exhibit include an interactive riverboat pilothouse, an exhibition recalling Evansville’s first contact with aviation, and a turn-of-the-century waiting room that overlooks the Museum’s historic railroad. Closed Mondays and Tuesdays. $2 admission fee.  LST 325 - Authentic WWII warship open for tours Tuesdays-Sundays. Docked on the Evansville riverfront, it is the last navigable ship of its kind in operation today. Call for hours and special group rates.  Mesker Park Zoo - Located on over 50 acres, Mesker Park Zoo has over 600 animals including the oldest living hippopotamus in captivity in the United States. It also has giraffes, lions, zebras, a jaguar, and river otters.  Mesker Park  University of Southern Indiana - This publicly funded institution has been among the fastest growing comprehensive state universities in the Midwestern United States.Record fall enrollment in 2010 reached 10,702. The University has a modern 300-acre suburban campus situated within wooded rolling hills. In October, 2006, the University completed a master plan that provides the framework to double the size of the school and support a campus of over 20,000 students. University of Evansville - A small, private university with approximately 3,050 students. Founded in 1854 as Moores Hill College, it is located near the interchange of the Lloyd Expressway and U.S. Route 41. It is affiliated with the United Methodist Church. The University features liberal arts and sciences degrees, most with strong cooperative learning opportunities both on and off campus.</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">63337</field>
		<field name="title">Oakland</field>
		<field name="main">learn</field>
		<field name="name">Mills College</field>
		<field name="content">An all-womens liberal arts college.</field>
		<field name="directions">Near Pierson St.</field>
		<field name="phone">+1 510 430-2255</field>
		<field name="address">5000 MacArthur Blvd.</field>
		<field name="url">http://www.mills.edu</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">63338</field>
		<field name="title">Cleveland</field>
		<field name="main">learn</field>
		<field name="name">learn</field>
		<field name="content">Cleveland Institute of Art,   . Visit its galleries and catch an art film at the Cinematheque.  Cleveland Institute of Music,   . A leading international conservatory for classical music.</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">63339</field>
		<field name="title">Cincinnati</field>
		<field name="main">learn</field>
		<field name="name">learn</field>
		<field name="content">University of Cincinnatis campus</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">63340</field>
		<field name="title">Nashville</field>
		<field name="main">learn</field>
		<field name="name">learn</field>
		<field name="content">Kirkland Hall, Vanderbilt University   Vanderbilt University,   . One of Americas top 20 universities, Vanderbilt is home to just over 11,000 undergraduate and professional students. Vanderbilt offers 66 major fields of study in the arts and sciences, engineering, music, education, and human development, as well as a full range of graduate and professional degrees.  Middle Tennessee State University (MTSU), 1301 E Main St, Murfreesboro, +1 615 898-2300,   .  Austin Peay State University, 601 College St, Clarksville, +1 931 221-7011 or +1 877 861-APSU (861-2778),   .  Belmont University, 1900 Belmont Blvd, +1 615 460-6000,   .  A private university offering undergraduate and graduate degree programs in over 65 different studies.  Belmont University hosted the United States Presidential Townhall debate on October 7th, 2008   .  Fisk University, 1000 17th Ave N, +1 615 329-8500,   .  Fisk University has a long history.  It is a liberal arts college that was founded in 1866 to educate freed slaves and has since then seen many distinguished graduates.  Lipscomb University, Physical Address: 3901 Granny White Pike. Mailing Address: One University Park Drive, +1 615 966-1000,   . Lipscomb University is a private coeducational institution whose principal focus is undergraduate education in the liberal arts and sciences, combined with a number of pre-professional fields and master’s degree programs. Its primary mission is to integrate Christian faith and practice with academic excellence.  Tennessee State University, 3500 John A Merritt Blvd, +1 615 963-5000,   .  Trevecca Nazarene University,   .  Aquinas College, 4210 Harding Rd, +1 615 297-7545,   .  A private Catholic school with liberal arts and science curriculum.  Free Will Baptist Bible College, 3606 West End Ave, +1 615 844-5000,   . Founded in 1942, FWBBC now enrolls around 350 students per year and offers them a number of degree programs.   Nashville State Community College,   .  Strayer University,   .  Tennessee Foreign Language Institute, 227 French Landing Dr, Ste 100. +1 615 741-7579,   . One of a kind state-supported language institute offering classes on site and in the workplace in up to 141 languages, including ESL, and interpretation and translation services to government, business and the community at large.  Nossi College of Art,   .  OMore College of Design, Franklin,   .  The Art Institute of Tennessee- Nashville,   .  Meharry Medical College,   .  Volunteer State Community College,   .  Watkins College of Art and Design,   .  Nashville Auto Diesel College.</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">63341</field>
		<field name="title">Newark (New Jersey)</field>
		<field name="main">learn</field>
		<field name="name">Essex County College</field>
		<field name="address">303 University Ave</field>
		<field name="url">http://www.essex.edu/</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">63342</field>
		<field name="title">Cincinnati</field>
		<field name="main">learn</field>
		<field name="name">College of Mt. St. Joseph on the Ohio</field>
		<field name="content">Private Catholic college located in Cincinnatis western suburb of Delhi.  Known for its Education majors.</field>
		<field name="phone">+1-513 -244-4200</field>
		<field name="address">5701 Delhi Road</field>
		<field name="url">http://www.msj.edu/</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">63343</field>
		<field name="title">Momence</field>
		<field name="main">learn</field>
		<field name="name">learn</field>
		<field name="content">Olivet Nazarene University  is located in nearby  Bourbonnais .     Kankakee Community College  is located in nearby  Kankakee .</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">63344</field>
		<field name="title">Skaneateles</field>
		<field name="main">learn</field>
		<field name="name">Gazella Performance Wellness Studio</field>
		<field name="content">Gazella offers group exercise classes (including bootcamp, body fusion, cardio kickboxing and Zumba), yoga, pilates, TRX suspension training, personal and small group training, cycling and triathlon coaching, and nutrition and wellness counseling.  One day drop-ins and weekly passes are available.</field>
		<field name="directions">From the village, north on Jordan.  Gazella is on the right just past the first stop sign.</field>
		<field name="phone">+1 315  729-8645</field>
		<field name="address">3986 Jordan Road</field>
		<field name="url">http://www.gazella-studio.com</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">63345</field>
		<field name="title">Phoenix</field>
		<field name="main">learn</field>
		<field name="name">Arizona State University</field>
		<field name="content">Located in the eastern suburb of  Tempe , with three branch campuses around the Phoenix metro area, ASU is one of the largest public universities in the U.S. and is noted for its engineering, business, music, and creative writing programs.</field>
		<field name="url">http://www.asu.edu</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">63346</field>
		<field name="title">New London (Connecticut)</field>
		<field name="main">learn</field>
		<field name="name">learn</field>
		<field name="content">Connecticut College, Private liberal arts college located on the Thames River.  Mitchell College, A liberal arts college that sits on the Thames River.  United States Coast Guard Academy, The military academy for the U.S. Coast Guard.</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">63347</field>
		<field name="title">Fredericksburg (Texas)</field>
		<field name="main">learn</field>
		<field name="name">Fredericksburg Culinary Arts</field>
		<field name="directions">At Fischer Wiesers Das Peach Haus</field>
		<field name="phone">+1 830-997-8396</field>
		<field name="address">S. Washington St</field>
		<field name="email">learn2cook@fbgculinaryarts.com</field>
		<field name="hours">Sat 3-5PM</field>
		<field name="url">http://www.fbgculinaryarts.com</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">63348</field>
		<field name="title">Louisville</field>
		<field name="main">learn</field>
		<field name="name">learn</field>
		<field name="content">University of Louisville,    Indiana University Southeast,     Bellarmine University,    Spalding University,    Sullivan University,    Jefferson Community College,    McKendree College,    Southern Baptist Theological Seminary,</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">63349</field>
		<field name="title">Minneapolis</field>
		<field name="main">learn</field>
		<field name="name">learn</field>
		<field name="content">University of Minnesota .   Augsburg College .   Minneapolis College of Art and Design .   Minneapolis Community and Technical College .</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">63350</field>
		<field name="title">Pocatello</field>
		<field name="main">learn</field>
		<field name="name">learn</field>
		<field name="content">Idaho State University is an important part of Pocatello.</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">63351</field>
		<field name="title">Norman (Oklahoma)</field>
		<field name="main">learn</field>
		<field name="name">learn</field>
		<field name="content">The Firehouse Art Center , 444 S. Flood Ave., offers classes in a variety of artistic forms.</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">63352</field>
		<field name="title">Wilmington (Ohio)</field>
		<field name="main">learn</field>
		<field name="name">Wilmington College</field>
		<field name="phone">+1-937 -382-6661</field>
		<field name="address">251 Ludovic Street</field>
		<field name="url">http://www.wilmington.edu</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">63353</field>
		<field name="title">Valdosta</field>
		<field name="main">learn</field>
		<field name="name">learn</field>
		<field name="content">Valdosta State University   Valdosta State University, 1500 N Patterson St, +1 229 333-5800, 1-800-618-1878,   .  Over 10,000 students enrolled undergraduate and graduate programs.</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">63354</field>
		<field name="title">Stamford (Connecticut)</field>
		<field name="main">learn</field>
		<field name="name">Stamford Public Library Main Branch</field>
		<field name="content">Located in a three story historic building in downtown Stamford. Books, music, and videos can be borrowed with a library card or read and viewed in the library. Also free computers with Internet access and a large kids section downstairs. Starbucks connected to the library with large glass windows that view the pedestrian traffic in Stamford and the front steps of the library where people usually congregate.</field>
		<field name="directions">Corner of Broad Bedford Streets</field>
		<field name="phone">+1 203  964-1000</field>
		<field name="address">One Public Library Plaza Stamford, CT 06904</field>
		<field name="url">http://www.fergusonlibrary.org/main</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">63355</field>
		<field name="title">Bluefield (West Virginia)</field>
		<field name="main">learn</field>
		<field name="name">learn</field>
		<field name="content">The city newspaper is the  Bluefield Daily Telegraph .   Bluefield High School, 535 W Cumberland Road, 304-325-9116,   . Home of the Bluefield Beavers.   Bluefield State College, 219 Rock Street, 304-327-4000 or 800-344-8892 or 800-654-7798,   . A four-year historically black college located on the north side of town, first established as a teachers college in 1895 and integrated in 1954. Bluefield State specializes in career and technical two- and four-year programs, enhanced by a selection of liberal arts courses.</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">63356</field>
		<field name="title">Long Island</field>
		<field name="main">learn</field>
		<field name="name">learn</field>
		<field name="content">Long Island is also the home to Stony Brook University (with campuses in Stony Brook and Southampton), one of the top-100 Universities (U.S. News World Report), which is part of the State University of New York (SUNY) system, providing a very academic and international community within central Long Island. Brookhaven National Laboratory, affiliated with the U.S. Department of Energy, and Cold Spring Harbor Laboratory is also located on Long Island. Both labs are affiliated with Stony Brook University.  Other notable institutions of higher learning on Long Island include:  Hofstra University (Hempstead), Adelphi University (Garden City), Long Island University (Brookville, Brentwood, Riverhead), New York Institute of Technology (Old Westbury), Central Islip), SUNY College at Old Westbury (Old Westbury), Farmingdale State College (East Farmingdale), Polytechnic Institute of New York University (Melville), Five Towns College (Dix Hills), Nassau Community College (East Garden City), Suffolk County Community College (Selden, Brentwood, Riverhead, Sayville), Briarcliffe College (Bethpage, Patchogue), Dowling College (Oakdale, Shirley, Melville), Molloy College (Rockville Centre), Saint Johns University (Oakdale), Saint Josephs College (Patchogue).</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">63357</field>
		<field name="title">Springfield (Illinois)</field>
		<field name="main">learn</field>
		<field name="name">learn</field>
		<field name="content">The University of Illinois Springfield (UIS)    is the newest of the University of Illinoiss three campuses. Founded in 1970 as Sangamon State University, the University of Illinois Springfield claims a student body of 5,000 and a vibrant, modern prairie-style campus.</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">63358</field>
		<field name="title">Milwaukee</field>
		<field name="main">learn</field>
		<field name="name">learn</field>
		<field name="content">A January 2000 study from McGill University in Montreal ranked Milwaukee 6th in a list of U.S. and Canadian cities with the highest number of college students per 100 residents.  The largest university is the University of Wisconsin–Milwaukee with around 30,000 students. Other schools include Marquette University, Alverno College, Cardinal Stritch University, Medical College of Wisconsin, Milwaukee Area Technical College, Milwaukee Institute of Art and Design, Milwaukee School of Engineering, Mount Mary College, Wisconsin Lutheran College, Concordia University Wisconsin, Lakeland College, and Wisconsin School of Professional Psychology.</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">63359</field>
		<field name="title">Buffalo</field>
		<field name="main">learn</field>
		<field name="name">learn</field>
		<field name="content">Buffalo is home to a large number of private and public colleges and universities. The largest school in the area is the  University at Buffalo  (UB). One of the four "university centers" of the State University of New York (SUNY) system, UB is renowned as a large public research university. For this reason, it is one of 62 elected members of the prestigious Association of American Universities. UB has two campuses: the smaller South Campus is located in the University Heights neighborhood at the citys northeast corner, and the larger North Campus is located in the suburb of Amherst, about four miles (6km) northeast of the South Campus.    Buffalo State College , also part of the SUNY system, is located across from the Albright-Knox Art Gallery, at the north end of the Elmwood Village.  Canisius College  is Buffalos largest private college, located near the intersection of Humboldt Parkway and Main Street. Other colleges and universities in the city and its surrounding area include Trocaire College, Medaille College, Villa Maria College, DYouville College, Daemen College, and the three campuses of Erie Community College.  The University at Buffalo has an annual  Distinguished Speakers Series , which has played host to Bill Clinton, Al Gore, Michael Moore, the Dalai Lama, Stephen Colbert, and Dr. Sanjay Gupta in recent years. These events take place on the North Campus and are open to the public; tickets are available from the Universitys box office. UB has a  free series of summer lectures  available to the public, and Buffalo State regularly has  events  open to visitors.</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">63360</field>
		<field name="title">Baltimore</field>
		<field name="main">learn</field>
		<field name="name">learn</field>
		<field name="content">American Career Institute,   . A career training school located in Baltimore.  Baltimore Career Training,   . A career training school located in Baltimore.   Coppin State University,   . A historically black college that is part of the University of Maryland System.  Johns Hopkins University,   . A school most notably known for its medical program.   Loyola University, Maryland,   . A Roman Catholic, Jesuit private university.  Maryland Bartending Academy,   . 2-week bartending program in Baltimore.  Maryland Institute College of Art,   . MICA is an art and design college, and one of the first and oldest art colleges in the United States.  North American School of Trades,   . Maryland job training career training in Baltimore.  Notre Dame of Maryland University,   . An independent, Catholic-affiliated, liberal arts college that primarily serves female students.  University of Baltimore,   . A public university that is part of the University System of Maryland. UB serves both undergraduates and postgraduates.  University of Maryland, The Founding Campus,   . Also known as University of Maryland, Baltimore, the school comprises some of the oldest professional schools in the nation and world. UMB is the original campus of the University System of Maryland.  Sojourner–Douglass College,   . A private institution of higher learning with an Afrocentric focus.</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">63361</field>
		<field name="title">Hickory</field>
		<field name="main">learn</field>
		<field name="name">learn</field>
		<field name="content">Patrick Beaver Memorial Library,   . Excellent library with comfy chairs and plenty of books and periodicals. Internet access available for a fee. Lenoir^Rhyne University,   . Four-year liberal arts institution with a variety of majors. Affiliated with the NC Synod of the ELCA   . Appalachian State University,   . Offers classes in Hickory as part of the Hickory Metro Higher Education Center. Catawba Valley Community College,   .</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">63362</field>
		<field name="title">Lincoln (Nebraska)</field>
		<field name="main">learn</field>
		<field name="name">learn</field>
		<field name="content">University of Nebraska at Lincoln Southeast Community College Nebraska Wesleyan University Union College Kaplan University College of Hair Design</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">63363</field>
		<field name="title">Taos</field>
		<field name="main">learn</field>
		<field name="name">learn</field>
		<field name="content">Ski lessons are available at Taos Ski Valley.  The  Taos School of Music  is a well-regarded summer program for the aspiring (age 18 and up) professional musician.  The focus is on chamber music, with a very favorable student/faculty ratio and performance opportunities.  A concert series involving significant chamber ensembles is part of the program.  Admission into the program is highly competitive.</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">63364</field>
		<field name="title">Utica</field>
		<field name="main">learn</field>
		<field name="name">learn</field>
		<field name="content">Utica Public Library  The Utica area is home to several colleges and universities, which host events regularly.     Utica College, 1600 Burrstone Road.  Spun-off from Syracuse University in 1946, Utica College (UC) offers bachelors degrees from Syracuse, as well as masters degrees in its own name, for a wide variety of academic programs within the fields of health sciences, social sciences, liberal arts, and business studies (to name a few).  It prides itself on a low faculty-to-student ratio and the individual attention possible in a small-college setting.    Mohawk Valley Community College, 1101 Sherman Drive.  MVCC is the oldest community college in New York State, dating from 1946.    Pratt at Munson Williams Proctor Arts Institute, 310 Genesee Street.  In addition to its Fine and Performing Arts programs (see Museums, above), Munson-Williams-Proctor Institute is also home to a well-regarded School of Art.     State University of New York (SUNY) Institute of Technology (in Marcy - just north of Utica).  Established in 1966, SUNYIT offers undergraduate and graduate degree programs in technology, professional studies, and selected liberal arts disciplines. SUNYIT has a large, grassy/wooded campus just north of Utica.</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">63365</field>
		<field name="title">Teaneck</field>
		<field name="main">learn</field>
		<field name="name">learn</field>
		<field name="content">Teaneck is home to the Metropolitan Campus of Farleigh Dickinson University, which is set on the border between Teaneck and the Hackensack River. The college has served over 4,000 undergraduates and over 2,300 graduate students as of the 2010-2011 school year.</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">63366</field>
		<field name="title">Cookeville</field>
		<field name="main">learn</field>
		<field name="name">learn</field>
		<field name="content">Tennessee Tech University,   .</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">63367</field>
		<field name="title">Fairmont (West Virginia)</field>
		<field name="main">learn</field>
		<field name="name">learn</field>
		<field name="content">The local newspaper is the Times West Virginian, 304-367-2500,   .   Fairmont State, 1201 Locust Avenue, 304-367-4892,   . Community and technical college founded in 1974, and state university founded in 1865, offering 90 baccalaureate and 50 associate degrees.</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">63368</field>
		<field name="title">Wilmington (North Carolina)</field>
		<field name="main">learn</field>
		<field name="name">learn</field>
		<field name="content">University of North Carolina Wilmington, 601 S. College Rd., +1 910 962-3000,    . Cape Fear Community College, 411 N. Front St., +1 910 362-7000,   . New Hanover County Public Library, 201 Chestnut St., +1 910 798-6301,   . New Hanover County Schools, 6410 Carolina Beach Rd., +1 910 763-5431,   .</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">63369</field>
		<field name="title">Omaha</field>
		<field name="main">learn</field>
		<field name="name">learn</field>
		<field name="content">Bellevue University,   .  Clarkson College,   .  College of St. Mary,   .  The only all womens Catholic college in the region.  Creative Center Art College,   . A small private graphic design and advertising trade school owned by Dotzler Creative Arts Design Firm.  Creighton University,   . Jesuit Catholic university.  Grace University,   .  ITT Technical Institute,   .  Metropolitan Community College,   . Multiple campuses throughout Omaha metro area.  Nebraska Christian College,   .  Nebraska Methodist College,   .  University of Nebraska - Omaha,   . The only public university located in Omaha.  University of Nebraska Medical Center,   .</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">63370</field>
		<field name="title">Bettendorf</field>
		<field name="main">learn</field>
		<field name="name">Bettendorf Public Library</field>
		<field name="phone">+1 563 344-4175</field>
		<field name="hoursextra">(Su closed Jun, Jul, Aug)</field>
		<field name="fax">+1 563 344-4185</field>
		<field name="address">2950 Learning Campus Dr.</field>
		<field name="hours">M-Th 9AM-9PM, F-Sa 9AM-5:30PM, Su 1PM-5PM</field>
		<field name="url">http://www.bettendorflibrary.com/</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">63371</field>
		<field name="title">Winston-Salem</field>
		<field name="main">learn</field>
		<field name="name">learn</field>
		<field name="content">Wake Forest University    Winston-Salem State University    Salem College    University of North Carolina School of the Arts</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">63372</field>
		<field name="title">Irvine</field>
		<field name="main">learn</field>
		<field name="name">learn</field>
		<field name="content">University of California, Irvine - The fourth largest campus of the University of California, UC Irvine (24,000 students), is located in the west part of the city.      Concordia University - A Christian university of roughly 1800 undergraduates.      Irvine Valley College - Part of the California Community College system enrolling about 16,000 students. Popularly referred to as "IVC".</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">63373</field>
		<field name="title">Brownsville (Texas)</field>
		<field name="main">learn</field>
		<field name="name">learn</field>
		<field name="content">University of Texas at Brownsville and Texas Southmost College UTB/TSC    South Texas Vocational Technical Institute</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">63374</field>
		<field name="title">Santa Clara (California)</field>
		<field name="main">learn</field>
		<field name="name">learn</field>
		<field name="content">Santa Clara University, http://www.scu.edu/, is a private, Jesuit university offering a variety of undergraduate and graduate curricula in the schools of Arts and Sciences, Education and Counseling Psychology, Business, Engineering, Theology, and Law. Summer school classes are open to visitors and students. Mission College, phone +1 408-988-2200, 3000 Mission College Boulevard Santa Clara, CA 95054, http://www.missioncollege.org/. This community college offers academic, vocational, and other classes, including associates degrees and certificates. UCSC offers accredited curricula and courses through their Silicon Valley Extension, with a Santa Clara location. http://www.ucsc-extension.edu/ Santa Clara Adult Education, http://www.scae.org/, a division of the Santa Clara Unified School District, offers selected technical, academic, and recreational classes. Students must be at least 18 years of age. The Santa Clara Parks and Recreation Department offers a variety of classes, largely recreational, listed in their Recreation Activities guide. Classes are open to non-residents, but city residents pay lower fees. http://santaclaraca.gov/index.aspx?page=233 The Santa Clara City Library, http://library.santaclaraca.gov/, offers numerous programs, lectures, presentations, and classes. Visit their program schedule on their website for current details.</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">63375</field>
		<field name="title">Canton (Ohio)</field>
		<field name="main">learn</field>
		<field name="name">learn</field>
		<field name="content">Kent State University, Stark Campus, 6000 Frank Avenue NW, North Canton, +1 330 244-3300,   . Kent Stark is one of Kent State Universitys regional campuses.  This public college is positioned on approximately 200 acres and has more than 10,000 students as of 2007.   Malone University, 2600 Cleveland Ave. NW, +1 330 471-8100,   .  Malone University is a private university that has an enrollment of 3,700 students as of 2007.  Stark State College of Technology, 6200 Frank Avenue NW, North Canton, +1 330 494-6170,   .  Stark State College is a technical college that offers more than 45 associate degrees in several fields.    Walsh University, 2020 East Maple Street NW, North Canton, +1 330 490-7090,   .  Walsh is a private university that has approximately 2,500 students as of 2007.</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">63376</field>
		<field name="title">United States of America</field>
		<field name="main">learn</field>
		<field name="name">learn</field>
		<field name="content">Short courses that do not count as credits towards the awarding of an academic degree may be undertaken on a tourist visa, or under the visa-waiver program. Any courses that contribute credits towards the awarding an academic degree will require you to obtain a student visa in advance regardless of how short your stay in the US may be. (This rule does not apply to citizens of  Palau ,  Marshall Islands  and the  Federated States of Micronesia .) In order to apply for a student visa, you will need to present an I-20 form from the college, pay a  SEVIS fee , and demonstrate evidence of sufficient funds to cover your tuition fees and living expenses for the duration of your course. You will also need to demonstrate your proficiency in English. Note that unless it is required as part of one of your course modules (for which you are required to apply for special permission in advance), international students are not allowed to work off campus in the United States.  Community colleges typically offer college-credit courses on an open-admissions basis; anyone with a high school degree or its equivalent and the required tuition payment can generally enroll. In large cities, open universities may offer short non-credit courses on all sorts of practical topics, from ballroom dance to buying real estate. They are a good place to learn a new skill and meet people.  Studying full-time in the United States is an excellent opportunity for young adults seeking an advanced education, a chance to see a foreign country, and a better understanding of the U.S. and its people. It can be done independently by applying directly to a college for admission, or through the "study abroad" or "foreign exchange" department of a college in your own country, usually for a single term or one year. (Either approach requires, at minimum, an F or J student visa.) The latter is usually easiest; the two institutions will handle much of the arrangements, and you dont have to make a commitment to four years living in a strange country. Be forewarned, however: many state universities and private colleges are located in small towns, hundreds of miles from any big urban centers. Dont expect to spend your weekends in  New York  if your college is in  North Dakota . The U.S. attracts the most international students in the world and a lot of cultural diversity can be seen throughout its universities.   Institutions range from some of the worlds most prestigious universities, to many lower-ranked institutions whose quality of education may be questionable. Unlike in many other countries, there is no centralized governmental body which regulates the academic standards for university education, meaning that universities are by and large free to decide their own admissions process, syllabi and academic standards. This means that the quality of education, study environment, and reputation varies widely from institution to institution. This also means that there is no centralized body which manages university applications, and you will need to apply directly to each institution you are interested in attending. However, practically all universities are accredited by non-governmental, regional academic standards bodies and many courses of study are accredited by similar bodies or by professional organizations (such as the Accreditation Board for Engineering and Technology for most engineering programs or the American Bar Association for legal studies). Even within the universities, lecturers are often given considerably more freedom to set their own syllabi and examinations than those in universities in many other countries, so two similar courses taught by different lecturers can also be drastically different in their focus and difficulty.  Most public universities are part of the state university systems, which are partially subsidized by state governments, and may have many campuses spread around the state, with hundreds of thousands of students. Private colleges are generally smaller (hundreds or a few thousand students), with a larger percentage of their students living on campus; some are affiliated with churches and may be more religious in character. Other kinds of colleges focus on teaching specific job skills, education for working adults, and providing inexpensive college-level education to local residents. Although nearly all colleges are open to students regardless of race, gender, religion, etc. many were originally established for a particular group (e.g. African-Americans, women, members of a particular religion) and may still attract primarily students from that group. Several private colleges remain female-only, there are a few male-only private colleges, and private religious colleges may expect students to practice the schools faith.  Colleges are partially funded by "tuition" charged to the student, which is often quite expensive, very commonly reaching into the tens of thousands of dollars per year. The most selective colleges (and hence, often the most desirable) run up to $40,000-50,000 per year, including both tuition and "room board" in that price. In general, private universities charge the same tuition fees for both U.S. and international students. Public universities generally offer subsidized tuition fees only to U.S. citizens or permanent residents who reside in their state, meaning that students from interstate are usually required to pay full tuition fees like international students. Most U.S. citizens and some permanent residents receive substantial financial assistance from the federal and state governments in the form of grants and low-interest loans, which are not available to non-citizens. Often financial aid for foreign students is provided by their home country. They may be eligible for privately-funded "scholarships" intended to provide educational opportunities for various kinds of students.  Some U.S. and major global banks offer loans to foreign students, which usually require a citizen to guarantee that theyll be repaid.  Contact the Financial Aid Office of any college you are interested in attending for more information about the sources of aid available.  Almost all U.S. colleges and universities operate web sites (in the .edu domain) with information for prospective students and other visitors. Information on touring a handful of them has been collected into  Touring prestigious and notable universities in the U.S.</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">63377</field>
		<field name="title">Newark (New Jersey)</field>
		<field name="main">learn</field>
		<field name="name">Seton Hall University School of Law</field>
		<field name="address">One Newark Center</field>
		<field name="url">http://law.shu.edu/</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">63378</field>
		<field name="title">Oxford (Mississippi)</field>
		<field name="main">learn</field>
		<field name="name">learn</field>
		<field name="content">The  University of Mississippi  is a comprehensive research university and is home to a chapter of the prestigous Phi Beta Kappa.  It also is listed in The Student Guide to Americas 100 Best College Buys and The Student Guide to Americas Best College Scholarships. UM also ranks 50th on Kiplingers Personal Finance magazines list of best college buys for in-state tuition and 46th for out-of-state tuition.  Also in town is a branch of  Northwest Mississippi Community College .  The local public school system is excellent and diverse.  The two local high schools are Oxford High School    and Lafayette High School   .</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">63379</field>
		<field name="title">Appleton</field>
		<field name="main">learn</field>
		<field name="name">learn</field>
		<field name="content">In general Appleton is well-respected for the quality of the education in its public schools, both at the primary and secondary levels.    Lawrence University  - a small, private liberal arts college.  Ranked 1 university in Wisconsin by Forbes  .   University of Wisconsin-Fox Valley - a two-year collegiate campus of the University of Wisconsin System.   Fox Valley Technical College - a technical (community) college of the Wisconsin Technical College System.</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">63380</field>
		<field name="title">Brookline</field>
		<field name="main">learn</field>
		<field name="name">learn</field>
		<field name="content">Brookline is home to some of the best public schools around.  Brookline High School has many famous alumni including Theo Epstein, the current General Manager of the Cubs; Michael Dukakis, former Massachusetts Governor and 1988 Democratic Presidential nominee; Robert Kraft, current Patriots and Revolution owner; Conan OBrien, TV host.</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">63381</field>
		<field name="title">Fallbrook</field>
		<field name="main">learn</field>
		<field name="name">Fallbrook School of the Arts</field>
		<field name="phone">+1 760 728-6383</field>
		<field name="address">310 E. Alvarado St.</field>
		<field name="email">brigitte@fallbrookschoolofthearts.org</field>
		<field name="url">http://fallbrookschoolofthearts.org</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">63382</field>
		<field name="title">Miami</field>
		<field name="main">learn</field>
		<field name="name">Barry University</field>
		<field name="content">(, – This Catholic university, located 20 miles outside of Miami, has majors such as biomedical and forensic photography as well as the very popular nursing, education and liberal arts majors. The university is co-ed with close to 10,000 students enrolled.</field>
		<field name="directions">in Miami Shores</field>
		<field name="phone">+1 305 899-3100</field>
		<field name="fax">+1 305 899-2971</field>
		<field name="address">11300 North East Second Ave</field>
		<field name="email">admissions@mail.barry.edu</field>
		<field name="url">http://www.barry.edu</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">63383</field>
		<field name="title">Dayton</field>
		<field name="main">learn</field>
		<field name="name">University of Dayton</field>
		<field name="phone">+1 937 229-1000</field>
		<field name="address">300 College Park</field>
		<field name="email">info@udayton.edu</field>
		<field name="url">http://www.udayton.edu/</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">63384</field>
		<field name="title">Naperville</field>
		<field name="main">learn</field>
		<field name="name">learn</field>
		<field name="content">Carnegie Hall on campus   North Central College  is a private, 4-year college nestled nicely into the surrounding historical district.  It has very strong business and education programs, award-winning track coach Al Carius and an impressive array of study abroad options for a small college.  The school is very integrated with the community at large as well: non-students are welcome to watch a musical performance at the impressive new Wentz Concert Hall, see a play at Pfeiffer Hall, check out the upstairs gallery at Oesterle Library and grab a coffee at the Boilerhouse Cafe.</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">63385</field>
		<field name="title">Knoxville</field>
		<field name="main">learn</field>
		<field name="name">learn</field>
		<field name="content">University of Tennessee.  A public land-grant doctoral-degree granting university.  The campus is near downtown.  Knoxville College.  A small, historically African-American college.  University of Tennessee Trial Gardens.  Located just off Neyland Drive behind the UT Veterinary Hospital on the UT Institute of Agriculture campus.</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">63386</field>
		<field name="title">Montpelier</field>
		<field name="main">learn</field>
		<field name="name">learn</field>
		<field name="content">New England Culinary Institute (NECI), (877) 223-6334 (email:info@neci.edu),   . Has a campus in Montpelier and operates the La Brioche bakery, Main Street Bar Grill, and the Chefs Table.</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">63387</field>
		<field name="title">Syracuse (New York)</field>
		<field name="main">learn</field>
		<field name="name">learn</field>
		<field name="content">Syracuse University (SU), Syracuse University, Syracuse, +1 315 443-1870,   . SUNY Upstate Medical University, 766 Irving Avenue, Syracuse, 315 464-5540    SUNY College of Environmental Science and Forestry (ESF), 1 Forestry Dr., +1 315 470-6500,   . LeMoyne, 1419 Salt Springs Rd., +1 315 445-4100,   . Onondaga Community College (OCC), 4941 Onondaga Rd., +1 315 498-2622,   . Cazenovia College, 22 Sullivan St., Cazenovia, +1 800 654-3210   .</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">63388</field>
		<field name="title">Saratoga Springs</field>
		<field name="main">learn</field>
		<field name="name">learn</field>
		<field name="content">Skidmore College, 815 North Broadway, 518-580-5000,   . Offering bachelors and/or graduate degrees in over 30 areas of study, as well as the "University Without Walls" degree completion program.  Empire State College, 111 West Avenue, 518-587-2100 ext. 2297,   .  Adirondack Community College, 6 Mountain Ledge Drive, Gansevoort 12831, 518-584-3959,   .</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">63389</field>
		<field name="title">Gary</field>
		<field name="main">learn</field>
		<field name="name">learn</field>
		<field name="content">Indiana University Northwest  has a campus in Gary, with about 5,000 students.   Ivy Tech Community College  is also in the area.</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">63390</field>
		<field name="title">Oviedo (Florida)</field>
		<field name="main">learn</field>
		<field name="name">learn</field>
		<field name="content">Seminole State College</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">63391</field>
		<field name="title">Newport (Rhode Island)</field>
		<field name="main">learn</field>
		<field name="name">Salve Regina University</field>
		<field name="phone">+1 401 847-6650</field>
		<field name="address">100 Ochre Point Avenue</field>
		<field name="url">http://www.salve.edu/</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">63392</field>
		<field name="title">Cleveland</field>
		<field name="main">learn</field>
		<field name="name">Cuyahoga Community College</field>
		<field name="content">"Tri-C" has three campuses (downtown, East Side and West Side suburbs). Dont miss its annual JazzFest.</field>
		<field name="phone">+1 800 954-8742</field>
		<field name="address">700 Carnegie Ave</field>
		<field name="url">http://www.tri-c.cc.oh.us</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">63393</field>
		<field name="title">Kansas City</field>
		<field name="main">learn</field>
		<field name="name">Steamboat Arabia Museum</field>
		<field name="phone">+1 816 471-4030</field>
		<field name="address">400 Grand Blvd</field>
		<field name="hours">M-Sa 10AM-5:30PM, Su noon-5PM</field>
		<field name="url">http://www.1856.com/</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">63394</field>
		<field name="title">Ann Arbor</field>
		<field name="main">learn</field>
		<field name="name">learn</field>
		<field name="content">the University of Michigan Diag</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">63395</field>
		<field name="title">Greenwich (Connecticut)</field>
		<field name="main">learn</field>
		<field name="name">learn</field>
		<field name="content">Greenwich has an extensive  public school system , mainly funded by town property taxes. As of October 1st, 2004, the enrollment in Greenwich public schools totaled 9,083 for the 2004-2005 academic year. This includes eleven elementary schools, three middle schools, and one high school (Greenwich High School).  Eagle Hill School, one of the nations premiere schools for children with learning disabilities, was founding in 1974 in Greenwich. It is located at 45 Glenville Road.</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">63396</field>
		<field name="title">Newark (New Jersey)</field>
		<field name="main">learn</field>
		<field name="name">Drake College of Business</field>
		<field name="content">Branch location of Elizabeths main campus.</field>
		<field name="address">800 Broad St</field>
		<field name="url">http://www.drakecollege.com/</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">63397</field>
		<field name="title">Bellingham (Washington)</field>
		<field name="main">learn</field>
		<field name="name">learn</field>
		<field name="content">Western Washington University   Whatcom Community College</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">63398</field>
		<field name="title">Waco</field>
		<field name="main">learn</field>
		<field name="name">learn</field>
		<field name="content">Baylor University  is in Waco.  McLennan Community College  has an active music and theater program. Texas State Technical College</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">63399</field>
		<field name="title">Bloomington-Normal</field>
		<field name="main">learn</field>
		<field name="name">learn</field>
		<field name="content">Illinois State University,   .  Illinois State University is Illinois first public university.  The town of Normal grew up around this school, long a teachers college and formerly known as "Illinois State Normal University" (a "normal" school being one dedicated to educating teachers).  It expanded enormously in the 1960s and is now a major university.  The basketball program is strong, although most other sports are at the 1-AA ("sub-major") level.  A trivium: the Watterson Towers complex on campus is, at nearly 300 feet high, the tallest college dormitory in the world. Illinois Wesleyan University,   .  Considerably smaller and more selective than its neighbor, with strong liberal-arts programs.  Illinois Wesleyan often appears on lists of the nations best "regional" small colleges. Heartland Community College,   .  Community college founded in 1991.</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">63400</field>
		<field name="title">Richmond (Indiana)</field>
		<field name="main">learn</field>
		<field name="name">learn</field>
		<field name="content">Richmond has four colleges Earlham College 801 National Road West    Founded by members of the Religious Society of Friends (Quakers) in 1847. It is known for its Biology, Peace Global Studies, and Japanese Studies Programs Indiana University East 2325 Chester Blvd    Ivy Tech Community College of Indiana 2357 Chester Blvd    Purdue University School of Technology 2325 Chester Blvd     In addition to its colleges, Richmond also has two seminaries located on the Earlham College Campus Earlham School of Religion (Quaker)    Bethany Theological Seminary (Church of the Brethren)</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">63401</field>
		<field name="title">Wellesley</field>
		<field name="main">learn</field>
		<field name="name">Babson College</field>
		<field name="content">Babson Park. Highly ranked business school.</field>
		<field name="phone">+1 781 235-1200</field>
		<field name="address">231 Forest Street</field>
		<field name="url">http://www.babson.edu/</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">63402</field>
		<field name="title">Fairmont (Minnesota)</field>
		<field name="main">learn</field>
		<field name="name">learn</field>
		<field name="content">Presentation College</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">63403</field>
		<field name="title">Kankakee</field>
		<field name="main">learn</field>
		<field name="name">learn</field>
		<field name="content">Kankakee is the home of  Olivet Nazarene University , located in the suburban Village of  Bourbonnais .   Kankakee Community College  is located in Kankakee.</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">63404</field>
		<field name="title">Gainesville (Georgia)</field>
		<field name="main">learn</field>
		<field name="name">learn</field>
		<field name="content">Brenau University     -   Gainesville State College     -</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">63405</field>
		<field name="title">Salt Lake City</field>
		<field name="main">learn</field>
		<field name="name">Family History Library</field>
		<field name="content">Search your family tree and study genealogy at the largest genealogy library in the world.</field>
		<field name="directions">across West Temple St from the Assembly Hall</field>
		<field name="phone">+1 801 240-2331</field>
		<field name="price">Free</field>
		<field name="address">35 North West Temple St</field>
		<field name="hours">M 7:30AM-5PM, Tu-Sa 7:30AM-10PM</field>
		<field name="url">http://www.utah.com/mormon/family_history.htm</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">63406</field>
		<field name="title">Lubbock</field>
		<field name="main">learn</field>
		<field name="name">learn</field>
		<field name="content">Public and private education in Lubbock are recognized state-wide and nationally. The economic contribution the citys education industry makes to this area is brought home during the summer months when business cools compared to the well-known summer heat.   Lubbock Christian University, 19th St. Dover Ave.,   .  A liberal arts, Christian university associated with the Church of Christ. Enrollment varies between 1,750 and 2,500 students. The university attracts a large number of non-religious students.   Texas Tech University, Broadway University Ave.,   . The largest university in west Texas, with upwards of 30,000 undergraduate and graduate students. The university is a public institution governed by a Board of Regents appointed by the Governor of Texas.   Texas Tech Health Sciences Center, 4th St. Indiana Ave.,   .  Established in 1961 as the School of Medicine at Texas Tech University. The TTUHSC operates regional campuses in Amarillo and El Paso. The University Medical Center    and its associated health system are a service operated in partnership with area governments and the TTUHSC.   Wayland Baptist University, 19th St. Iola Ave.,   . One of twelve campuses throughout the country, Waylands Lubbock facility offers several business certificate and degree programs.</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">63407</field>
		<field name="title">Lewisburg (Pennsylvania)</field>
		<field name="main">learn</field>
		<field name="name">Bucknell University</field>
		<field name="phone">+1 570-577-2000</field>
		<field name="address">701 Moore Avenue, Lewisburg</field>
		<field name="email">admissions@bucknell.edu</field>
		<field name="url">http://bucknell.edu/</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">63408</field>
		<field name="title">Harrisburg</field>
		<field name="main">learn</field>
		<field name="name">learn</field>
		<field name="content">Harrisburg University of Science and Technology , offers undergraduate, graduate and certificate programs in high technology fields in demand.  Harrisburg Area Community College , central Pennsylvanias community college with three campuses in the city.  Temple University Harrisburg , located in the heart of downtown offering graduate and certificate programs.  Dixon University Center , located in Uptown and is home to an array of undergraduate and graduate programs offered by way of other state universities.</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">63409</field>
		<field name="title">Dubuque</field>
		<field name="main">learn</field>
		<field name="name">learn</field>
		<field name="content">There are thousands of students who attend colleges in Dubuque. The largest are the citys 3 liberal arts colleges: Clarke College, Loras College, and the University of Dubuque. Collectively, the schools are known as the "Tri Colleges" and enjoy a friendly rivalry with one another. Other students attend the various religious institutions in the city, or Northeast Iowa Community College, which has a satellite location downtown.   Capri Cosmetology College    cosmetology college  Clarke University    4-year Roman Catholic college  Divine Word College    Roman Catholic missionary college in Epworth  Emmaus Bible College    Evangelical seminary, college  Loras College    4-year Roman Catholic college  Northeast Iowa Community College    2-year community college  University of Dubuque    4-year Presbyterian university  Wartburg Theological Seminary    Lutheran seminary</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">63410</field>
		<field name="title">Berkeley (California)</field>
		<field name="main">learn</field>
		<field name="name">Graduate Theological Union</field>
		<field name="directions">next to UC Berkeley</field>
		<field name="address">2400 Ridge Rd</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">63411</field>
		<field name="title">Joplin</field>
		<field name="main">learn</field>
		<field name="name">learn</field>
		<field name="content">Missouri Southern State University.  Messenger College.  Ozark Christian College</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">63412</field>
		<field name="title">Big Island</field>
		<field name="main">learn</field>
		<field name="name">learn</field>
		<field name="content">Dance, culture, and traditional crafts classes are available for long or short term students. Many resorts offer 1-3 day classes in hula or lei making. To learn about history, culture and the environment, visit the State and National Parks and speak with Rangers and other guides that reside there. Parks have many programs ranging from paricipation based programs, games, festivals, classes and more for visitors to learn about Hawaii. The only state or national parks that charge an entry fee are Puu o Honaunau and Volcanoes National Park.</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">63413</field>
		<field name="title">Concord (New Hampshire)</field>
		<field name="main">learn</field>
		<field name="name">learn</field>
		<field name="content">Franklin Pierce Law Center, Two White Street, Phone: (603) 228-1541,   .</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">63414</field>
		<field name="title">McHenry (Maryland)</field>
		<field name="main">learn</field>
		<field name="name">learn</field>
		<field name="content">Garrett College :687 Mosser Rd.; McHenry, MD 21541;  website  Library at Garrett College :687 Mosser Rd.; McHenry, MD 21541; 1-301-387-3009;  website</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">63415</field>
		<field name="title">Montgomery</field>
		<field name="main">learn</field>
		<field name="name">learn</field>
		<field name="content">Alabama State University,   . Southern Christian University,   . Auburn University Montgomery,   . Faulkner University,   . Is a small Christian university. Huntingdon College,   . A small United Methodist affiliated college. Air University,   . AU is operated by the U.S. Air Force.</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">63416</field>
		<field name="title">Grundy</field>
		<field name="main">learn</field>
		<field name="name">Appalachian College of Pharmacy</field>
		<field name="alt">ACP</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">63417</field>
		<field name="title">Miami</field>
		<field name="main">learn</field>
		<field name="name">University of Miami</field>
		<field name="content">Coral Gables, (, – Over 16,000 men and women are enrolled in this private college. Business, communication, medicine and biology majors are popular here.</field>
		<field name="phone">+1 305 284-4323</field>
		<field name="fax">+1 305 284-2507</field>
		<field name="email">admission@miami.edu</field>
		<field name="url">http://www.miami.edu</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">63418</field>
		<field name="title">Oakland</field>
		<field name="main">learn</field>
		<field name="name">The Crucible</field>
		<field name="content">An industrial arts collaborative offering classes in everything from blacksmithing to welding.</field>
		<field name="directions">At Union St., two blocks from West Oakland BART</field>
		<field name="phone">+1 510 444-0919</field>
		<field name="fax">+1 510 444-0918</field>
		<field name="address">1260 7th St.</field>
		<field name="email">info@thecrucible.org</field>
		<field name="url">http://www.thecrucible.org</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">63419</field>
		<field name="title">Huntington (West Virginia)</field>
		<field name="main">learn</field>
		<field name="name">learn</field>
		<field name="content">The local newspaper is the Herald-Dispatch, 946 5th Avenue, 304-526-4000 or 800-955-6110,   .   Marshall Universitys visitors center is located on Hal Greer Blvd. at 5th Ave.   .</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">63420</field>
		<field name="title">Kent (Ohio)</field>
		<field name="main">learn</field>
		<field name="name">Kent State University</field>
		<field name="content">Kent State, a public research university founded 1912 as a teachers college, offers 300 degree programs on eight campuses. The main campus in Kent houses 28800 of the systems 42500 students. Programs include nursing, liquid crystals, business, history, library science, aeronautics, journalism and fashion design.</field>
		<field name="phone">+1-330-672-2444</field>
		<field name="fax">+1-330-672-2499</field>
		<field name="wikipedia">Kent State University</field>
		<field name="url">http://www.kent.edu/</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">63421</field>
		<field name="title">Oakland</field>
		<field name="main">learn</field>
		<field name="name">Merritt College</field>
		<field name="content">Located high in the Oakland Hills, Merritt is the other Peralta community college.</field>
		<field name="directions">Off of Redwood Rd.</field>
		<field name="phone">+1 510 531-4911</field>
		<field name="address">12500 Campus Dr.</field>
		<field name="url">http://www.merritt.edu</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">63422</field>
		<field name="title">Bismarck</field>
		<field name="main">learn</field>
		<field name="name">learn</field>
		<field name="content">Gateway to Science , located in the former Masonic Temple. Interactive exhibits for all ages for learning about science. Open Tuesday through Saturday, from noon to 5:00 PM. Tel: (701) 258-1975.   Ft. Abraham Lincoln State Park   is made historically important because within its boundaries are the ruins of On-A-Slant Mandan Indian Village and the Fort Abraham Lincoln cavalry and infantry post.  It was from this fort that Lt. Col. George Armstrong Custer and the Seventh Cavalry rode out on their ill-fated expedition against the Sioux at the Little Big Horn. It has 95 camping sites. There are special events year-round. Guided horse-back trail riding is available in the summer and offers a wide view of the Missouri basin in this area. Tel: (800) 807-4723</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">63423</field>
		<field name="title">San Francisco</field>
		<field name="main">learn</field>
		<field name="name">learn</field>
		<field name="content">There are three world-class research universities in the Bay Area:  University of California, San Francisco  with two large campuses in San Francisco focused on biomedical research and training;  University of California, Berkeley  in  Berkeley ; and  Stanford University  in  Palo Alto . Many of the major businesses in the area have a connection to one of these universities.  The University of California, San Francisco is one of the citys largest employers and is dedicated solely to the education of health and the biomedical sciences. Unlike many other universities, it does not have undergraduate programs and only admits graduate students. Also in the University of California system is the Hastings College of the Law, a major law school located in downtown San Francisco. The San Francisco State University is another major public university that offers a broader range of studies than the UC colleges in the city. Rounding off the citys public colleges is the City College of San Francisco, a two-year community college.  San Francisco also has numerous private colleges and universities, some of them large, such as the University of San Francisco located in the Richmond district, and Academy of Art with properties throughout the city.</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">63424</field>
		<field name="title">Pittsburgh</field>
		<field name="main">learn</field>
		<field name="name">learn</field>
		<field name="content">University of Pittsburghs  Cathedral of Learning includes a unique collection of 27 working "Nationality" classrooms which are available to tour.]] The City of Pittsburgh is home to many colleges, universities and research facilities, the most well known of which are Carnegie Mellon University (CMU), Duquesne University, and the University of Pittsburgh (Pitt). Also located in the city are Carlow University, Chatham University, Point Park University, The Art Institute of Pittsburgh, and a branch campus of the suburban Robert Morris University as well as the Community College of Allegheny County and the Pittsburgh Institute of Mortuary Science. Oakland is the hub of college activity, home to CMU, Pitt, Carlow, and Chatham Universities.  The greater Pittsburgh region boasts even more colleges and universities.  The city also has an extensive library system, both public and university. Most notable are the Carnegie Library of Pittsburgh and the University of Pittsburghs University Library System, which rank 9th largest (public) and 18th largest (academic) in the nation, respectively.</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">63425</field>
		<field name="title">Cleveland</field>
		<field name="main">learn</field>
		<field name="name">Cleveland State University</field>
		<field name="content">Clevelands large state school is nestled next to the Theater District (Playhouse Square) and is a cornerstone of the St. Vincent Quadrangle District. The Levin College of Urban Affairs is ranked in the Top 10 in the US. Over the past century, CSUs law school,  Cleveland-Marshall College of Law , has educated many of the regions renowned judicial and political figures.</field>
		<field name="phone">+1 216 687-2000</field>
		<field name="address">2121 Euclid Ave</field>
		<field name="url">http://www.csuohio.edu/</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">63426</field>
		<field name="title">Cambridge (Massachusetts)</field>
		<field name="main">learn</field>
		<field name="name">Hult International Business School</field>
		<field name="phone">+1-617-746-1990</field>
		<field name="address">1 Education St</field>
		<field name="url">http://www.hult.edu</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">63427</field>
		<field name="title">Springfield (Massachusetts)</field>
		<field name="main">learn</field>
		<field name="name">learn</field>
		<field name="content">American International College,   . A university located in Springfields Mason Square neighborhood, notable for Americas first "Model Congress" program.   Springfield College  Founded in 1885 as Y.M.C.A. International College, basketball was invented at this institution by Dr. James Naismith. In addition to basketball, Americas first physical education course was taught here in 1912. A $50 million student center was constructed here in 2011.   Springfield Technical Community College  Located on 35 acres behind the Springfield Armory National Park, surrounded by the Armorys distinctive wrought-iron fence, STCC is Massachusetts only "technical" community college. STCC continues Springfields tradition of technical innovation.   Tufts University School of Medicine  Baystate Health serves as the western teaching campus of Tufts Universitys School of Medicine.    University of Massachusetts Urban Design Center  UMass opened an urban design center in Springfield in 2010, where it houses its urban design graduate program.   Western New England University  University in Springfields suburban Sixteen Acres neighborhood, featuring a pretty campus, prominent law school, and as of 2011, a $40 million, new pharmacy school.</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">63428</field>
		<field name="title">Rochester (New York)</field>
		<field name="main">learn</field>
		<field name="name">Rochester Brainery</field>
		<field name="content">Looking for a quick infusion of knowledge?  Or maybe you have something to teach the fine residents of Rochester?  Either way, the Brainery is the place to go, as they provide classroom space for teachers to teach just about anything, from cat care to computer graphics.  Their offerings change constantly, so check back often.</field>
		<field name="directions">Village Gate</field>
		<field name="phone">+1 585 730-7034</field>
		<field name="price">Students pay $15-25 per class; teachers receive $5 per seat sold</field>
		<field name="address">274 N Goodman St, Ste B134</field>
		<field name="email">info@rochesterbrainery.com</field>
		<field name="hours">Hours variable</field>
		<field name="url">http://rochesterbrainery.com/</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">63429</field>
		<field name="title">Newark (New Jersey)</field>
		<field name="main">learn</field>
		<field name="name">Rutgers University - Newark</field>
		<field name="url">http://www.newark.rutgers.edu/</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">63430</field>
		<field name="title">Beckley</field>
		<field name="main">learn</field>
		<field name="name">learn</field>
		<field name="content">The local newspaper is the Register-Herald, 304-255-4400 or 800-950-0250,   .   Mountain State University, 609 S Kanawha Street, 800-766-6067,   . An independent not-for-profit university founded in 1933 with more than 40 undergraduate and masters degree programs, mostly in business, technology, health, and human services.</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">63431</field>
		<field name="title">Worcester (Massachusetts)</field>
		<field name="main">learn</field>
		<field name="name">learn</field>
		<field name="content">Worcester boasts a fair number of high schools, colleges and universities in its region.   Assumption College, 500 Salisbury St.,   .  Becker College, 61 Sever St.,   .   Clark University, 950 Main St.,   .  College of the Holy Cross, 1 College St.,   .  Massachusetts College of Pharmacy and Health Sciences, 19 Foster St.,     Quinsigamond Community College, 670 West Boylston St.,   .  University of Massachusetts Medical School, 55 Lake Ave N,   .  Worcester Polytechnic Institute (WPI), 100 Institute Rd.,   .  Worcester State College, 486 Chandler St.,   .</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">63432</field>
		<field name="title">Cambridge (Massachusetts)</field>
		<field name="main">learn</field>
		<field name="name">Lesley University</field>
		<field name="phone">+1 617 868-9600</field>
		<field name="address">29 Everett Street</field>
		<field name="url">http://web.lesley.edu</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">63433</field>
		<field name="title">Downingtown</field>
		<field name="main">learn</field>
		<field name="name">learn</field>
		<field name="content">Education Systems:    ;Elementary: Beaver Creek Elementary Bradford Heights Elementary Brandywine Wallace Elementary East Ward Elementary Lionville Elementary Pickering Valley Elementary Shammona Creek Elementary- It lies at the top of the hill on Moore Road with a light blue roof ontop of it.  The mascot is the shamona creek sharks. Springton Manor Elementary Uwclan Hills Elementary West Bradford Elementary  ;Middle School: Downingtown Middle School Lionville Middle School  ;High School: Downingtown East High School- Located on route 113 and the crosstown rival of Downingtown West.  It is a public school.   Downingtown West High School- crosstown rival to Downingtown East and know for its sports.  Like Downingtown East it is a public school also.   Downingtown Educational Center   ;College: Delaware County Community College West Chester University lies just a town over from</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">63434</field>
		<field name="title">Frankfort (Kentucky)</field>
		<field name="main">learn</field>
		<field name="name">learn</field>
		<field name="content">Kentucky State University, East Main St., (502) 597-6000,   . KSU is a small, unique liberal studies university founded in 1886. Originally founded for the states African American community during the era of legalized segregation, KSU has long been integrated, but retains much of its historic African American character. Hume and Jackson Halls are on the National Register. Jackson Hall contains a public art gallery which features exhibits by KSU students and the Center of Excellence for the Study of Kentucky African Americans. Blazer Library contains over 350,000 volumes, has a special African-American collection, and is open to the public. KSU has facilities available for meetings and conferences. Athletic events, concerts, art exhibits, theater productions and public lectures are available to the public.</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">63435</field>
		<field name="title">Hartford</field>
		<field name="main">learn</field>
		<field name="name">learn</field>
		<field name="content">Trinity College, 300 Summit Street,   . Hartfords small ivy- consistently ranked as one of the best liberal arts colleges in the country. The college was founded in 1823 making it one of the oldest in the country. Trinitys 100 acre campus is in the Frog Hollow neighborhood and includes some of the most historic buildings in the city.  University of Connecticut School of Law, 45 Elizabeth Street,   . One of the nations best public law schools is in the citys West End. The campus is also listed on the National Register of Historic Sites.  University of Connecticut School of Business Graduate Learning Center, 100 Constitution Plaza,   . State of the art facility that opened downtown in 2004.  Capital Community College, 950 Main Street,   . Located downtown in the restored G. Fox Company department store building.  Rensselaer At Hartford, 275 Windsor Street,   .. The Connecticut State Library, 231 Capital Avenue,   . Located in the State Supreme Court building, along with the Connecticut State Museum. University of Hartford, 200 Bloomfield Avenue, West Hartford,   . Private university with one of the best music schools in the country. St Josephs College, 1678 Asylum Avenue, West Hartford,   . Womens college founded back in 1932 by the Sisters of Mercy that is on a scenic 84 acre campus.  Manchester Community College, 161 Hillstown Road, Manchester.   . Largest Community college in the state. Porter and Chester Institute, 30 Waterchase Drive, Rocky Hill   . PCI is less than 10 miles South of Hartford and focuses on learning-by-doing. Central Connecticut State University, 1615 Stanley Street, New Britain,   . Part of the Connecticut State University system located in the small city of New Britain about 10 miles southwest of Hartford. Founded in 1849 the university excels in educational excellence and Division I Sports. Goodwin College, 475 Burnside Avenue, East Hartford,   . Located minutes from downtown, just over the Connecticut River.  Tunxis Community College, 27 Scott Swamp Road, Farmington,   . Located about 20 minutes southwest of Hartford the college is home to about 7,000 full and part time students.  Hartford Seminary, 77 Sherman Street, Hartford,   . Located in the West End neighborhood, Hartford Seminary is a nondenominational graduate theological college notable for its programs on interfaith relations and Islamic Studies. It has academic tracks with an MA and PhD program as well as preparatory programs in congregational leadership.</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">63436</field>
		<field name="title">Aurora (Illinois)</field>
		<field name="main">learn</field>
		<field name="name">Aurora University</field>
		<field name="content">A private 4-year university with its main campus in Aurora, Illinois and the George Williams campus in Williams Bay, Wisconsin.  Approximately 4000 students have a wide range of majors to choose from.  The campus is also the home of the Schingoethe Center for Native American Cultures.</field>
		<field name="address">347 S. Gladstone Ave.</field>
		<field name="url">http://www.aurora.edu/</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">63437</field>
		<field name="title">Port Orange</field>
		<field name="main">learn</field>
		<field name="name">learn</field>
		<field name="content">Palmer College of Chiropractic</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">63438</field>
		<field name="title">Blue Bell</field>
		<field name="main">learn</field>
		<field name="name">learn</field>
		<field name="content">Wings Field is a general aviation airport located in Blue Bell. There is many airport information you can learn and even learn how to fly through certain precautions. There are flight training programs to teach you how to fly a plane. There is much history and education you can learn from Wings field and it is only 10 miles away from Philadelphia.  Montgomery County Community College is the sole public college in Montgomery County.</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">63439</field>
		<field name="title">Weston (West Virginia)</field>
		<field name="main">learn</field>
		<field name="name">learn</field>
		<field name="content">The citys newspaper is the Weston Democrat, 306 Main Avenue, 304-269-1600,   .</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">63440</field>
		<field name="title">Saginaw</field>
		<field name="main">learn</field>
		<field name="name">learn</field>
		<field name="content">Saginaw Valley State University  7400 Bay Road (University Center, MI). +1 989 964-4000.   Delta College  1961 Delta Rd. (University Center, MI). +1 989 686-9000.</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">63441</field>
		<field name="title">Middletown (Pennsylvania)</field>
		<field name="main">learn</field>
		<field name="name">Penn State Harrisburg</field>
		<field name="content">A branch campus of the Penn State University.</field>
		<field name="phone">+1 717-948-6020</field>
		<field name="address">777 West Harrisburg Pike, 17057</field>
		<field name="url">http://www.hbg.psu.edu/</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">63442</field>
		<field name="title">Ann Arbor</field>
		<field name="main">learn</field>
		<field name="name">University of Michigan</field>
		<field name="content">A highly-ranked research university with a strong athletics tradition, the University of Michigan has been located in Ann Arbor since 1837 and is deeply intertwined with the town, being one of the major employers in the area. It offers both undergraduate and graduate programs in social sciences, sciences, humanities and arts, engineering, law, business and medicine. The average student population is around 40,000, with about 5,000 faculty members. There are three campuses — North, Central, and South — with downtown Ann Arbor being adjacent to, and somewhat intermingled with, Central Campus.</field>
		<field name="phone">+1 734 764-1817</field>
		<field name="url">http://www.umich.edu</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">63443</field>
		<field name="title">Newton</field>
		<field name="main">learn</field>
		<field name="name">learn</field>
		<field name="content">Mount Ida College, Located in the more suburban south side of the city.  Boston College, Originally located in Bostons South End, the campus moved to the Boston/Newton border in the 19th Century.  The Boston campus (which is actually located in Newton) is filled with stunning Collegiate Gothic architecture, while the Newton campus boasts more modern buildings.  Lassell College, Located in Auburndale.  Lovely campus, some of which overlooks Woodlands Country Club golf course. Andover Theological Seminary, Located right next to Newton Centre.  Newton North High School and Newton South High School are among the best public high schools in the country. There are several elementary schools which feed into four middle schools and ultimately the two high schools.</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">63444</field>
		<field name="title">Council Bluffs</field>
		<field name="main">learn</field>
		<field name="name">Buena Vista University Council Bluffs Campus</field>
		<field name="content">Satellite campus of BVU which is based in  Storm Lake .</field>
		<field name="phone">+1 712 328-0788</field>
		<field name="fax">+1 712 322-8604</field>
		<field name="address">2700 College Rd</field>
		<field name="email">councilb@bvu.edu</field>
		<field name="tollfree">+1 800 798-0788</field>
		<field name="url">http://www.bvu.edu/learn/who_we_are/locations/council_bluffs.dot</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">63445</field>
		<field name="title">Boston</field>
		<field name="main">learn</field>
		<field name="name">learn</field>
		<field name="content">The Greater Boston area has some 65 accredited institutions of higher learning, including many world-renowned colleges, universities, conservatories, and seminaries. The metro Boston area has something of around 250,000 students living in the area at any given time. The most famous institutions in the area are undoubtedly  Harvard University , the first university to be founded in the United States, as well as the  Massachusetts Institute of Technology . Both universities have among the most competitive admissions process in the world, and are considered by many to be the two most prestigious universities in the world, and as such draw top quality students and faculty from far and wide.  In Boston:  Berklee College of Music      Boston Architectural College     Boston Conservatory     Boston University (BU)     Emerson College     Emmanuel College     Fisher College     Massachusetts College of Art and Design (MassArt)     Massachusetts College of Pharmacy and Health Sciences (MCPHS)     Massachusetts School of Professional Psychology (MSPP)     New England Conservatory of Music     New England School of Law     New England School of Acupuncture     Northeastern University     School of the Museum of Fine Arts (SMFA)     Simmons College     Suffolk University     Tufts University School of Medicine     University of Massachusetts Boston (UMass)     Wentworth Institute of Technology     Wheelock College     In Cambridge:  Harvard University     Lesley University     Massachusetts Institute of Technology (MIT)     In Brookline:  The New England Institute of Art (NEiA)     In Newton:  Boston College (BC)     In Waltham:  Brandeis University     Bentley University     In Medford:  Tufts University    (partially in Somerville)</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">63446</field>
		<field name="title">Charleston (West Virginia)</field>
		<field name="main">learn</field>
		<field name="name">learn</field>
		<field name="content">Charleston has three newspapers published under the umbrella corporation of Charleston Newspapers, 1001 Virginia Street E, +1-800-WVA-NEWS (982-6397):  : The Charleston Gazette,   . Daily weekday paper, published in some form since 1873.  : Charleston Daily Mail,   . Daily afternoon newspaper.  : Sunday Gazette-Mail,   . Sunday paper jointly published by the Gazette and the Daily Mail.  The city also has one university within its limits, and a second is in an unincorporated community about 8 miles (13 km) west of downtown. A two-year community college shares its campus with the second university.  : University of Charleston, 2300 MacCorkle Avenue SE, +1 304-357-4750 or +1 800-995-GO-UC (4682),   . A private, co-educational, residential university founded in 1888, offering baccalaureate degrees in 29 fields, associate degrees in 5 fields, and masters degrees in business administration and human resource management. : West Virginia State University, WV Route 25, Institute, +1 800-987-2112   . A public coeducational university founded in 1891 for the states African American community. Following the Brown v. Board of Education decision in 1954, it transformed from a primarily residential black college to a predominantly commuter college with a heavily white student body, although its administration remains heavily African American to this day. "State", as the school is locally called, offers about 70 different bachelors degrees in 20 different departments, plus masters degrees in biotechnology and media studies. : Kanawha Valley Community and Technical College, 102 Cole Complex, Institute, +1 304-766-3118   . A public two-year college located on West Virginia States campus, KVCTC was founded in 1953 as a unit of State. The two-year college received separate accreditation in 2003 and was separated from State in 2008; it now offers 22 associates degree programs, 11 certificate programs, and 12 collaborative degree programs.</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">63447</field>
		<field name="title">Wenham</field>
		<field name="main">learn</field>
		<field name="name">Gordon College</field>
		<field name="phone">+1 978-927-2300</field>
		<field name="address">255 Grapevine Road</field>
		<field name="url">http://www.gordon.edu/</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">63448</field>
		<field name="title">Oakland</field>
		<field name="main">learn</field>
		<field name="name">Lincoln University</field>
		<field name="content">A private university primarily focused on business, offering a modest variety of minors.</field>
		<field name="directions">At Franklin St.</field>
		<field name="phone">+1 510 628-8010</field>
		<field name="address">401 15th St</field>
		<field name="email">admissions@lincolnuca.edu</field>
		<field name="tollfree">+1-888-810-9998</field>
		<field name="url">http://www.lincolnuca.edu</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">63449</field>
		<field name="title">Dallas</field>
		<field name="main">learn</field>
		<field name="name">learn</field>
		<field name="content">Cheesemaking at a shop in  Deep Ellum .</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">63450</field>
		<field name="title">Beaumont</field>
		<field name="main">learn</field>
		<field name="name">learn</field>
		<field name="content">Lamar University</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">63451</field>
		<field name="title">Cleveland</field>
		<field name="main">learn</field>
		<field name="name">David N. Myers College</field>
		<field name="phone">+1 216 696-9000</field>
		<field name="address">3921 Chester Ave</field>
		<field name="tollfree">+1 877-DNMYERS</field>
		<field name="url">http://www.dnmyers.edu/</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">63452</field>
		<field name="title">Buckhannon</field>
		<field name="main">learn</field>
		<field name="name">learn</field>
		<field name="content">West Virginia Wesleyan College, 59 College Avenue, 304-473-8000,   . A liberal arts university founded in 1890, with 36 academic majors including biology, business, education, political science and psychology.</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">63453</field>
		<field name="title">Akron</field>
		<field name="main">learn</field>
		<field name="name">learn</field>
		<field name="content">UA Polymer Science Building    Kent State University, home of the Liquid Crystal Institute (where liquid crystal displays were invented) is about 15 miles northeast of downtown Akron in the delightful small college town of  Kent .</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">63454</field>
		<field name="title">Fort Worth</field>
		<field name="main">learn</field>
		<field name="name">learn</field>
		<field name="content">Southwestern Baptist Theological Seminary   The College of Saint Thomas More   Tarrant County College   Texas Christian University   University of North Texas Health Science Center   Texas Wesleyan University   Texas Wesleyan University School of Law</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">63455</field>
		<field name="title">Spencer (West Virginia)</field>
		<field name="main">learn</field>
		<field name="name">learn</field>
		<field name="content">The local newspaper is the Times Record, 210 E Main Street, 304-927-2360,   .</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">63456</field>
		<field name="title">Cincinnati</field>
		<field name="main">learn</field>
		<field name="name">Xavier University</field>
		<field name="content">Xavier (pronounced Zay-vyur) is a private Jesuit, Catholic university located in the neighborhood of Evanston. It was founded in 1831. Its three colleges offer 78 undergraduate majors, 43 minors and 11 graduate programs to 6,646 total students, including 3,961 undergraduates. The University is the sixth-oldest Catholic university in the nation and one of 28 Jesuit colleges and universities nationwide. Xavier has been recognized as one of the nations best colleges and universities for 13 consecutive years by U.S. News World Report, including 2 in the Midwest in the 2008 rankings. Xavier is also ranked as one of the "Best 368 Colleges and Universities" by the Princeton Review. Xaviers Williams College of Business is also recognized by the Princeton Review as one of the "Best 290 Business Schools." Xaviers part-time MBA program is also highly ranked by U.S. News World Report and the Health Services Administration Graduate Program is ranked number one in the country by Modern Healthcare. Xavier supports 16 NCAA Division I sports teams. The mens basketball team made it to the Elite Eight in 2008 and 2004, and the womens basketball team matched the feat in 2010.</field>
		<field name="phone">+1-513 -745-3000</field>
		<field name="address">3800 Victory Parkway</field>
		<field name="url">http://www.xu.edu/</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">63457</field>
		<field name="title">Modesto</field>
		<field name="main">learn</field>
		<field name="name">Community Business College</field>
		<field name="content">Take a class for pleasure and learn a new skill.</field>
		<field name="directions">Take Hwy 99 to Standiford Ave, then right on McHenry</field>
		<field name="phone">+1 209 529-3648</field>
		<field name="price">$37+</field>
		<field name="address">3800 McHenry Ave</field>
		<field name="hours">8AM-5PM</field>
		<field name="url">http://www.communitybusinesscollege.edu</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">63458</field>
		<field name="title">Fairfield (Iowa)</field>
		<field name="main">learn</field>
		<field name="name">learn</field>
		<field name="content">Home of the Maharishi University of Management and the Maharishi School for the Age of Enlightenment.  Local media: The Source (monthly) and The Weekly Reader (weekly) have current listings for classes, workshops, music, art shows, theater, dance, and everything else thats going on here as well as around the state.</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">63459</field>
		<field name="title">Fall River (Massachusetts)</field>
		<field name="main">learn</field>
		<field name="name">learn</field>
		<field name="content">Bristol Community College is a two year community college with a wide array of degree options, ranging from certificates, to associates degrees. BCC offers transfer options to four year colleges, as well as competitive two year programs in Nursing and Dental Hygiene.</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">63460</field>
		<field name="title">Fullerton</field>
		<field name="main">learn</field>
		<field name="name">Cal State University of Fullerton</field>
		<field name="content">CSUF is a 4-year university that offers 105 degree programs, including a doctorate in education.</field>
		<field name="phone">+1 714 278-2011</field>
		<field name="address">800 N. State College Blvd.</field>
		<field name="alt">CSUF</field>
		<field name="url">http://www.fullerton.edu/</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">63461</field>
		<field name="title">Natick</field>
		<field name="main">learn</field>
		<field name="name">learn</field>
		<field name="content">Natick doesnt have any colleges and universities in town.  There are notable schools, including the Walnut Hill School for the Arts   .  The High School is known for Ivy League university preparation.</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">63462</field>
		<field name="title">Salt Lake City</field>
		<field name="main">learn</field>
		<field name="name">learn</field>
		<field name="content">Granite Peaks Lifelong Learning  is part of the Granite School District in Salt Lake City and offers a wide variety of courses for serious education or for fun at a reasonable price.  English as a second language, GED Prep and Food Handlers Permit classes are available, as well as a few Spanish-language courses.  For those of you looking for something more fun, sign up for wine tasting, pottery or even ghost hunting!    The University of Utah Continuing Education Department  also offers classes on art, finance, foreign languages and a variety of specialty subjects.</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
</add>