<add>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">51300</field>
		<field name="title">Westchester County</field>
		<field name="main">municipalities</field>
		<field name="name">cities</field>
		<field name="content">Mount Vernon  - named after George Washingtons home. The Mount Vernon Public Library is the largest public library in Westchester County.  New Rochelle  - On Long Island Sound. Home of Iona College and the College of New Rochelle.  Peekskill  - northern-most city in Westchester with scenic views of the Hudson Highlands.  Rye  - upscale city on the Long Island Sound; home of Playland amusement park. Smallest and least city-like of the cities in Westchester; has a small central area with one main street (Purchase Street) and feels much more like a village than anything else.  White Plains  - the seat of government for Westchester County, its downtown has recently been redeveloped with upscale housing and retail. Has two large shopping malls, the Galleria and the Westchester.   Yonkers  - 4th largest city in New York state and undergoing major development along the Hudson River. Getty Square, its traditional center only a few blocks east of the river, is down-scale.</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">51301</field>
		<field name="title">Westchester County</field>
		<field name="main">municipalities</field>
		<field name="name">villages and towns</field>
		<field name="content">Westchester has 19 towns and 23 villages, including the following:    Ardsley  - this village is part of the town of Greenburg, not be confused with the nearby hamlet of Ardsley-on-Hudson, which is part of the village of Irvington   Bedford (New York)  - yes, Martha Stewart still lives here. The Bedford Village Historic District, Caramoor Center for Music and the Arts, Palmer-Lewis Estate, and The Woodpile are listed on the National Register of Historic Places.   Briarcliff Manor  - a village shared by two towns, two libraries and two school districts. Home to (Donald) Trump National Golf Course and many wealthy families including the late Brooke Astor, heir of Americas first multi-millionaire, John Jacob Astor.   Bronxville  - affluent square-mile community listed in Forbes as one of "Americas Most Expensive ZIP Codes". Historic sites include the US Post Office–Bronxville, the Bronxville Womens Club, Lawrence Park Historic District, and the Masterton-Dusenberry House.   Buchanan  - home of the Indian Point nuclear power facility   Chappaqua  - home of Bill and Hillary Clinton   Cortlandt  - township in the northwest corner of the county, borders the Hudson River and  Putnam County . The Old Croton Dam is listed on the National Register of Historic Places.   Croton-on-Hudson  - location of popular Croton Point Park, which juts nearly a mile into the river. Also home to Teatown Lake Reservation.   Dobbs Ferry  - quaint Hudson River village. The Estherwood and Carriage House, Hyatt-Livingston House, South Presbyterian Church, and United States Post Office are listed on the National Register of Historic Places.   Eastchester  - former home of a president, John Adams, and vice president, Aaron Burr. Upscale shopping at the Vernon Hills Shopping Center.    Elmsford  - roughly one mile square, this village is the alleged birthplace of the term "cocktail".    Greenburgh  - historic sites in this town include the Romer-Van Tassel House (town hall in 1793), the Church of St. Joseph of Arimathea, the Odell House, and the Spanish American War Monument to the 71st Infantry Regiment.   Harrison  - both a town and a village of the same name. Historical places include the Hadden-Margolis House, Stony Hill Cemetery, and United States Post Office.   Hastings-on-Hudson  - Hudson River village has stunning views of the cliffs of the Palisades. Former home to Billie Burke, the "Good Witch" in the Wizard of Oz. Historical sites include the Jasper F. Cropsey House and Studio, the Hastings Prototype House,and the John William Draper House.   Irvington  - "Charming, quiet, green, with a darling Main Street, stunning river views, and a burgeoning dining scene ... this unassuming rivertown is pretty near perfect."    Named for Washington Irving, who lived nearby at Sunnyside.   Katonah  - in 1897 over 50 buildings of the original town were moved a mile or so south to make way for one of New York Citys reservoirs. The Katonah Village Historic District, Stepping Stones, and St. Lukes Episcopal Church are listed on the National Register of Historic Places. The John Jay Homestead is listed as a National Historic Landmark.   Larchmont  - Affluent square-mile community on Long Island Sound. Before the automobile, Larchmont was a resort community serving wealthy New York City residents; many of the Victorian "cottages" and a few of the grand hotels remain to this day.   Lewisboro  - though lacking a downtown business district, Lewisboro is rich in natural areas with two Westchester County Parks, six town parks and several community preserves.    Mamaroneck  - name of both a town and a village on Long Island Sound. The exclusive Winged Foot Golf Club has hosted the PGA Championship and several US Opens. Home to Walters Hot Dog Stand, a Westchester County landmark.   Mount Kisco  - ostensibly named after local Native American chief Kisco. Now a commercial hub of northern Westchester for shopping and dining with both small businesses and large chain stores like Target, Gap, and Staples.   Mount Pleasant  township containing Eastview, Hawthorne, Pleasantville, Pocantico Hills, Sleepy Hollow, Thornwood, Valhalla, and part of Briarcliff Manor.   New Castle  this town includes the hamlet of Millwood. The Williams-DuBois House and Isaac Young House are listed on the National Register of Historic Places   North Salem  - mostly rural; rolling hills, horse farms, and apple orchards. The fictitious headquarters of the X-Men superhero team is located in Salem Center.   Ossining  - the location of Sing Sing maximum-security prison where New York City mobsters were sent "up the river". Outside the prison walls, Ossining is ranked the 2 best community to live in by Westchester Magazine.   Pelham  - "the first suburb north of New York City" lies on Long Island Sound, bordering the Bronx. Consists of Villages of Pelham and Pelham Manor.   Pleasantville  - no, we didnt make this up; longtime address of Readers Digest   Port Chester  - The Bush-Lyon Homestead, Capitol Theater, Life Savers Building, Putnam and Mellor Engine and Hose Company Firehouse, St. Peters Episcopal Church, and United States Post Office are listed on the National Register of Historic Places.   Pound Ridge  - this wealthy town has been the home of many celebrities including Christopher Reeve (Superman).    Purchase  - home of a state university of fine art as well as headquarters for several major American corporations   Rye Brook  - contains six main parks totaling nearly 100 acres    Scarsdale  - ranked by CNN Money in 2011 as the 3rd "top earning town" in the nation with residents like Liza Minnelli and Yoko Ono     Sleepy Hollow  - the very one from The Legend of Sleepy Hollow. Many places in the story can still be visited today like the Old Dutch Church and Cemetery.    Somers  - "cradle of the American circus" where Hachaliah Bailey bought an African elephant to use for farm work but it drew such crowds that Bailey took "Old Bet" on the road as a traveling circus. Bailey built the Elephant Hotel in Old Bets honor and the elephant remains a symbol of the town to this day.   Tarrytown  - this Hudson River village is home to several significant historic sites as well as a quaint business district featuring restaurants and antique shops.    Town of Rye  - not the city of Rye, the town of Rye includes  Port Chester ,  Rye Brook  and part of  Mamaroneck .   Tuckahoe  - was a major producer of high-quality white marble for the world.   Valhalla  - this hamlet is reputedly named by a devoted fan of Wagner for the heavenly abode in Norse mythology. Today Valhalla is home to several large cemeteries which are final resting places of many rich and famous people.   Yorktown Heights  - home to the IBM Thomas J. Watson Research Center and the Guiding Eyes for the Blind headquarters. The town hosts a yearly Greasestock festival, a showcase of alternative fuel vehicles.   West Harrison  - site of the Battle of White Plains during the Revolutionary War</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">51302</field>
		<field name="title">Medina County (Ohio)</field>
		<field name="main">municipalities</field>
		<field name="name">municipalities</field>
		<field name="content">Brunswick   Chippewa Lake   Creston   Gloria Glens Park   Lodi   Medina  the County Seat of Medina County, is another quaint Western Reserve town with antique stores, craft shops and cafes surrounding its Public Square.  Rittman   Seville   Spencer   Wadsworth   Westfield Center</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
</add>