<add>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">80619</field>
		<field name="title">Ridgewood</field>
		<field name="main">orientation</field>
		<field name="name">orientation</field>
		<field name="content">Ridgwood is a fairly large town with many different neighborhoods so it is important to get somewhat aqauinted with all of them if you are planning on exploring Ridgewood outside of downtown: Downtown - Self-Expanatory.  The central area of the town.  Most of what you would want to see and do is in this neighborhood.  It is divided into two distinct ares: East Downtown and West Downtown (Separated by the NJ Transit Railroad Tracks).  East Downtown (Which straddles E. Ridgewood Ave. and the surrounding streets) is by far the larger of the two sides and has a vibrant energy to it and is home to "action".  West Downtown (Which Incorporates the areas around W. Rigewood Ave. and Wilsey Sq.) has more of a quaint and small town attitude to it.  But dont be fooled by the quaint vibe of W. Downtown because most if not all of the stores are luxury stores selling luxury goods.  The main streets of the Downtown neighborhood are Ridgewood Ave. (East to N Maple Ave. and West to Godwin Ave.), Wilsey Sq., Van Neste Sq., Franklin Ave., Godwin Ave., N. Maple Ave., and Broad Street (North of Brogan Cadillac). Broad Street - Straddles Broad Street south of Downtown (After Brogan Cadillac).  The grungiest area of Ridgewood is home to mainly multi-family homes and apartment buildings.  Luckily, "the worst part of town" only runs along Broad Street and only a couple houses into the surrounding streets. Old Ridgwood - The oldest part of Ridgewood.  Located south of Downtown and east of Broad Street all the way up to the border with Glen Rock).  Mainly homes built on treelined streets, many of which with original stone-paved "gutters" on the sides of the roads.  Home to some of the largest houses in Ridgewood.  Be aware when driving in this area that many of the streets are very narrow and some have not been paved in a very long time leaving ruts and potholes around.  Also be aware during the winter on icy roads due to the fact that most roads heading east of this area eventually scale a steep and poorly paved road down to other roads.  To avoid the steep icy roads, head west until you hit Broad Street and the head north of Broad Street until you reach downtown.  Head east on E. Ridgewood Ave. and at the intersection with Maple Ave., make a right onto S. Maple Ave.  From here you should be able to access wherever you need to go with going down a steep, poorly pave street.</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
</add>