<add>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">105381</field>
		<field name="title">Providence</field>
		<field name="main">other eateries</field>
		<field name="name">Local 121</field>
		<field name="phone">+1 401 274-2121</field>
		<field name="address">121 Washington St.</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">105382</field>
		<field name="title">Providence</field>
		<field name="main">other eateries</field>
		<field name="name">Cafe Noir</field>
		<field name="content">Specializing in all your fine dining needs, Cafe Noir is the place for a classy and elegant dining experience. Known for its french cuisine with a twist, Cafe Noir is a must if you are new to the area or just passing through. Full bar available and also a variety of delectable desserts which are made fresh to order!</field>
		<field name="phone">+1 401-272-2116</field>
		<field name="price">$$$</field>
		<field name="address">125 North Main St.</field>
		<field name="hours">Sunday-Thursday 5pm-10pm, Friday Saturday 5pm-11pm</field>
		<field name="url">http://www.cafenoirri.com</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">105383</field>
		<field name="title">Providence</field>
		<field name="main">other eateries</field>
		<field name="name">El Rancho Grande</field>
		<field name="content">Family business owner Maria Meza opened her restaurant mid 2007. This Mexican family restaurant offers traditional and affordable dished while also using authentic ingredients at the same time. Most of their ingredients are brought in directly from Mexico, providing an authentic Mexican taste and experience. Maria hosts many festive Mexican traditional events throughout the year to give her customers a rare and memorable time.</field>
		<field name="phone">+1  401 275-0808</field>
		<field name="address">311 Plainfield St</field>
		<field name="hours">8am-10pm</field>
		<field name="url">http://www.elranchogranderestaurant.com/</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">105384</field>
		<field name="title">Providence</field>
		<field name="main">other eateries</field>
		<field name="name">A Taste of India</field>
		<field name="content">A small but cozy Indian restaurant which specializes in curry dishes and authentic appetizers. Vegan friendly, and also offers Gluten-free menu items. Price range $2-$35.</field>
		<field name="phone">+1 401-421-4355</field>
		<field name="address">230 Wickenden Street, Providence, RI</field>
		<field name="hours">M- F: 11:30AM-2:30PM, 5:00PM-10:00PM Sa Su: 12:00PM-3:00 PM, 5:00PM-9:30PM</field>
		<field name="url">http://www.tasteofindiari.com/</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">105385</field>
		<field name="title">Providence</field>
		<field name="main">other eateries</field>
		<field name="name">other eateries</field>
		<field name="content">Rue De LEspoir, 99 Hope Street, +401 751-8890,   . Offers unique dining experiences in breakfast, lunch, dinner and weekend brunch. Set in the historic East Side district of Providence, "The Rue" features food specializing in fresh regional cooking, with influences from France, Italy, and Asia. Charming and warm ambience, friendly wait staff and an impressive menu. Interesting choices are their cheese board and Mondays "Dollar Daze," with $1 apps at the bar.   Not Just Snacks, 833 Hope Street, +1 401 831-1150. This is a small restaurant that serves very traditional Indian and Pakistani food at an affordable price. This family owned and handicapped accessible business is open from 11AM-9PM 7 days a week. They do not take reservations but you can call in to place an order either to be eaten there or to take out. They do not serve and drinks that are alcoholic. However, they are a BYOB establishment and will provide you with glasses for beer or wine upon request. Both the outside and inside of the buildings are very unassuming so make sure when looking for it your eyes are peeled.   Fellinis Pizzeria, 166 Wickenden Street, +1 401 751-6737,   .Su-W open until 12AM, Th-Sa open until 2AM . New York style, thin-crust pizza with creative toppings. Fun atmosphere, for kids and kids at heart due to the pinball machines. Awesome specials, specifically at Thanksgiving time, which is when they offer a one-time-a-year Thanksgiving style pizza. Free delivery for Providence area.  Sakura, 231 Wickenden Street, +1 401 331-6861,   . Enjoy traditional Japanese cuisine and fresh sushi, in true Japanese style, at Sakura. The staff are very friendly although some are hard to understand. It can get very busy and sometimes the only available in the dining room where you must sit on the floor at the tables. You usually find a lot of college students in this dining room, they dont mind it. BYOB. Meals $6-$20.  3 Steeple Street, 125 Canal Street, +1 401 272-3620, serving dishes like smoked trout and Maryland crab cakes within stone slate walls and wooden plank floors in the second-oldest industrial building in the United States. $16-$33.  Union Station Brewery, 36 Exchange Terrace.  +1 401 274-2739.  Serves bar grill-type food, but come for the beer!  Union Station brews its own beer in 6 different styles.  Cant decide which to get?  Theyll serve you 5oz of each for $7.50.  The namesake comes from the fact that the restaurant was carved out of the original 1898 Union Station.  The Capital Grille, 1 Union Station, +1 401 521-5600,   . The Capital Grille has exquisite dry aged steaks and a friendly, but comfortable atmosphere. They also have an award winning wine list. Eating here is always excellent. This franchise is actually the original restaurant in the Capital Grille chain.  Capriccio, 2 Pine St., +1 401 421-1320,   . M-Th 11:30PM-10:30PM; F-Sa 11:30AM-11PM and Su 11:30AM-9PM. This restaurant is among the best of Providence. Extended wine list (more than 550 available), fabulous wait staff, exquisite food are some of the things that make this restaurant as good as it is. The food is expensive, but worth it. Many of the items on the menu are made by your table. You can not go wrong with the Steak Diane, cooked tableside, or any other dish on the menu for that matter!   Cuban Revolution, 50 Aborn St., +1 401 331-8829,   . M-Sa 11AM-12AM.Cuban Revolution features a signature, award winning Latin menu. Voted Best Sandwich in Rhode Island in 2003.  Meals $6-$12.  Ruths Chris Steakhouse, GTech Center 10 Memorial Blvd., +1 401 272-2271,   . M-Th 5PM-10PM,F4:30PM-11PM, Sa 4PM-11PM, Su 5PM-9PM. Ruths Chris Steakhouse serves New Orleans-inspired appetizers, U.S. Fine steaks, fresh seafood, classic desserts, and an award winning wine list. This is a frequent place of interest for the New England Patriots football players. Private dining rooms available.</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">105386</field>
		<field name="title">Providence</field>
		<field name="main">other eateries</field>
		<field name="name">Wings and Things</field>
		<field name="content">Wings and Things is located within the Brown University campus on the East Side. They are best known for their wings and boneless chicken chunks, slathered in your choice of 20 sauces. As far as dedicated wing joints go in Providence, this is the one to beat. They offer dine-in, take out, or delivery. If youre in the mood for some spicy wings or want to test your machismo by trying to handle their highest heat, then Wings and Things is the place to go.</field>
		<field name="phone">+1 401 369-7551</field>
		<field name="address">250 Brook St.</field>
		<field name="url">http://www.wingsandthingsri.com/</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">105387</field>
		<field name="title">Providence</field>
		<field name="main">other eateries</field>
		<field name="name">Tea in Sahara</field>
		<field name="content">Very affordable Moroccan appetizers, smoothies, and paninis. Hookahs, with a variety of flavors, are also served. Relaxed atmosphere and friendly servers. Free WiFi provided.</field>
		<field name="phone">+1 401 709-3252</field>
		<field name="address">69 Governor St.</field>
		<field name="hours">11 am - 11 pm</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">105388</field>
		<field name="title">Providence</field>
		<field name="main">other eateries</field>
		<field name="name">La Sonrisa</field>
		<field name="content">Best Spanish food around. For $5.00 get a full course meal. From Chicken rice and beans to seafood salad. Order in or take out.</field>
		<field name="phone">+1 401  228-3470</field>
		<field name="price">$5.00</field>
		<field name="address">320 Broad St Providence</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
</add>