<add>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">32009</field>
		<field name="title">Arizona</field>
		<field name="main">other destinations</field>
		<field name="name">national parks</field>
		<field name="content">Glen Canyon National Recreation Area    Grand Canyon National Park    Lake Mead National Recreation Area    Petrified Forest National Park    Saguaro National Park</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">32010</field>
		<field name="title">Arizona</field>
		<field name="main">other destinations</field>
		<field name="name">national monuments</field>
		<field name="content">Canyon de Chelly National Monument    Casa Grande Ruins National Monument    Chiricahua National Monument    Four Corners Monument    Montezuma Castle National Monument    Navajo National Monument    Ravens, Petrified Forest National Park     Organ Pipe Cactus National Monument    Parashant National Monument    Sunset Crater Volcano National Monument</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">32011</field>
		<field name="title">Arizona</field>
		<field name="main">other destinations</field>
		<field name="name">national forests</field>
		<field name="content">Apache-Sitgreaves National Forest    Tonto National Forest    Coronado National Forest    Coconino National Forest</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">32012</field>
		<field name="title">Arizona</field>
		<field name="main">other destinations</field>
		<field name="name">state parks</field>
		<field name="content">The  Arizona State Parks  offer an array of options for outdoor enthusiasts:    Homolovi Ruins State Park    Kartchner Caverns State Park    Lake Havasu State Park    Lyman Lake State Park     Picacho Peak State Park    Roper Lake State Park</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">32013</field>
		<field name="title">California</field>
		<field name="main">other destinations</field>
		<field name="name">national parks</field>
		<field name="content">Channel Islands National Park  - five remarkable islands (Anacapa, Santa Cruz, Santa Rosa, San Miguel, and Santa Barbara) and their ocean environment  Death Valley National Park  - A place of legend and a place of trial  Joshua Tree National Park    Lassen Volcanic National Park  - witness a brief moment in the ancient battle between the earth shaping forces of creation and destruction  Redwood National Park  - Stand at the base of a coast redwood and even the huckleberry bushes tower over you  Sequoia and Kings Canyon National Parks  - These twin parks hold monuments to natures size, beauty, and diversity  Yosemite National Park  - one of the first wilderness parks in the United States</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">32014</field>
		<field name="title">California</field>
		<field name="main">other destinations</field>
		<field name="name">california state parks</field>
		<field name="content">California has many  state parks , approximately half of which are located near urban centers. A few are highlighted below:   Big Basin Redwoods State Park   Pfeiffer Big Sur State Park   Richardson Grove State Park   Calaveras Big Trees</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">32015</field>
		<field name="title">Connecticut</field>
		<field name="main">other destinations</field>
		<field name="name">beaches</field>
		<field name="content">See "Do"</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">32016</field>
		<field name="title">Kitsap Peninsula</field>
		<field name="main">other destinations</field>
		<field name="name">islands</field>
		<field name="content">Eagle Harbor on Bainbridge Island  Several islands are accessible from bridges or ferries from the Kitsap Peninsula and are included in this entry.  Bainbridge Island  -- a 35 minute ferry ride from  Seattle  this Island of 20,000 residents is a good place to visit and/or live   Blake Island  -- Manchester is the closest boat launch to this popular island state park between Seattle and the Kitsap Peninsula.  Eagle Island  -- off of the Key Peninsula more info in State Parks Section.  Fox Island  -- a 5.2 square mile island with a lighthouse.</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">32017</field>
		<field name="title">New Jersey</field>
		<field name="main">other destinations</field>
		<field name="name">attractions</field>
		<field name="content">Here are a few areas worth exploring:  Cream Ridge — Wine country.  The  Delaware Water Gap National Recreation Area  — Camping, hiking and rafting on the Delaware River.  The  Jersey Shore - Beaches, birds, and boardwalks-and beautiful lighthouses.   Lake Hopatcong  — New Jerseys largest lake provides boating and swimming for families and singles. Mountain Creek — Ski resort and water park in  Sussex County , 1 hour from New York City.  Keansburg  -- Boardwalk Amusement Park and Water Slide The  Pine Barrens  — A natural forest that covers about a third of the state.  Raritan Bayshore -  An area along the Raritan Bay between the Amboys and Sandy Hook. Though the area is more developed than the Delaware Bayshore, its brackish water beaches remain less crowded than the Atlantic Beaches.     Sandy Hook . At the northern end of New Jerseys coast, Sandy Hook is home to one of the Northeasts only officially clothing-optional beaches. Six Flags Great Adventure Hurricane Harbor — Safari, waterpark and amusement park in  Jackson Township . Camden Waterfront--includes USS New Jersey (battleship), Adventure Aquarium, and Childrens Garden. Cape May Whale Watcher- Sailing daily from the Miss Chris Marina. Cape May, New Jersey affords opportunities to view species of whales, dolphins, porpoise and pelagic birds. Jersey Shore Fishing- Head boats are large boats which carry several passengers for bottom fishing and wreck fishing. Charter boats are smaller boats which are typically privately chartered for fishing excursions. From the Atlantic Highlands south to Cape May and up the Western Shore to Fortescue, fishing boats for hire can be found to take you deep sea fishing for many species (flounder, drumfish, bluefish, striped bass, and tuna are among the favorites). Typically this is relegated to the Spring, Summer and Fall.</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">32018</field>
		<field name="title">New Jersey</field>
		<field name="main">other destinations</field>
		<field name="name">national parks</field>
		<field name="content">Appalachian National Scenic Trail    Delaware Water Gap National Recreation Area    Gateway National Recreation Area    New Jersey Pinelands National Reserve    Great Swamp National Wildlife Refuge    Morristown National Historical Park</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">32019</field>
		<field name="title">Stone County (Mississippi)</field>
		<field name="main">other destinations</field>
		<field name="name">flint creek water park</field>
		<field name="content">Located on Highway 29, Wiggins, MI. Centered around a 600-acre lake, stocked with bass, bream, crappie and catfish. Other activities include boating (rentals available), water skiing, and swimming. Flint Creeks Water Town offers multiple waterslides, including four giant ones for the adults, and is open most of the year.  There is plenty of camping available in the form of tent/rv spots, cabins, and camphouses. There is also a nature trail for hikers, and a picnic area with grills and tables. On the fourth of July, the park runs its annual fireworks display. A "haunted forest" is put on every year the Saturday before Halloween.</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">32020</field>
		<field name="title">Utah</field>
		<field name="main">other destinations</field>
		<field name="name">national parks and monuments</field>
		<field name="content">A  "Park Pass"  from the United States National Park Service is a particularly good investment if youre visiting Utah and planning to see its national parks and monuments.  The $80 fee allows unlimited access to all National Park Service units for a year, and also provides discounts on some of the services within the units.  Paying for this pass may save you money in the long run as you move from park to park in Utah.  (Note, however, that there are a very few national monuments that are not part of the National Park Service, and are therefore not covered by a Park Pass;  Monument Valley  is one prominent example in Utah.)   Arches National Park  ndash; largest concentration of natural arches in the world, just northeast of Moab, as well as other strange sandstone formations, such as pinnacles, cliffs, mesas, and gorges  Bryce Canyon National Park  ndash; heavily-forested mountainous area with large natural amphitheater and other strange sandstone formations  Canyonlands National Park  ndash; large, spectacular wilderness of sandstone cliffs, narrow gorges, canyons, plateaus, bluffs, and other strange and beautiful formations west of Moab  Capitol Reef National Park  ndash; remote park along the Waterpocket Fold, a 100 mile monocline of domes, monoliths and narrow canyons  Cedar Breaks National Monument  ndash; large natural amphitheater northeast of Cedar City in forested, mountainous area  Dinosaur National Monument  ndash; area featuring a major excavation site for dinosaur bones as well as spectacular scenery and Native American rock art  Glen Canyon National Recreation Area - Lake Powell   Golden Spike National Historic Site  ndash; the first transcontinental railroad was completed by the driving of a symbolic golden spike at Promontory Summit in The Utah Territory  Grand Staircase-Escalante National Monument   Hovenweep National Monument  -- mainly in  Colorado  but with some units in southeastern Utah  Zion National Park  ndash; popular area of sandstone cliffs, gorges, gullies, bluffs, plateaus, mesas, and other strange and colorful formations</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">32021</field>
		<field name="title">Utah</field>
		<field name="main">other destinations</field>
		<field name="name">other</field>
		<field name="content">Mount Timpanogos in the Uintah National Forest is located near  Provo .   Great Salt Lake    Bear Lake - popular water sports and summer resort area surrounded by spectacular mountain scenery northeast of Logan   Cache Valley  - a scenic mountain valley in Northern Utah, home to Utah State University and blanketed by irrigation-fed agriculture.   Dead Horse Point State Park  - spectacular gorge southwest of Moab where the Colorado River winds through a major bedrock of sandstone   Flaming Gorge  - reservoir north of Vernal, popular for water sports, located in the eastern Uintas   Four Corners  - only place where four states meet, located at southeast corner with Arizona, Colorado, and New Mexico   Goblin Valley  - desert valley with strange formations of sandstone in south-central portion of state  Great Salt Lake - shallow, salty lake in northwestern portion of state northwest of Salt Lake City. The Great Salt Lake Marina, operated as a state park,  Great Salt Lake State Park and Marina  is located on the south shore of the Great Salt Lake, 16 miles west of Salt Lake City along Interstate 80. The Great Salt Lake Marina has 300 slips and is available for year-round boating on the lake that never freezes. Few power boats frequent the lake which makes this large lake with beautiful vistas and expansive night skies an excellent sailing location. The  Great Salt Lake Yacht Club  organizes sailboat races that occur all summer long on Saturday mornings and Wednesday evenings.  Kings Peak - in the Uinta mountain range - the tallest mountain in Utah (13,528 feet)   Kodachrome Basin State Park  - is a small, popular (but very quiet) state park, situated about 20 miles (32 km) southeast of Bryce Canyon National Park, containing multicoloured rock formations     Maple Canyon  ndash; Conglomerate rock climbing area with hiking, camping, and OHV.   Monument Valley  - A  Navajo Nation  Tribal Park boasting the Southwests most famous desert scenery   Palisade State Park  ndash; Golf, Fish, Swim, Canoe, Camp.   Snowkite Skyline Drive  ndash; The newest extreme winter sport.   The Arapeen ATV Trail System  ndash; 350-mile Off-Highway Vehicle Trail System.  Uinta Mountains - large east-west range of the  Rocky Mountains  through northeast portion of state with spectacular mountain climbing and pristine, serene wilderness  Wasatch Mountains - mountain range running through center of state north-south with gorgeous mountain scenery, excellent summer recreational activities, and multiple world-famous ski areas; vibrant fall colors that rival that of New England   Yuba Lake State Park  ndash; Waterski, Fish, and Camp.</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">32022</field>
		<field name="title">Northeast Kingdom</field>
		<field name="main">other destinations</field>
		<field name="name">other destinations</field>
		<field name="content">NEK Border with Canada - including Derby Line   Peacham Village</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">32023</field>
		<field name="title">Volusia County</field>
		<field name="main">other destinations</field>
		<field name="name">other destinations</field>
		<field name="content">Blue Spring    Bulow Creek    Canaveral National Seashore     DeLeon Springs    Lake Woodruff</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">32024</field>
		<field name="title">Ohio</field>
		<field name="main">other destinations</field>
		<field name="name">other destinations</field>
		<field name="content">Cuyahoga Valley National Park  - The only national park in Ohio. According to the US National Park Service, the Cuyahoga Valley is the 5th most frequently visited park in the National Park System.   Lake Erie Islands  - Located north of Sandusky (between Cleveland and Toledo), a group of picturesque and festive islands in Lake Erie are accessible via ferry. In addition to several Ohio State Parks located on the islands, there is plenty to do including visiting wineries, restaurants, bars, marinas and beaches. One of the Islands, Put-In-Bay, is known as the "Key West of the North" for its party atmosphere, especially during the summer months.   North Coast Beaches  - Along the southern shore of Lake Erie are a large number of public beaches.  The largest natural sand beach in Ohio, Headlands Beach State Park, is located east of Cleveland, in Mentor. Cleveland Lakefront State Park also includes a large beach at its Edgewater Park, just west of downtown Cleveland. Many other beaches are available throughout Northern Ohio, including Huntington Beach, Euclid Beach and Fairport Harbor. In addition, Maumee Bay State Park, near Toledo, boasts an extensive Lake Erie Beach as well as an inland beach and various resort and banquet facilities, not to mention a challenging Scottish-links style golf course.   Ohio State Parks  - Ohio has many states parks, spread throughout the state. Fees vary from park to park, but all are very affordable. To the North, the Parks around Lake Erie have some of the best beaches and camping areas. Many have boat launches. Inland, most are in forest areas and offer outstanding amenities to campers, picnickers, boaters and horsemen.   Ohio Prehistoric Sites  -   Wayne National Forest  - Located in the Southeast portion of the state, includes the scenic Hocking Hills region and Lake Logan State Park.   Holmes County  - Located halfway between Columbus and Cleveland, Holmes County is home to the worlds largest population of Amish residents, along with famous attractions like Heinis Cheese, Skyview Ranch, the Amish Door and dozens of other historical Amish attractions.   Warren County  - Warren County, Ohio is the ultimate getaway for Ohio family fun. As the home of attractions such as Kings Island, Great Wolf Lodge, The Beach Waterpark and Ozone Zipline Adventures, Warren County is truly "Ohios Largest Playground".</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">32025</field>
		<field name="title">Mendocino County</field>
		<field name="main">other destinations</field>
		<field name="name">other destinations</field>
		<field name="content">City of Ten Thousand Buddhas - The largest Buddhist temples in the Western Hemisphere over 2,000 acres large, influenced by Chinese, Japanese and Vietnamese architecture. A must see. 4951 Bodhi Way.Ukiah, California 95482(707)462-0939  http://www.drba.org/</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">32026</field>
		<field name="title">Jefferson County (Florida)</field>
		<field name="main">other destinations</field>
		<field name="name">other destinations</field>
		<field name="content">St. Marks National Wildlife Refuge</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">32027</field>
		<field name="title">Delaware County (Ohio)</field>
		<field name="main">other destinations</field>
		<field name="name">other destinations</field>
		<field name="content">Alum Creek State Park, 3615 S. Old State Road,  Delaware , PH:(740)548-4631 or 1-866-644-6727,   . for camping and getaway rental reservations.   Delaware State Park, 5202 U.S. 23 North,  Delaware , PH:740-369-2761,   . 211 electric sites suitable for tents or trailers. Flush toilets, showers, laundry facilities and a dump station. Boat launch, beach, fishing. About 20 miles North of Columbus of SR 23.</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">32028</field>
		<field name="title">Rockland County</field>
		<field name="main">other destinations</field>
		<field name="name">other destinations</field>
		<field name="content">Monsey    Clarkstown</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">32029</field>
		<field name="title">Piedmont (Georgia)</field>
		<field name="main">other destinations</field>
		<field name="name">other destinations</field>
		<field name="content">Lake Lanier Islands</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">32030</field>
		<field name="title">Long Island</field>
		<field name="main">other destinations</field>
		<field name="name">other destinations</field>
		<field name="content">Fire Island National Seashore   The Hamptons   Shelter Island   The North Fork</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">32031</field>
		<field name="title">Bradford County</field>
		<field name="main">other destinations</field>
		<field name="name">other destinations</field>
		<field name="content">Osceola National Forest</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">32032</field>
		<field name="title">Upcountry South Carolina</field>
		<field name="main">other destinations</field>
		<field name="name">other destinations</field>
		<field name="content">Lake Jocassee  Lake Keowee   Devils Fork State Park    Keowee Toxaway State Park    Oconee State Park    Table Rock State Park</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">32033</field>
		<field name="title">Lassen County</field>
		<field name="main">other destinations</field>
		<field name="name">other destinations</field>
		<field name="content">Lassen Volcanic National Park</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">32034</field>
		<field name="title">Hudson County</field>
		<field name="main">other destinations</field>
		<field name="name">other destinations</field>
		<field name="content">Statue of Liberty</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">32035</field>
		<field name="title">Central Florida</field>
		<field name="main">other destinations</field>
		<field name="name">other destinations</field>
		<field name="content">Canaveral National Seashore   Disney World  Merritt Island National Wildlife Refuge - in  Titusville .  Ocala National Forest   Central Florida is home to many natural springs. Many have been incorporated into state parks. The springs are great during the summer months because the water stays at a constant 72 degrees and the water is perfect for cooling off. Many visitors also go to the springs to spot manatees and alligators and to go boating. Some of the more popular natural springs destinations are listed: Alexander Springs - Lake County  Blue Spring  - Volusia County  DeLeon Springs  - Volusia County Juniper Springs - Lake County Rock Springs - Lake County Weeki Wachee Springs - Hernando County Wekiva Springs - Orange County  Zolfo Springs  - Hardee County</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">32036</field>
		<field name="title">Franklin County (Florida)</field>
		<field name="main">other destinations</field>
		<field name="name">other destinations</field>
		<field name="content">Apalachicola National Forest    St. Vincent National Wildlife Refuge</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">32037</field>
		<field name="title">North County (San Diego County)</field>
		<field name="main">other destinations</field>
		<field name="name">other destinations</field>
		<field name="content">Bonsall  Fallbrook  Pala  Ramona   Rancho Santa Fe  Valley Center</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">32038</field>
		<field name="title">New Mexico</field>
		<field name="main">other destinations</field>
		<field name="name">other destinations</field>
		<field name="content">Bandelier National Monument  - Gorgeous canyon scenery and well-preserved ancient cliff-side dwellings.   Carlsbad Caverns National Park  - One of the most famous cave systems in the world, with spectacular underground formations.   Chaco Culture National Historical Park  - Extensive archaeological ruins of a large Ancestral Puebloan culture.   El Malpais National Monument  - Scenic desert landscapes, including ancient lava flows, sandstone cliffs, and caves.    Four Corners Monument  is where Arizona, Colorado, New Mexico, and Utah meet at right angles, though vehicle access is exclusively in New Mexico.   Navajo Nation  - The largest Indian reservation in the country, covering much of Northwestern New Mexico as well as parts of Arizona and Utah.   New Mexico Pueblos  - The 19 Indian Pueblos of New Mexico, each offering unique attractions.   Valles Caldera National Preserve  - A huge volcanic caldera in the middle of the Jemez Mountains; today filled with a lush alpine meadow.   White Sands National Monument  - One of the most spectacular of New Mexico sights, this monument holds a vast gypsum sand dune field.</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">32039</field>
		<field name="title">North Shore (Massachusetts)</field>
		<field name="main">other destinations</field>
		<field name="name">other destinations</field>
		<field name="content">Salisbury Beach State Reservation,    The park is the main day tripper access to the beach at Salisbury. The beach is lifeguard protected from Memorial Day to Labor day, weather permitting. Unless you are staying in the town of Salisbury it is easier to use the park since they offer a large parking area, bathrooms and outdoor showers.  Other draws at the park include a large campground and access to the Merrimack River. The campground is open full-time during the summer, on weekends during the early spring and late fall, and closes in the winter. There is a $7 fee to enter the park in the summer (summer of 2008, may increase in 2009). During the off season there is no fee.</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">32040</field>
		<field name="title">Southern California</field>
		<field name="main">other destinations</field>
		<field name="name">other destinations</field>
		<field name="content">Southern California is home to numerous world-famous attractions including Disneyland, the San Diego Zoo, Legoland, and others.    Disneyland    Knotts Berry Farm    Six Flags Magic Mountain</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">32041</field>
		<field name="title">Orleans County (New York)</field>
		<field name="main">other destinations</field>
		<field name="name">other destinations</field>
		<field name="content">Iroquois National Wildlife Refuge  mdash; also known as the swamp  Lakeside Beach State Park  mdash; fun in the sun  Point Breeze  mdash; the mouth of the Oak Orchard River</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">32042</field>
		<field name="title">Poconos and Endless Mountains</field>
		<field name="main">other destinations</field>
		<field name="name">other destinations</field>
		<field name="content">Bushkill Falls  - is also known as The "Niagara of Pennsylvania".</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">32043</field>
		<field name="title">Sonoma County</field>
		<field name="main">other destinations</field>
		<field name="name">other destinations</field>
		<field name="content">Armstrong Redwoods State Reserve    Sea Ranch    Sugarloaf Ridge State Park    Russian River</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">32044</field>
		<field name="title">Leon County (Florida)</field>
		<field name="main">other destinations</field>
		<field name="name">other destinations</field>
		<field name="content">Apalachicola National Forest  Natural Bridge Battlefield State Historic Site</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">32045</field>
		<field name="title">Warren County (Ohio)</field>
		<field name="main">other destinations</field>
		<field name="name">other destinations</field>
		<field name="content">Caesar Creek State Park - Recreational lake with beaches, boat ramps, hiking trails, and campsites - in  Waynesville</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">32046</field>
		<field name="title">Miami-Dade County</field>
		<field name="main">other destinations</field>
		<field name="name">other destinations</field>
		<field name="content">Bill Baggs Cape Florida State Park occupies approximately the southern third of the island of Key Biscayne. The park is home to the Cape Florida Light, the oldest standing structure in Miami-Dade County. In 2005 it was listed as having the 8th best beach in the country. It has over a mile of sandy Atlantic beachfront, where snorkeling and swimming is possible. Besides the beach and tours of the lighthouse and keepers quarters, activities include boating, canoeing, kayaking and fishing from the seawall along Biscayne Bay, bicycling, hiking and wildlife viewing. The park has such amenities as picnicking areas and youth camping. It also has a visitor center, a museum with interpretive exhibits and concessions.  Biscayne National Park</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">32047</field>
		<field name="title">Geauga County</field>
		<field name="main">other destinations</field>
		<field name="name">other destinations</field>
		<field name="content">Punderson State Park, 11755 Kinsman Rd., Newbury. Natural lake, resort manor house, family cottages, golf course, winter sports park, sledding, snowmobiling,  cross-country skiing, 196-site campground, showerhouses, flush toilets, electricity, pet camping, twenty-six cottages,  manor house features a dining room, meeting rooms, outdoor, indoor swimming pools,  championship-rated, 18-hole public golf course, pro shop, boat rentals, fishing, fourteen miles of hiking trails, tennis court, volleyball, basketball courts and cross country ski trails</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">32048</field>
		<field name="title">Washington (state)</field>
		<field name="main">other destinations</field>
		<field name="name">other destinations</field>
		<field name="content">Ruby Beach Olympic National Park     Ebeys Landing National Historical Reserve  preserves and protects an unbroken historical record of Puget Sound exploration and settlement from the 19th century to the present. Historic farms, still under cultivation in the prairies of Whidbey Island, reveal land use patterns unchanged since settlers claimed the land in the 1850s.  Lewis and Clark National Historic Trail  - Between May 1804 and September 1806, 32 men, one woman, and a baby traveled from the plains of the Midwest to the shores of the Pacific Ocean. They called themselves the Corps of Discovery.  Mount Rainier National Park  - a 14,410 feet volcano. Contains more snow and ice than all other Cascade range volcanos combined, and is the most "prominent" mountain in the lower 48 states.  Mount St. Helens National Volcanic Monument  - At 8:32 Sunday morning, May 18, 1980, Mount St. Helens erupted and life in the area was altered for better and for worse  North Cascades National Park  - Home to 50% of all glaciers in the lower 48 states  Olympic National Park  - Temperate rain forest, rugged Olympic Mountains and wild coastline, this is the only UNESCO World Heritage site in the Pacific Northwest.  San Juan Islands  — located in the rain shadow of the Olympic Mountains in  Puget Sound  these islands are famous for abundant eagles and Orca whales and includes the newly formed  San Juan Islands National Monument  as well as the  San Juan Island National Historical Park .   Sun Lakes-Dry Falls State Park  - An overlook where you can see the remains of the end of the last ice age where a flow of up to 10 times of all the present-day rivers of the world merged into a huge waterfall. While not as deep as the Grand Canyon, you can get dizzyingly close to the edge.   Washington Coast  - scenic, wild and interspersed with quaint towns the coast includes 100 km of wilderness coastline, the longest undeveloped coast in the contiguous United States.  Itineraries  The North Cascade Loop  is a very scenic drive that loops around this area through pristine mountains, grand rivers, crystalline lakes and scenic islands. If you cant do the loop, at least go as far as Mazama (eastbound) or the visitor center near Newhalem (westbound) on State Hwy 20. Note the most spectacular parts of the drive are not where the highway is sandwiched between the two halves of the national park, but further east in the Okanogan National Forest. Washington Pass is the highest point at 5,477 feet. As the park has virtually no roads, non-hikers should stay on the main highway unless clearly marked signs are visible (such as the visitor center which is about a mile to the south).</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">32049</field>
		<field name="title">Union County (Georgia)</field>
		<field name="main">other destinations</field>
		<field name="name">other destinations</field>
		<field name="content">Vogel State Park</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">32050</field>
		<field name="title">Metro New York</field>
		<field name="main">other destinations</field>
		<field name="name">other destinations</field>
		<field name="content">Coney Island    Fire Island  - An all pedestrian summer resort island located off the coast of Long Island with  Fire Island National Seashore    Gateway National Recreation Area  - With portions in  Brooklyn ,  Queens ,  Staten Island , and  Sandy Hook , this collection of parkland is home to wondrous views of nature and many family activities.   The Hamptons    Montauk    The Palisades  - Majestic cliffs rising sharply on the western bank of the Hudson River with numerous viewpoints, trails and camp sites.   Rye  - Home to Rye Playland, the countrys only government-owned amusement park.   Shelter Island    Times Square</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">32051</field>
		<field name="title">Idaho</field>
		<field name="main">other destinations</field>
		<field name="name">other destinations</field>
		<field name="content">Custer Ghost Town   Sun Valley  -- the first great ski resort in the U.S.  Craters of the Moon National Monument  -- volcanic park with vast fields of seemingly lifeless lava, fun lava tubes to explore Frank Church  River of No Return Wilderness  -- follows the Snake River through Hells Canyon (as deep as 9,300 feet, much deeper than the  Grand Canyon ) north towards Lewiston, where the Clearwater and Snake River meet  Yellowstone National Park  -- The worlds oldest national park and home to the largest concentration of mammals in the lower 48 states is mostly within Wyoming, but the most notable feature, Old Faithful is probably most easily reached from  Idaho Falls  via  West Yellowstone ,  Montana  - though the park road is only open to cars in summer (May to early November) but open to snow vehicles during winter months. The Nez Perce Indian Reservation, home to Native Americans whose forebears helped Lewis and Clark through the winter during their expedition, is just East of Lewiston.   City of Rocks National Reserve  -- Located on the southern edge of the state. Popular with hikers and rock climbers for its maze of massive boulders (some over 100 meters in height).  Lewis and Clark National Historic Trail  - Between May 1804 and September 1806, 32 men, one woman, and a baby traveled from the plains of the Midwest to the shores of the Pacific Ocean. They called themselves the Corps of Discovery.  Sawtooth National Recreation Area  Largest national recreation area in the United States</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">32052</field>
		<field name="title">Michigan</field>
		<field name="main">other destinations</field>
		<field name="name">other destinations</field>
		<field name="content">Isle Royale National Park    Keweenaw Peninsula  mdash; Former Copper mining region, known for history, bird migrations, rock collecting, winter sports.    Mackinac Island    Pictured Rocks National Lakeshore  mdash; Near Munising in the Upper Peninsula.   Sleeping Bear Dunes National Lakeshore</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">32053</field>
		<field name="title">Summit County (Ohio)</field>
		<field name="main">other destinations</field>
		<field name="name">other destinations</field>
		<field name="content">Portage Lakes State Park, 5031 Manchester Rd.,  Akron . 74 non-electric campsites, 400 horsepower limit on lake,  8 boat launch ramps, boat rentals, fishing, hunting, beach, five miles of hiking trails, volleyball courts, horseshoe pits, basketball court, hunting waterfowl in designated areas.   Cuyahoga Valley National Park</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">32054</field>
		<field name="title">Ventura County</field>
		<field name="main">other destinations</field>
		<field name="name">other destinations</field>
		<field name="content">Channel Islands   Channel Islands National Park</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">32055</field>
		<field name="title">Humboldt County</field>
		<field name="main">other destinations</field>
		<field name="name">other destinations</field>
		<field name="content">Redwood National Park   Patricks Point State Park</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">32056</field>
		<field name="title">Kentucky</field>
		<field name="main">other destinations</field>
		<field name="name">other destinations</field>
		<field name="content">Big South Fork National River and Recreation Area    Cumberland Gap National Historical Park    Daniel Boone National Forest    Kentucky Bourbon Trail    Kentucky Lake    Kentucky State Parks    Land Between the Lakes National Recreation Area    Lake Barkley    Mammoth Cave National Park</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">32057</field>
		<field name="title">Martin County (Florida)</field>
		<field name="main">other destinations</field>
		<field name="name">other destinations</field>
		<field name="content">Jonathan Dickinson State Park is a large and varied state park between Hobe Sound and Jupiter.  Great place to see natural Floridas grasslands, woodlands, mangrove forest, and swamp.  A 4-hour kayak trip or 2-hour pontoon boat tour to Trapper Nelsons Cabin is well worth your while, as is the much easier stroll up Hobe Mountain, the highest point in Florida south of Lake Okeechobee.</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">32058</field>
		<field name="title">Mariposa County</field>
		<field name="main">other destinations</field>
		<field name="name">other destinations</field>
		<field name="content">Yosemite National Park</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">32059</field>
		<field name="title">Central Coast (California)</field>
		<field name="main">other destinations</field>
		<field name="name">other destinations</field>
		<field name="content">Pinnacles National Park . Rising out of the chaparral-covered Gabilan Mountains, east of central Californias Salinas Valley, are the spectacular remains of an ancient volcano. Massive monoliths, spires, sheer-walled canyons and talus passages define millions of years of erosion, faulting and tectonic plate movement.</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">32060</field>
		<field name="title">Morris County (New Jersey)</field>
		<field name="main">other destinations</field>
		<field name="name">other destinations</field>
		<field name="content">Chatham</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">32061</field>
		<field name="title">St. Lucie County</field>
		<field name="main">other destinations</field>
		<field name="name">other destinations</field>
		<field name="content">Avalon State Park is a Florida State Park, located on North Hutchinson Island, 4 miles north of Fort Pierce Inlet State Park, along A1A.</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">32062</field>
		<field name="title">Crawford County</field>
		<field name="main">other destinations</field>
		<field name="name">other destinations</field>
		<field name="content">Mid-Ohio Sports Car Track,  7721 Steam Corners Road,  Lexington , E-Mail:postmaster@midohio.com, PH:Phone: 1-800-MID-OHIO,   .</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">32063</field>
		<field name="title">North Fork</field>
		<field name="main">other destinations</field>
		<field name="name">other destinations</field>
		<field name="content">The South Fork or the Hamptons and Montauk point are just south of the North Fork. It is an easy drive of easier to take a small ferry to Shelter Island, drive through to the next ferry to Sag Habor and explore there as well.  Heading west from the North Fork, you can visit Long Island and head further west to New York City.  Long Island has many enjoyable places to visit, including nice villages. Beautiful ocean beaches, restaurants, and tours are available of  Gold Coast Mansions , that dotted the coast during the era of the Great Gatsby. For groups of 50 or more tour guides are available. If small groups, you can visit the mansions online and check for events and availability.  Staying in the North Fork or returning if a long trip there are many things to do. Mostily it is a quiet place and relaxation and tranquility along with a picturesque setting are part of what makes the North Fork an enjoyable destination.</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">32064</field>
		<field name="title">Skylands</field>
		<field name="main">other destinations</field>
		<field name="name">other destinations</field>
		<field name="content">Delaware Water Gap National Recreation Area  — beautiful park on the river for camping, hiking, tubing, canoeing, more  Lake Hopatcong — the largest body of fresh water in New Jersey: fishing, boating, ice skating, more.</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">32065</field>
		<field name="title">Escambia County (Florida)</field>
		<field name="main">other destinations</field>
		<field name="name">other destinations</field>
		<field name="content">Big Lagoon State Park is a 733-acre (2.97 km2) Florida State Park located on the northwestern Florida coast, approximately 10 miles southwest of Pensacola on Gulf Beach Highway. It encompasses the northern boundary of Big Lagoon as it snakes toward Pensacola Bay to the east. Wild Grande Lagoon and its minor tributaries lay within the boundaries of the park, as does the alligator-inhabited Long Pond that covers a coastal slough. The park is a "gateway site" for the Great Florida Birding Trail. It features four distinct natural communities including estuarine tidal marsh, mesic flatwoods, wet flatwoods, and is dominated by coastal scrub. The park features a number of threatened and endangered species such as the Eastern Indigo Snake, Gopher Tortoise, migratory shorebirds such as Snowy Plover, Least Tern among some twenty other listed species. The park has such amenities as beaches along the shoreline of Big Lagoon, bicycling down the 2.6 mile park drive, boating from a 40-slip boat ramp, canoeing along Big Lagoon, fishing, hiking along 4 miles of trails, kayaking in Grande Lagoon, wildlife viewing from a four story observation tower and footbridge overlooks at Long Pond and Grande Lagoon, picnicking at 21 shelters, swimming in Big Lagoon and 75 electrified camping sites and a group camp.  Escambia Bay  Fort Pickens   Gulf Islands National Seashore   Fort McRee  Naval Air Station Pensacola  Perdido Key State Park</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">32066</field>
		<field name="title">Arizona</field>
		<field name="main">other destinations</field>
		<field name="name">other destinations</field>
		<field name="content">Meteor Crater    Mogollon Rim    Monument Valley    Mount Humphries  - San Francisco Peaks   Mount Lemmon    Mystery Castle    Navajo Nation    Painted Desert    Tombstone    White Mountains</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">32067</field>
		<field name="title">North Bay (Bay Area)</field>
		<field name="main">other destinations</field>
		<field name="name">other destinations</field>
		<field name="content">Point Reyes National Seashore  - From its thunderous ocean breakers crashing against rocky headlands and expansive sand beaches through its open grasslands to its brushy hillsides and forested ridges, visitors can discover over 1000 species of plants and animals. Home to several cultures over thousands of years, Point Reyes preserves a tapestry of stories and interactions of people.</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">32068</field>
		<field name="title">Santa Clara County</field>
		<field name="main">other destinations</field>
		<field name="name">other destinations</field>
		<field name="content">Cordevalle, One CordeValle Club Drive, San Martin, Tel (408) 695-4563,   . This Northern California luxury resort is located in the bay area’s wine country. The resort offers a full-service spa, golf course, and a wine vineyard on site.</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">32069</field>
		<field name="title">Fairfield County (Ohio)</field>
		<field name="main">other destinations</field>
		<field name="name">other destinations</field>
		<field name="content">Buckeye Lake Hocking Hills</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">32070</field>
		<field name="title">Prairies and Lakes</field>
		<field name="main">other destinations</field>
		<field name="name">other destinations</field>
		<field name="content">Dinosaur Valley State Park  Fort Worth Nature Center Refuge</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">32071</field>
		<field name="title">San Juan Islands</field>
		<field name="main">other destinations</field>
		<field name="name">other destinations</field>
		<field name="content">Orcas Island , with Eastsound Village, Orcas Village, and Mount Constitution  San Juan Island , with the towns of  Friday Harbor  and  Roche Harbor   Lopez Island   Shaw Island    Blakely Island   Waldron Island   Decatur Island   Stuart Island</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">32072</field>
		<field name="title">Franklin County (Ohio)</field>
		<field name="main">other destinations</field>
		<field name="name">other destinations</field>
		<field name="content">Battelle Darby Creek ,  Southwestern Franklin County. 6,600 acre park along the Big and Little Darby creeks. Cross-country skiing, Hiking trails, Pet trail, Picnicking, Canoeing, Fishing, Hunting, Ice-skating, Nature programs.    Franklin County Metro-Parks  Open daily, no admission charge, Wild Places and Open Spaces, one of Central Ohio’s largest landowners with fifteen parks, conveniently located throughout the area. Miles of trails through beautiful prairies, forests or wetlands. 2,200 species of plants and animals.</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">32073</field>
		<field name="title">Frederick County</field>
		<field name="main">other destinations</field>
		<field name="name">other destinations</field>
		<field name="content">Catoctin Mountain Park</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">32074</field>
		<field name="title">Eastern Shore (Maryland)</field>
		<field name="main">other destinations</field>
		<field name="name">other destinations</field>
		<field name="content">Assateague Island  — a true gem of the East Coast shoreline; a barrier island with a beautiful beach, wild ponies, and nature trails through the bayside wetlands.  Chesapeake Bay  — the Great Shellfish Bay, and the source of Marylands maritime and seafood culture.  Hoopers Island  — a quiet collection of three tiny islands home to fishing communties and the historic Hoopers Island Lighthouse.  Kent Island  — a pretty island off the Bay Bridge, home to historic Stevensville.  Smith Island  — a watermen island long lost in time, with nary a car to its name.</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">32075</field>
		<field name="title">Green County</field>
		<field name="main">other destinations</field>
		<field name="name">Edelweiss Chalet Country Club</field>
		<field name="directions">From WI 69 in New Glarus take Elmer Road south</field>
		<field name="phone">+1 608  527-2315</field>
		<field name="address">W4764 Edelweiss Rd, New Glarus, WI</field>
		<field name="url">http://www.edelweissccc.com</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">32076</field>
		<field name="title">Gulf County</field>
		<field name="main">other destinations</field>
		<field name="name">other destinations</field>
		<field name="content">St. Vincent National Wildlife Refuge</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">32077</field>
		<field name="title">Monmouth County</field>
		<field name="main">other destinations</field>
		<field name="name">other destinations</field>
		<field name="content">Gateway National Recreation Area  — The  Sandy Hook  section is in Monmouth County.</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">32078</field>
		<field name="title">Southern Delaware</field>
		<field name="main">other destinations</field>
		<field name="name">other destinations</field>
		<field name="content">Dewey Beach</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">32079</field>
		<field name="title">Kiamichi Country</field>
		<field name="main">other destinations</field>
		<field name="name">other destinations</field>
		<field name="content">Talimena Drive in the fall   Talimena Drive  from  Talihina ,  Oklahoma  to  Mena ,  Arkansas  54 Mile scenic drive in Oklahoma and Arkansas along the ridge of the Ouachita Mountains and the Ouachita National Forest. Ouachita Mountains (pronounced "wah-shi-tah") Located in west central  Arkansas  and southeastern  Oklahoma</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">32080</field>
		<field name="title">Inland (San Diego County)</field>
		<field name="main">other destinations</field>
		<field name="name">other destinations</field>
		<field name="content">Borrego Springs Campo Jacumba Jamul  Julian  Lakeside Pine Valley Spring Valley</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">32081</field>
		<field name="title">Erie County (Ohio)</field>
		<field name="main">other destinations</field>
		<field name="name">other destinations</field>
		<field name="content">Cedar Point   Kelleys Island</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">32082</field>
		<field name="title">Saratoga County</field>
		<field name="main">other destinations</field>
		<field name="name">other destinations</field>
		<field name="content">Saratoga Spa State Park</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">32083</field>
		<field name="title">New England</field>
		<field name="main">other destinations</field>
		<field name="name">other destinations</field>
		<field name="content">Acadia National Park  — a  United States National Park  attracting nearly 3 million visitors per year.  Block Island  — an island off the southern coast of Rhode Island. This island packs great scenery and great beaches into a small, walkable and bikable area.   Boston Harbor Islands  — a group of thirty-four islands in Massachusetts.  Cape Cod National Seashore   Green Mountains   White Mountain National Forest</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">32084</field>
		<field name="title">South Carolina</field>
		<field name="main">other destinations</field>
		<field name="name">other destinations</field>
		<field name="content">Edisto Island  - Natural and uncommercialized, Edisto Island is just 45 minutes south of Charleston, with moss-covered oak trees, creeks, and sandy beaches.    Hilton Head Island    Congaree National Park    Seabrook Island    Isle of Palms    Beaufort  - The Queen of the Sea Islands is 300 years old, as of 2011</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">32085</field>
		<field name="title">Washtenaw County</field>
		<field name="main">other destinations</field>
		<field name="name">other destinations</field>
		<field name="content">Northwestern Washtenaw County is home to the Waterloo State Recreation Area and the Pinckney State Recreation Area, both large parks with several popular recreational lakes, like Silver Lake and Bruin Lake.   The Huron River flows through  Dexter ,  Ann Arbor  and  Ypsilanti  on its way to Lake Erie.</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">32086</field>
		<field name="title">Orange County (California)</field>
		<field name="main">other destinations</field>
		<field name="name">other destinations</field>
		<field name="content">Caspers Wilderness Park   Fullerton Arboretum</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">32087</field>
		<field name="title">Palouse (Washington)</field>
		<field name="main">other destinations</field>
		<field name="name">other destinations</field>
		<field name="content">Nez Perce National Historical Park  - Since time immemorial, the Nimiipuu or Nez Perce have lived among the rivers, canyons and prairies of the inland northwest    Hooper  — Once thriving, now a ghost town.  It was built by the McGregor Company based on the sheep-raising industry. In Whitman County, on the Palouse River just south of Highway 26, between  Washtucna  and  Pampa .</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">32088</field>
		<field name="title">Hamilton County (Florida)</field>
		<field name="main">other destinations</field>
		<field name="name">other destinations</field>
		<field name="content">Big Shoals State Park is a Florida State Park, located on County Road 135, approximately a mile east of White Springs, off US 41. This park features the largest whitewater rapids in Florida. Limestone bluffs, towering 80 feet above the banks of the Suwannee River, afford outstanding vistas not found anywhere else in Florida. When the water level on the Suwannee River is between 59 and 61 feet above mean sea level, the Big Shoals rapids earn a Class III Whitewater classification, attracting thrill-seeking canoe and kayak enthusiasts. A smaller set of rapids downstream is called Little Shoals. Over 28 miles of wooded trails provide opportunities for hiking, biking, horseback riding, and wildlife viewing. The Woodpecker Trail, a 3.4 mile long multipurpose paved trail, connects the Little Shoals and Big Shoals entrances to the park. The river offers excellent opportunities for freshwater fishing. A picnic pavilion that seats up to 40 people is available at the Little Shoals entrance.   Osceola National Forest</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">32089</field>
		<field name="title">West Virginia</field>
		<field name="main">other destinations</field>
		<field name="name">other destinations</field>
		<field name="content">Blackwater Falls State Park  — the most photographed location in West Virginia, running through a gorge along the Blackwater River.   Monongahela National Forest  — over 919,000 acres of forest stretching from near  Elkins  to  Richwood .   New River Gorge National River    Coopers Rock State Forest</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">32090</field>
		<field name="title">Georgia (state)</field>
		<field name="main">other destinations</field>
		<field name="name">other destinations</field>
		<field name="content">Stone Mountain    Amicalola Falls    Appalachian National Scenic Trail    Cumberland Island National Seashore     Okefenokee National Wildlife Refuge    Oconee National Forest    Jekyll Island    Lake Chatuge    Saint Simons Island    Stone Mountain</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">32091</field>
		<field name="title">San Benito County</field>
		<field name="main">other destinations</field>
		<field name="name">other destinations</field>
		<field name="content">Pinnacles National Park</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">32092</field>
		<field name="title">Oregon</field>
		<field name="main">other destinations</field>
		<field name="name">other destinations</field>
		<field name="content">California National Historical Trail  — The road to California carried over 250,000 gold-seekers farmers to the gold fields rich farmlands of California during the 1840s and 1850s as well as those who choose to head north to the Oregon Territory  Crater Lake National Park  — Deepest lake in the world above sea level, Oregons only national park  Lewis and Clark National Monument  — 12 park sites located on a 40-mile stretch of the Pacific coast located at the western end of the Lewis Clark National Historic Trail  Mount Bachelor  — skiing and snowboarding (November through May)  Mount Hood  — snowboarding skiing (lift serviced year round), snowshoeing, alpine slides, hiking, backpacking, camping  Painted Hills  — Part of John Day Fossil Beds National Monument, 75 Miles East of Bend, approximately 1000 Ha, 3132 Acres, one of the most photographed areas in Oregon. Colors change as the sun moves in the sky, making an extended visit quite worthwhile. Brilliant yellow wildflowers bloom in rivers of color down the "valleys" of the hillsides in late April/early May.  Oregon National Historical Trail  — As the harbinger of Americas westward expansion, the Oregon Trail was the pathway to the Pacific for fur traders, gold seekers, missionaries and others.  Willamette National Forest  — Offering numerous outdoor recreation activities including hiking, sailing, and camping at  Waldo Lake .  Wallowa Lake  — One of Oregons finest lakes.  Beautiful scenery, camping, boating, fishing, hiking, eating, and lodging in the quiet town of  Joseph .  Silver Falls State Park  — Located 26 miles East of Salem this state park has 10 waterfalls.  Take the canyon trail on a 6.9 mile hike and see all 10.  For a shorter hike take the shortcut and see 8 waterfalls in a 5.1 mile loop.</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">32093</field>
		<field name="title">Holmes County (Florida)</field>
		<field name="main">other destinations</field>
		<field name="name">other destinations</field>
		<field name="content">Ponce de Leon Springs State Recreation Area</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">32094</field>
		<field name="title">Keweenaw Peninsula</field>
		<field name="main">other destinations</field>
		<field name="name">other destinations</field>
		<field name="content">Munising, MI Escanaba, MI</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">32095</field>
		<field name="title">Walton County (Florida)</field>
		<field name="main">other destinations</field>
		<field name="name">other destinations</field>
		<field name="content">Choctawhatchee National Forest  Deer Lake State Park  Eden Gardens State Park - A 115 acre Florida State Park and historic site located in Point Washington, south of Freeport, off U.S. 98 on CR 395, in northwestern Florida.  Grayton Beach State Park  Topsail Hill Preserve State Park</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">32096</field>
		<field name="title">Northern Oregon Coast</field>
		<field name="main">other destinations</field>
		<field name="name">other destinations</field>
		<field name="content">Tillamook State Forest</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">32097</field>
		<field name="title">Bay County (Florida)</field>
		<field name="main">other destinations</field>
		<field name="name">other destinations</field>
		<field name="content">Apalachicola National Forest  Camp Helen State Park is a Florida State Park and historic site located west of Panama City Beach, in northwestern Florida. The park is south of U.S. 98, and bounded by the Gulf of Mexico and Lake Powell (one of the largest coastal dune lakes in the state). The park has such amenities as beaches, birding, beachcombing, boating, canoeing, fishing, hiking, kayaking, picnicking areas, swimming and wildlife viewing. It also has a visitor center and an interpretive exhibit.  Museum Of Man In The Sea  St. Andrews State Park  SS Tarpon (Shipwreck)  Vamar Shipwreck Site</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">32098</field>
		<field name="title">Nebraska</field>
		<field name="main">other destinations</field>
		<field name="name">other destinations</field>
		<field name="content">Pine Ridge ndash; a historic region of pine forests, rugged buttes and  badlands  formations in the northwest corner of the state.    Sand Hills  are the largest formation of sand dunes in the western hemisphere, and the largest area of grass-stabilized dunes in the world.  The Sand Hills encompass 19,300 square miles, or about 12.75 million acres.  The dunes can be as high as 400 feet and stretch for 20 miles, with slopes as steep as 25%.  The area is sparsely populated, with widely spaced ranches and small towns.   Western Foothills - large expanse of steep forested buttes that rise over flat valleys covering the most western part of the state (generally called the "Panhandle"). They are the transition point from plains to mountains, hence the name Foothills.   Metropolitan contains Omaha, Lincoln, and other large cities in between the two, and is located in east-central Nebraska. Includes many attractions, mostly city attractions, such as entertainment, dining, museums, and more.   Lewis Clark National Historic Trail  - Between May 1804 and September 1806, 32 men, one woman, and a baby traveled from the plains of the Midwest to the shores of the Pacific Ocean. They called themselves the Corps of Discovery.</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">32099</field>
		<field name="title">Mojave Desert</field>
		<field name="main">other destinations</field>
		<field name="name">other destinations</field>
		<field name="content">Edwards Air Force Base is in the western Mojave.  The airfield is used for aircraft testing; it is also an alternate landing spot for the Space Shuttle.  Aircraft designer Burt Rutan operates out of Mojave but occasionally uses the long runways at Edwards for testing or noteworthy flights such as the Voyager around-the-world.</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">32100</field>
		<field name="title">Kenai Peninsula</field>
		<field name="main">other destinations</field>
		<field name="name">other destinations</field>
		<field name="content">Kenai Fjords National Park   Kachemak Bay State Park   Chugach National Forest   Kenai National Wildlife Refuge</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">32101</field>
		<field name="title">Allegany County (Maryland)</field>
		<field name="main">other destinations</field>
		<field name="name">other destinations</field>
		<field name="content">Chesapeake and Ohio Canal National Historic Park   Rocky Gap State Park  — a state park with a popular lake for boating and fishing, a large lodge-style resort, and golf course.  Green Ridge State Forest</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">32102</field>
		<field name="title">Hancock County (Maine)</field>
		<field name="main">other destinations</field>
		<field name="name">other destinations</field>
		<field name="content">Acadia National Park    Deer Isle</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">32103</field>
		<field name="title">Acadiana</field>
		<field name="main">other destinations</field>
		<field name="name">other destinations</field>
		<field name="content">Arnaudville    Avery Island    Eunice    LaPlace    Mamou    New Roads  River Road Plantation Country</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">32104</field>
		<field name="title">Mercer County (New Jersey)</field>
		<field name="main">other destinations</field>
		<field name="name">other destinations</field>
		<field name="content">Hightstown   Bordentown</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">32105</field>
		<field name="title">Flagler County</field>
		<field name="main">other destinations</field>
		<field name="name">other destinations</field>
		<field name="content">Bulow Plantation Ruins State Historic Site is a Florida State Park in Flagler Beach, Florida. It is three miles west of Flagler Beach on CR 2001, south of SR 100, and contains the ruins of an ante-bellum plantation. Among the wildlife of the park are Bald Eagles, Swallow-tailed Kites, and Florida manatees. Activities include hiking, fishing, wildlife viewing, canoeing and kayaking, and picnicking. Amenities include a 6.8 mile hiking trail, a boat ramp, and a screened picnic pavilion. Bulow Creek is recognized as a State Canoe Trail.  Gamble Rogers Memorial State Recreation Area in  Flagler Beach   Washington Oaks State Gardens near Palm Coast, along Highway A1A. This park is famous for its formal gardens, but it also preserves the original habitat of a northeast Florida barrier island.</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">32106</field>
		<field name="title">Nassau County (Florida)</field>
		<field name="main">other destinations</field>
		<field name="name">other destinations</field>
		<field name="content">Amelia Island State Recreation Area is a Florida State Park located 7 miles (11 km) north of Little Talbot Island State Park on SR A1A, and 8 miles (13 km) south of Fernandina Beach on Amelia Island, Florida. The park consists of 200 acres (0.81 sq km) of beaches, salt marshes and coastal maritime forests. Activities include fishing, hiking, sunning, watching wildlife, and horseback riding. 45-minute horseback tours along the shoreline are given four times daily. The park is open from 8AM till sundown year round.  Big Talbot Island State Park is a Florida State Park located on Big Talbot Island, 20 miles east of downtown Jacksonville on A1A North and immediately north of Little Talbot Island State Park. The park is a nature preserve and a location for nature study, bird–watching, or photography. Other activities include hiking, bicycling, fishing, boating, canoeing, and kayaking, and picnicking. Amenities include picnic pavilions, nature trails, a fishing pier, a boat ramp, bike trails and beaches. The park is open from 8AM till sundown year round.  Little Talbot Island State Park is a Florida State Park located on Little Talbot Island, 17 miles northeast of Jacksonville on State Road A1A. The park covers the entire 2,500 acre island. Big Talbot Island State Park lies to the immediate north. The park contains maritime forests, dunes, and salt marshes on the western side of the island. Wild life includes river otters, marsh rabbits, bobcats, and a variety of native and migrating birds. Activities include camping, fishing, hiking, swimming, canoeing, nature watching and surfing. Amenities include a full–facility campground, as well as a youth/group tent campground and beachside picnic pavilions. The park also has bath houses, a small boat ramp, a nature trail, and a playground. Bicycles and canoes can be rented at at the campground. The park is open from 8AM till dark.</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">32107</field>
		<field name="title">Oklahoma</field>
		<field name="main">other destinations</field>
		<field name="name">other destinations</field>
		<field name="content">Great Salt Plains State Park  Northwest of  Enid  and near  Jet . Dig for Selenite crystals.  The Oklahoma Space Port  at  Burns Flat</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">32108</field>
		<field name="title">Southeast Arizona</field>
		<field name="main">other destinations</field>
		<field name="name">other destinations</field>
		<field name="content">Chiricahua National Monument</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">32109</field>
		<field name="title">Columbia County (Florida)</field>
		<field name="main">other destinations</field>
		<field name="name">other destinations</field>
		<field name="content">Osceola National Forest</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">32110</field>
		<field name="title">Santa Clarita Valley</field>
		<field name="main">other destinations</field>
		<field name="name">other destinations</field>
		<field name="content">Angeles National Forest    Six Flags Magic Mountain</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">32111</field>
		<field name="title">Panhandle (Texas)</field>
		<field name="main">other destinations</field>
		<field name="name">other destinations</field>
		<field name="content">Palo Duro Canyon   Caprock Canyons State Park  Buffalo Springs Lake Lake Meredith Lake Ransom Canyon Lake Alan Henry</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">32112</field>
		<field name="title">El Dorado County</field>
		<field name="main">other destinations</field>
		<field name="name">other destinations</field>
		<field name="content">Lake Tahoe</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">32113</field>
		<field name="title">Clermont County</field>
		<field name="main">other destinations</field>
		<field name="name">other destinations</field>
		<field name="content">East Fork State Park,  25 miles east of  Cincinnati  and south of SR 32, off of Route 133. 384 electric campsites, 5 full-hookup sites, showers, flush toilets, drinking water, campers beach, boat ramp, pet camping, 4 spacious Cedar Cabins, 4 camper cabins, horsemens camp.  Backpacker trail, 10 miles of scenic areas,  20-mile round trip. 32-mile perimeter trail circles the park, for hikers, backpackers, and horsemen. Four primitive campsites are these trails. 5-mile mountain bike trail. 2,160 acres of water, unlimited horsepower boating, six launch ramps. Hunting, fishing, picnic areas, tables, grills, drinking water, two picnic shelters, swimming, 1,200-foot beach, change booths, restrooms, vending area, mini-golf course, bike rental, basketball, horseshoe courts, and playgrounds.</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">32114</field>
		<field name="title">Emerald Coast</field>
		<field name="main">other destinations</field>
		<field name="name">other destinations</field>
		<field name="content">Choctawhatchee National Forest    Gulf Islands National Seashore</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">32115</field>
		<field name="title">Catskills</field>
		<field name="main">other destinations</field>
		<field name="name">other destinations</field>
		<field name="content">Shawangunk Ridge</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">32116</field>
		<field name="title">Mississippi</field>
		<field name="main">other destinations</field>
		<field name="name">other destinations</field>
		<field name="content">Gulf Islands National Seashore    Natchez Trace Parkway  - This 444 mile long parkway is administered by the National Park Service and follows a route from  Natchez  to  Nashville  that dates back hundreds of years. Hiking, Indian mounds, natural history exhibits, and interpretive exhibits make this is leisurely and enjoyable route for motorists.  The city of  Corinth : A historic town with many shopping areas and things to see. It is also a battleground area, for the Battle of Corinth happened here.  Mississippi State University</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">32117</field>
		<field name="title">Florida Keys</field>
		<field name="main">other destinations</field>
		<field name="name">other destinations</field>
		<field name="content">Biscayne National Park</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">32118</field>
		<field name="title">San Luis Obispo County</field>
		<field name="main">other destinations</field>
		<field name="name">other destinations</field>
		<field name="content">Carrizo Plain National Monument</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">32119</field>
		<field name="title">Burlington County</field>
		<field name="main">other destinations</field>
		<field name="name">other destinations</field>
		<field name="content">Cinnaminson</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">32120</field>
		<field name="title">Southcentral Alaska</field>
		<field name="main">other destinations</field>
		<field name="name">other destinations</field>
		<field name="content">Kenai Fjords National Park  - at Kenai Fjords, glaciers, earthquakes, and ocean storms are the architects.  Wrangell-St. Elias National Park and Preserve  - the continents largest assemblage of glaciers and greatest collection of peaks above 16,000 feet  Chugach National Forest  - the second largest forest in the country and home to a network of trails for hiking and mt. biking.</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">32121</field>
		<field name="title">Montana</field>
		<field name="main">other destinations</field>
		<field name="name">other destinations</field>
		<field name="content">Montana public lands map     Bighorn Canyon National Recreation Area    Glacier National Park      Pompeys Pillar National Monumen t  Large Rock where Captain Clark of Lewis and Clark signed his name (as the Expedition had split to cover more ground).   Little Bighorn Battlefield National Monument . Custers Last Stand battlefield and Reenactment location  Lewis and Clark National Historic Trail  - Between May 1804 and September 1806, 32 men, one woman, and a baby traveled from the plains of the Midwest to the shores of the Pacific Ocean. They called themselves the Corps of Discovery.   Yellowstone National Park  mdash; Majority located within Wyoming, however three entrances to the park are located in Montana. :  Livingston  mdash; The Park County seat; at the turnoff to Yellowstone National Park. :  Gardiner  mdash; The original and only all year entrance to Yellowstone National Park. :  Cooke City  mdash; Near the Northeast entrance to Yellowstone National Park. :  Silver Gate  mdash; Near the Northeast entrance to Yellowstone National Park. :  West Yellowstone  mdash; West entrance to Yellowstone National Park.</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">32122</field>
		<field name="title">Wisconsin</field>
		<field name="main">other destinations</field>
		<field name="name">other destinations</field>
		<field name="content">Apostle Islands National Lakeshore - Wild Beauty on Lake Superior   Ice Age National Scenic Trail  - hiking trail that spans the entire state   Wisconsin Dells  - Family tourist destination   Door County  - "Cape Cod" of the Midwest</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">32123</field>
		<field name="title">Collier County</field>
		<field name="main">other destinations</field>
		<field name="name">other destinations</field>
		<field name="content">Collier-Seminole State Park is a Florida State Park located on US 41, 17 miles (27 km) south of Naples, Florida. The park is the home of a National Historic Mechanical Engineering Landmark, the Bay City Walking Dredge used to build the Tamiami Trail through the Everglades. The park includes of 6,430 acres (26 km2) of mangrove swamp, cypress swamps, salt marshes, mangrove river estuaries, and pine flatwoods. Among the wildlife of the park are alligators, raccoons, ospreys, and white ibis. Brown Pelicans, Wood storks, bald eagles, red-cockaded woodpeckers, crocodiles, Florida black bears and big cypress fox squirrels also inhabit the park. Activities include picnicking, hiking, bicycling, and canoeing, camping, wildlife viewing, fishing and boating. Amenities include an RV park, four pavilion picnic shelters, a boat ramp, and a full-facility campground with youth, group and primitive campsites. The park has a number of trails. A 13.6-mile (21.9 km) canoe trail that flows down the Blackwater River through a mangrove forest. A 6.5-mile (10.5 km) hiking trail runs through the park. A .9 mile nature trail features a boardwalk system and observation platform that overlooks the salt marsh. The park is open from 8:00AM until sundown year round.  Fakahatchee Strand Preserve State Park – Approximately twenty miles long and five miles wide, the Fakahatchee Strand is a swamp forest that hosts a number of rare and endangered tropical plant species. It is the only place in the world where bald cypress trees and royal palms share the forest canopy. Wildlife such as the Florida panther, American alligator, White-tailed deer and Black bear may be spotted.   Florida Panther National Wildlife Refuge is part of the United States National Wildlife Refuge System, located in southwestern Florida, twenty miles east of Naples, in the upper segment of the Fakahatchee Strand of the Big Cypress Swamp. It is north of I-75 and west of SR 29. The 26,400 acre (107 km²) refuge was established in 1989 under the Endangered Species Act, to protect the endangered Florida Panther, as well as other threatened plant and animal species. Besides the panthers, the refuge is home to Big Cypress fox squirrels, bobcats, black bears, alligators, swallow-tailed kites and several wood stork rookeries. It is part of a network of private land and government protected areas. To protect the panther and other endangered inhabitants, general public use is only available at the southeast corner of the refuge, on designated hiking trails. All other areas are can only be seen by way of limited tours.   Ten Thousand Islands National Wildlife Refuge, 20 miles southeast of Naples, and south of SR 41 near Goodland. A chain of mangrove islets off the coast, one of the largest expanses of mangrove estuary in North America. About 30% of the refuge (8,000 acres) is mangrove forest, 16,000 acres marine water, and 11,000 acres is freshwater marshland and other habitat.</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">32124</field>
		<field name="title">Lancaster County</field>
		<field name="main">other destinations</field>
		<field name="name">other destinations</field>
		<field name="content">Amish towns have colorful names, most are unintentionally humorous.  Intercourse  Paradise  Blue Ball  Bird In Hand  Fertility  Gap</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">32125</field>
		<field name="title">Pennsylvania</field>
		<field name="main">other destinations</field>
		<field name="name">other destinations</field>
		<field name="content">Allegheny Portage Railroad National Historic Site   Delaware Water Gap National Recreation Area   Gettysburg National Military Park  — the site of the most famous battlefield on U.S. soil, which saw the bloodiest battle and the turning point of the Civil War  Johnstown Flood National Memorial   Lehigh Valley   Poconos and Endless Mountains   Raccoon Creek State Park   Steamtown National Historic Site   Penn State University  — the third-largest "city" in the state, but only when the Nittany Lions football team is playing</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">32126</field>
		<field name="title">Porcupine Mountains</field>
		<field name="main">other destinations</field>
		<field name="name">other destinations</field>
		<field name="content">Ontonagon County Historical Society, 422 River Street,   . The Museum is easy to spot as it is painted a bright pink and purple colors. The Museum offers lots of information on the area and is the starting point for Lighthouse Tours. Lighthouse Tours are available in summer M-F at 11:00AM, 2PM, and 4PM, and Sa at 11AM and 3PM. Tours are also available by appointment on Sundays and in the off season.    Copper Peak Adventure Ride  near Ironwood, MI.  This is southwest of the Porkies. Only the brave will climb to the top of the worlds largest ski jump.  Porcupine Mountains Folk School,   . Located within the park near the Union Bay Campground, this Folk School features workshops year round by local artists and artisians.  Recent workshops have included timber framing, black ash basketry, and snowshoe making.  The Folk School has a fun and relaxing atmosphere.  It is run by the non-profit organization, Friends of the Porkies, whose mission is to enhance the park visitors experience and in cooperation with Porcupine Mountains State Park. It offers things to do for those not able to get out do 20 mile day hikes and has been popular with local retirees.</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">32127</field>
		<field name="title">Ashland County (Ohio)</field>
		<field name="main">other destinations</field>
		<field name="name">other destinations</field>
		<field name="content">Malabar Farm State Park, southern Ashland County,  4050 Bromfield Road, Lucas.    15 Primitive campsites and over 12 miles of back-country trails.The original Bromfield home is now a 19-bed hostel. Mohican State Park and Lodge, southern Ashland County. Lodge: 96 air-conditioned rooms, private balcony, color television. The lodge has private meeting, banquet rooms, dining room, sauna, gift shop, lounge, olympic-size indoor and outdoor pools. Cabins: Twenty-five two-bedroom family cottages, heated, utensils, towels, bed linens and blankets Camping: 120 campsites, electricity, fire rings, picnic tables, full service hookups available at 33 campsites. The main campground has showers, flush toilets, dump station.  Hemlock Grove campground has 24 non-electric sites, pit latrines, tables and fire rings. Two camper cabins, equipped with bunk, double beds, a mini refrigerator and fan, can be rented. Other aminities: 13 miles of trails, forest, two waterfalls, scenic wooden bridge and lake. Mohican Adventures Canoe, Camp, Cabins, and Fun Center, 3045 State Route 3 South, ☎ 800-662-2663. Mohican Adventures Canoe, Campground, Cabins, Fun Center offers an affordable place for families to stay during their Ohio vacation. They offer canoe, kayak, raft, and tube trips down the Mohican River. They also have three 18-hole mini golf courses and 2 lighted go-kart tracks. Their campground has an indoor swimming pool and hot tub, a lake and pond stocked for fishing, a beach area, hiking and biking trails, 3 playgrounds, and much much more! They also offer a Fun Package that provides for a day or two of fun for one low price. Website: www.mohicanadventures.com Charles Mill Lake  Loudonville  Recreation area. Mohican State Forest Mid-Ohio Sports Car Course Mansfield Motorsports Park Pleasant Hill State Park and Lake</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">32128</field>
		<field name="title">Polk County (Florida)</field>
		<field name="main">other destinations</field>
		<field name="name">other destinations</field>
		<field name="content">Allen David Broussard Catfish Creek  — is a Florida State Park, located about 10 miles east of Dundee, off US 27. The park offers six miles of hiking trails along with eight miles of equestrian trails; meandering through scrub, sandhill and flatwoods habitats. The preserves scrub, sandhill, and flatwoods communities are home to numerous rare plants such as scrub morning glory, scrub plum, pygmy fringe tree, and cutthroat grass. They are also home to several protected animal species including Florida scrub-jays, bald eagles, gopher tortoises, and Florida scrub lizards. Visitors can enjoy hiking, wildlife viewing, and horseback riding.    Circle B Bar Reserve     Lake Kissimmee State Park</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">32129</field>
		<field name="title">Greater Boston</field>
		<field name="main">other destinations</field>
		<field name="name">other destinations</field>
		<field name="content">Boston Harbor Islands</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">32130</field>
		<field name="title">Franklin County (Vermont)</field>
		<field name="main">other destinations</field>
		<field name="name">other destinations</field>
		<field name="content">Ensoburg Falls</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">32131</field>
		<field name="title">Maryland</field>
		<field name="main">other destinations</field>
		<field name="name">other destinations</field>
		<field name="content">The massive Chesapeake Bay Bridge     Antietam Battlefield  — site of the bloodiest single day in American History, at the first battle of the Civil War in the North   Appalachian Trail  — the great Appalachian Trail passes through the Maryland panhandle for a mere 40 miles, but that includes one excellent and easy hike to the ever popular rock-climbing mecca of Annapolis Rock—its also just fun to be able to say that you walked across the state of Maryland, which you can do in just a couple of days   Assateague Island  — a beautiful national park of a barrier island, populated by wild ponies   Catoctin Mountain Park  — a big, rugged National Park centered around Catoctin Mountain, and home to the Presidential retreat of Camp David   Chesapeake Bay  — the Great Shellfish Bay is a whole travel region of its own, offering fishing, crabbing, swimming, boating, sailing, unique island communities, placid bed breakfasts, and just plain beautiful sunsets   Deep Creek Lake  — Marylands mountain/lake resort and spa   Great Falls  — the spectacular Great Falls along the Potomac River, plus endless walking/biking trails along the historic Chesapeake and Ohio Canal   St. Marys City  — Marylands original colonial capital and one of the very first  British  settlements in  North America    Patapsco Valley State Park  — a big state park with over 32 miles of well-marked trails leading to historic and natural sites of interest, all just a half-hours drive away from  Baltimore</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">32132</field>
		<field name="title">Washington County (Maryland)</field>
		<field name="main">other destinations</field>
		<field name="name">other destinations</field>
		<field name="content">Chesapeake and Ohio Canal National Historic Park</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">32133</field>
		<field name="title">Arkansas</field>
		<field name="main">other destinations</field>
		<field name="name">other destinations</field>
		<field name="content">Hot Springs National Park    Buffalo National River</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">32134</field>
		<field name="title">St. Tammany Parish</field>
		<field name="main">other destinations</field>
		<field name="name">other destinations</field>
		<field name="content">Abita Springs  town in the woods; namesake of regionally popular beer   Fontainebleau State Park , popular park stretching from the lakeshore into the woods, east of Mandeville.   Madisonville  old town on the Tchefuncte River just north of Lake Pontchartrain</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">32135</field>
		<field name="title">South Dakota</field>
		<field name="main">other destinations</field>
		<field name="name">other destinations</field>
		<field name="content">Badlands National Park    Black Hills National Forest    Chief Crazy Horse Memorial  A mountain which is to be the worlds largest statue. Decades-long, generations-long project near  Custer    Jewel Cave National Monument    Lewis and Clark Trail  - Lewis and Clark passed through the state along the Missouri River in their now legendary journey to the  Pacific Northwest    Minuteman Missile National Historic Site    Missouri National Recreational River    Mount Rushmore National Memorial    Wind Cave National Park  A park is named for its sacred cave whos air which is either sucked in or blown out, depending on atmospheric conditions</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">32136</field>
		<field name="title">Channel Islands (California)</field>
		<field name="main">other destinations</field>
		<field name="name">other destinations</field>
		<field name="content">Channel Islands National Park  - The visitor center is located in  Ventura .  The park encompasses five islands (Anacapa, Santa Cruz, Santa Rosa, San Miguel, and Santa Barbara) and their ocean environment, preserving and protecting a wealth of natural and cultural resources. Isolation over thousands of years has created unique animals, plants, and archeological resources found nowhere else.      WikiPedia:Channel Islands of California     Commons:Category:Channel Islands, California</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">32137</field>
		<field name="title">North Coast (California)</field>
		<field name="main">other destinations</field>
		<field name="name">other destinations</field>
		<field name="content">Gualala   Redwood National Park  - ancient coast redwood ecosystem preserved in the park contains some of the planets most majestic forests  Sinkyone Wilderness   Trinity Alps   Fort Ross  - Historic Russian Outpost located on Historic Highway 1 City of Ten Thousand Buddhas - The largest Buddhist temples in the Western Hemisphere over 2,000 acres large, influened by Chinese, Japanese and Vietnamese architecture. A must see. 4951 Bodhi Way.Ukiah, California 95482(707)462-0939</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">32138</field>
		<field name="title">Monroe County (Michigan)</field>
		<field name="main">other destinations</field>
		<field name="name">other destinations</field>
		<field name="content">Sterling State Park  - the only state park on Lake Erie</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">32139</field>
		<field name="title">Clay County (Florida)</field>
		<field name="main">other destinations</field>
		<field name="name">other destinations</field>
		<field name="content">Gold Head Branch State Park is a Florida State Park with 2,000-acres (8 km²) of rolling sandhills, marshes, ravines, lakes and scrub located six miles north of Keystone Heights on SR 21. Among the wildlife of the park are fox squirrels, southeastern kestrels, red-tailed hawks, bald eagles, turkeys, and gopher tortoises. The park also has pocket gopher, fox, white-tailed deer and variety of water and wading birds. The park has a diversity of wild flowers. Among them are blazing Star, goldenrod, and lopsided Indian grass. Recreational activities include fishing, horseback riding, canoeing, swimming, hiking and wildlife viewing. Amenities include full facility camping, lakeside cabins, a picnic area overlooking Little Lake Johnson, and a beach on the lake. The park also has four marked hiking trails and a seven mile equestrian trail.</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">32140</field>
		<field name="title">Putnam County (Florida)</field>
		<field name="main">other destinations</field>
		<field name="name">other destinations</field>
		<field name="content">Dunns Creek is a Florida State Park, located 13 miles south of Palatka, on US 17 between Pomona Park and Satsuma. The parks natural communities include sandhills, covered with longleaf pines and wiregrass, and sand pine scrub. These communities protect several endangered and threatened species, such as the gopher tortoise, as well as a variety of other native animals. A picnic and hiking area is located on U.S. 17, north of Pomona Park. The mile-and-a-half hiking and bicycling trail takes visitors to the pristine waters of Blue Pond.   Ravine Gardens State Park is a 59 acre Florida State Park located in Palatka, Florida. The park was constructed by the Works Progress Administration, with cypress buildings, rock gardens and fieldstone terraces. Near the park entrance is The Court of States and a 64 foot obelisk dedicated to Franklin D. Roosevelt. Recreational activities include viewing the thousands of plants and shrubs, picnicking, jogging, hiking and biking. Amenities include interpretive exhibits, picnic areas, gardens, hiking trails, a 1.8 mile paved perimeter loop road, and a parcours trail. Visitors can rent a large covered pavilion, auditorium, and meeting rooms. The park is part of the annual Azalea Festival the first weekend in March, when the nearly 100,000 plants that the WPA planted decades ago bloom.</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">32141</field>
		<field name="title">New Hampshire</field>
		<field name="main">other destinations</field>
		<field name="name">other destinations</field>
		<field name="content">Mount Washington State Park    Waterville Valley  — a resort town in the White Mountains.   White Mountain National Forest  — home of many peaks in the Presidential Range</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">32142</field>
		<field name="title">Baker County (Florida)</field>
		<field name="main">other destinations</field>
		<field name="name">other destinations</field>
		<field name="content">Olustee Battlefield Historic State Park is a Florida State Park in the Osceola National Forest, near the town of Olustee. The site of Floridas largest Civil War battle, the park is located 50 miles west of Jacksonville and 15 miles east of Lake City, on U.S. 90. The State of Florida actually owns only 3.09 acres of the Park, but manages another 688 acres of the original battlefield under a Special Use Permit from the United States Forest Service. Under the title of Olustee Battlefield, it was added to the U.S. National Register of Historic Places on August 12, 1970.</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">32143</field>
		<field name="title">Northern Arizona</field>
		<field name="main">other destinations</field>
		<field name="name">other destinations</field>
		<field name="content">Chloride  mdash; a "living ghost town" just off the road to Vegas  Grand Canyon   Navajo Nation   Glen Canyon National Recreation Area- Lake Powell</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">32144</field>
		<field name="title">Nevada</field>
		<field name="main">other destinations</field>
		<field name="name">other destinations</field>
		<field name="content">Great Basin National Park    Lake Mead National Recreation Area   U.S. Route 50 "Loneliest Highway"   Area 51   Nevada State Route 375, "The Extraterrestrial Highway"   Black Rock City  — town of 50,000 people during Burning Man Festival, wide open desert during the rest of the year</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">32145</field>
		<field name="title">Frontier Country</field>
		<field name="main">other destinations</field>
		<field name="name">other destinations</field>
		<field name="content">Oklahoma City/Adventure District  - Home to seven outstanding attractions in one location.   Oklahoma City/Bricktown  - Oklahoma Citys entertainment district and neighborhood.</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">32146</field>
		<field name="title">Oregon Coast</field>
		<field name="main">other destinations</field>
		<field name="name">other destinations</field>
		<field name="content">Lewis and Clark National Historical Park  - made up of 12 park sites located on a 40-mile stretch of the Pacific coast from  Long Beach , WA to  Cannon Beach , OR. Visit the sites in any order you wish; we recommend starting at Fort Clatsop or the Lewis and Clark Interpretive Center at Cape Disappointment.    Oregon Dunes National Recreation Area  - Formed by the ancient forces of wind, water and time, these dunes are like no others in the world. This is the largest expanse of coastal sand dunes in North America.</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">32147</field>
		<field name="title">Charlotte County</field>
		<field name="main">other destinations</field>
		<field name="name">other destinations</field>
		<field name="content">Little Gasparilla Island   Charlotte Harbor Preserve State Park is a Florida State Park, composed of islands and land that surrounds Charlotte Harbor. The park can be accessed from Punta Gorda, Cape Coral, Cape Haze, El Jobean, Rotonda and Little Pine Island. The main offices are approximately 3 miles south of US 41/Tamiami Trail, in Punta Gorda. The park provides vast areas of unspoiled scenery and vital habitat for many varieties of wildlife. The upland areas of the park are accessible at pedestrian walk-throughs available in each section of the park. The park also manages more than 80 miles of Charlotte Harbor shoreline. Most of it is shallow water fringed by mangroves. These areas provide amazing opportunities to view wading birds, manatees, dolphins and other wildlife. It is best accessed by kayak or canoe.</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">32148</field>
		<field name="title">Olympic Peninsula</field>
		<field name="main">other destinations</field>
		<field name="name">other destinations</field>
		<field name="content">Ruby Beach in the Olympic National Park    Olympic National Park  - Here you will find Pacific Ocean beaches, rainforest valleys, glacier-capped peaks and a stunning variety of plants and animals  The Quinault Rain Forest is located the northern part of Grays Harbor county.  The Makah Indian Reservation has a great museum and is easy access to the Olympic National Park.  Fort Worden State Park is an old military fort right next to Port Townsend.</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">32149</field>
		<field name="title">Connecticut</field>
		<field name="main">other destinations</field>
		<field name="name">other destinations</field>
		<field name="content">Connecticut is rich with history, nature, art and beauty.  Truly something for everyone.  While many people are drawn each year to Mohegan Sun and Foxwoods Casinos, there is much more in this state.  There are a number of beaches at the shore, state parks and forests throughout the state, and many smaller parks as well.  Gillette Castle State Park in  East Haddam  is an excellent family destination.  So is the Essex Steam Train and River Boat Ride in  Essex .</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">32150</field>
		<field name="title">Piney Woods</field>
		<field name="main">other destinations</field>
		<field name="name">other destinations</field>
		<field name="content">Big Thicket National Preserve</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">32151</field>
		<field name="title">Eastern Oregon</field>
		<field name="main">other destinations</field>
		<field name="name">other destinations</field>
		<field name="content">Hells Canyon  - the part of the Snake River on the border between  Idaho  and  Oregon .  Parts of the River in this area are still wild but much of it is a series of reservoirs created by power dams.  One part of the Canyon is deeper than the  Grand Canyon  but getting to the overlook is generally only possible during the summer because some access roads are not maintained during winter.  John Day Fossil Beds National Monument - Within the John Day Valley are fossil beds. These sedimentary rock layers preserve a 40-million-year record of plant and animal life.   Nez Perce National Historical Park - Since time immemorial, the Nimiipuu or Nez Perce have lived among the rivers, canyons and prairies of the inland northwest. Despite the cataclysmic change of the past two centuries, the Nez Perce are still here.</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">32152</field>
		<field name="title">Kauai</field>
		<field name="main">other destinations</field>
		<field name="name">other destinations</field>
		<field name="content">Hanalei, on the north shore, is home to a quaint little beach town and famous Hanalei Bay, a crescent shaped bay known for its sandy white beaches and world class surf.  The center of town provides a young, relaxed vibe perfect for the young traveler. The burger joint in the center of town provides amazing views of one of Kauais biggest mountains with a visible waterfall in the center. Haena, lies just beyond Hanalei. It is mostly made up of residential homes, but is also is the gateway to Na Pali Coast and the location of Limahuli Valley, another National Tropical Botanical Garden of the Pacific. Hanapepe on the south shore has a quaint downtown filled with artists galleries and craft shops. There is also a swinging footbridge over the Hanapepe River. Be sure to check out the Banana Patch Studio for wonderful hand painted tiles and other locally made items. Kilauea is a small village that most people pass on the way to the Kilauea Lighthouse. The Kong Lung Center offers a few unique stores and restaurants. There is also a large fruit stand, Banana Joes, located north of Kilauea on the mountain side of the highway. Lumahai Beach is a very-well photographed beach but is only accessible by a short hike through a tropical path.  Located between Hanalei and Haena beaches, this secluded beach is perfect for people who want a more private experience.  There are lava formations and caves to explore and low wake perfect for snorkeling. For the more adventurous traveler, there is the opportunity to cliff jump into the ocean from one of the protruding lava rock formations.  Lumahai beach is a place many locals go so it gives tourists to see the special opportunity of the "real" Hawaii.</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">32153</field>
		<field name="title">Tuscarawas County</field>
		<field name="main">other destinations</field>
		<field name="name">other destinations</field>
		<field name="content">Atwood Lake Beach City Lake</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">32154</field>
		<field name="title">Wakulla County</field>
		<field name="main">other destinations</field>
		<field name="name">other destinations</field>
		<field name="content">Apalachicola National Forest   Bald Point State Park is a Florida State Park located south of Ochlockonee Bay, approximately seven miles southeast of  Panacea , in Alligator Point, off U.S. 98, in northwestern Florida. The park has such amenities as beaches, bicycling, birding, canoeing, fishing, hiking, kayaking, swimming and wildlife viewing.   Saint Marks  National Wildlife Refuge</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">32155</field>
		<field name="title">North America</field>
		<field name="main">other destinations</field>
		<field name="name">other destinations</field>
		<field name="content">Grand Mayan ruins at Tikal, Guatemala       Banff National Park  — Canadas first national park is also one of its largest   Chichen Itza  — the largest of the archaeological cities of the pre-Columbian Maya civilization in the Yucatan Peninsula of Mexico   Corcovado National Park  — very biologically diverse national park in Costa Rica   Grand Canyon  — a massive canyon in Arizona, carved over several million years   Niagara Falls  — three grandiose waterfalls on the border between the United States and Canada   Teotihuacan  — the city of the gods, with some of the largest ancient pyramids in the world   Tikal  —  an archaeological site in Guatemala, one of the largest and most important of the ancient Mayan cities   Walt Disney World  — the flagship of Disneys worldwide theme park empire, near Orlando, Florida   Yellowstone National Park  — the worlds first national park is also home to most of its geysers and an amazing concentration of animals</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">32156</field>
		<field name="title">Virginia</field>
		<field name="main">other destinations</field>
		<field name="name">other destinations</field>
		<field name="content">Blue Ridge Parkway   Shenandoah National Park</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">32157</field>
		<field name="title">Ulster County</field>
		<field name="main">other destinations</field>
		<field name="name">other destinations</field>
		<field name="content">Ellenville    Kerhonkson</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">32158</field>
		<field name="title">Lorain County</field>
		<field name="main">other destinations</field>
		<field name="name">other destinations</field>
		<field name="content">Amherst Ohio Town Hall  Findley State Park southern Lorain County, 25381 State Route 58,  Wellington , 272 non-electric camp sites, fully stocked camp store, sand volleyball, basketball court, two horseshoe pits, 93-acre lake, two launch ramps, canoes, rowboats, paddleboats and ten miles of hiking trails. Eight miles of singletrack mountain biking.  Findley Lake and Dam  Lake Erie Lake Erie is the shallowest, warmest and southernmost of the Great Lakes, and is the 12th largest freshwater lake in the world. Eries shallowness adds to its treacherous reputation; she can go from flat calm to a raging beast in less than 20 minutes. (Dave Kelch, Ohio State University Extension Specialist, Ohio Sea Grant)  Lake Erie Shipwrecks Lake Erie has over 1700 shipwrecks   , of which only approximately 277 have been found and salvaged, or located by divers and remain on the bottom. Over 6000 shipwrecks are known to have occurred Great Lakes-wide, with Lake Erie claiming the most at 1700. Lorains offshore waters hold some of the best wrecks for diving in Lake Erie. Popular destination shipwrecks offshore of the Lorain area include: Morning Star, City of Concord, Courtland, Hickory Stick, Sarah Sheldon, Ivanhoe, Craftsman, Alva B, John Pridgeon Jr., and the Duke Luedtke just to mention a few. (Dave Kelch, Ohio State University Extension Specialist, Ohio Sea Grant)   Back Roads and Beaches Bike and Multi-Sport Route  Miles of rolling, rural roads with beautiful scenery ranging from farmland and forest to the nautical flavor of the Lake Erie Shoreline. The route provides the most scenic and low traffic routes that lead riders through some of Ohios best landscape. It also highlights some of the areas most relevant history, culture, arts and cutting-edge environmental initiatives. The BRaB tour only highlights eateries that feature locally grown produce, organics, healthy choices and spectacular outdoor views of natural areas. The route travels through several small towns and cities in Lorain County. The tour is popular with both touring cyclists as well as training athletes and triathletes. The tour features abundant  Underground Railroad  history as well as six wineries and a number of art galleries along the way.   Mileage and Terrain: Most of the route is relatively flat with a few rolling sections. You will find some challenging climbs in the northwest section, just south of Vermilion.   Black River and Lake Erie Kayaking - Kayakers of all skill levels will be comfortable on the Black River and/or Lake Erie. Lake Erie offers spectacular scenery, birding and up-close views of the Lorain Lighthouse. From here you can kayak on Lake Erie, inside or outside the breakwall.   Mountain Biking The almost 10 mile Thorn Mountain Biking trail at Findley State Park has beautiful forested single track with options for beginner to expert. Cascade Park Elyria. Features beautiful twin waterfalls that mark the union of the east and west branches of the Black River. Explore the shale cliffs and natural formations created by the retreat of the Wisconsin glacier over 12,000 years ago.   Lakeview Beach and Park On SR 6 in Lorain. Newly restored, this is one of the nicest beaches on Lake Erie with a brand new bathhouse that overlooks Lake Erie and the Lorain Lighthouse. It is one of Lorain Countys most picturesque beaches. Historic fountain is lit up at night.  Lake Erie Central Basin Sport Fishing - Sport fishing in Lorain County consists of walleye fishing in Lake Erie, to fishing the numerous tributary streams for trophy steelhead. Walleye are considered the most-pursued game fish on Lake Erie, and in Lorain County waters, they are caught along Lorain Countys rocky nearshore beginning in the spring and continuing through the entire season. Deeper offshore waters offer anglers plenty of walleye action during the summer and fall months, with both trolling and drifting/cast methods being productive. Limit catches and trophy sized fish are trademarks of our Lake Erie waters. The well-known sandbar, located between Lorain and Vermilion, creates a natural habitat for summer and fall walleye, producing many trophy-size walleye in late October and November. Smallmouth bass are plentiful along the entire lenght of Lorain Countys rocky shoreline and artificial reef structures, providing fast action from spring through fall. (Dave Kelch, Ohio State University Extension Specialist, Ohio Sea Grant)   Underground Railroad History While northern Lorain County established itself as a manufacturing mecca, a tiny town miles to the south put itself on the map for a different reason. Oberlin would come to be known as "The Town that Started the Civil War." Students and faculty of Oberlin College were especially sympathetic to fugitive slaves. Today the colleges Underground Railroad sculpture, dramatic railroad tracks that emerge from the ground, is surrounded by a healing garden of flowering and leafed plants used by slaves on their road to freedom. The Oberlin Heritage Center    and the Spirit of 76 Museum in Wellington are valuable resources for more on the areas role in the civil War. Throughout Lorain County, churches, cemeteries, historic homes and peaceful parks collectively tell Americas story of freedom. "On the Trail to Freedom," is a program developed in 1992 by Visit Lorain County which guides visitors to points of interest on the Underground Railroad.   Allen Memorial Art Museum  One of the finest college or university collections in the United States, comprising more than 12,000 works of art from virtually every culture.    Frank Lloyd Wright - Weltzheimer/Johnson House  The first Usonian house in Ohio and one of the few in the nation open to the public.</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">32159</field>
		<field name="title">Mono County</field>
		<field name="main">other destinations</field>
		<field name="name">other destinations</field>
		<field name="content">Mono Lake  - Were talkin a lake thats truly bizarre-a-mundo!  At several points around it odd, Seussian-like towers of limestone rise from the water.  Rent a canoe or kayak in Mammoth Lakes or take one of the Mono Lake Committees canoe tours to see these "Tufa towers" close up.  Millions of birds stop at the lake to munch on the trillions of brine shrimp living in its salty waters.  If youre a birder, plan to attend the Mono Lake Bird Chatauqua on the third weekend of June.  It sells out, so reserve early to join walks, talks and otherwise birdy things.    Bodie State Historic Park  - Someone compared Bodie on this Wiki to the Eastern Sierras Deadwood.  Not at all.  Deadwood is a commercialized and inhabited tourist attraction, whereas Bodie is a completely uncommercialized ghost town, kept in a state of arrested decay by curators and historians of the California State Parks.  At Bodie, you get a real idea of what it was like in a big mining town (pop. 10,000), after everyone left... school work scattered across desks, cards left on dusty tables in saloons, lace window curtains blowing in the breeze of an abandoned home.  The only people left in Bodie are the prostitutes, outlaws, miners and ordinary citizens buried on boot hill, and you and a few caretakers whose job is to make sure the place never changes from what it looked like when the mines gave out and the people departed.   Twin Lakes  - Two, almost identically sized lakes are found 14 miles southwest of Bridgeport.  Located at 7,000 ft. in elevation, the lakes are favorite places for shore, float and boat fishing.  United States Marine Corps Mountain Warfare Training Center - Established in 1951 specifically to provide mountain and cold weather training for replacement personnel bound for Korea, this intense training ground is one of the U.S. Marine Corps’ most remote and isolated posts, and one of its most difficult training grounds. The Center is located at 6,762 feet, on 46,000 acres of the Toiyabe National Forest. Lowest course elevation is 6,800 ft, and highest elevation is 7,800 ft. Average temperature in May is 53 degrees.  This is where the U.S. Marines receive high-altitute training before heading to battle the Taliban and Al Qaeda in the mountains of Afghanistan.  On this terrain is run one of the most challenging 10K runs, anywhere.  Its open not only to military athletes, but to anyone willing to take on a Marine Corps-sized challenge.  The gain is 1,100 feet beginning at 6,800 ft. and climbing to 7,600 ft in just 2.3 miles.  The Marines have named this stretch, "Heart Attack Hill."  About the time you hit the first water station at only one mile up the hill, youve hit the runners proverbial wall and are thankful youre just a marathoner and not one of the Marines stationed here who, in the course of their arduous training, have to do similar things carrying full combat gear.  You settle in and begin to understand what the Marines mean when they call each other grunts and experience a little of what its about to be one of the few, the proud.   Humboldt-Toiyabe National Forest    Inyo National Forest    Virginia Lakes    Lundy Canyon   Tioga Pass   June Lakes   Convict Lake  McGee Creek  Crowley Lake   Rock Creek   Mono Craters  Hot Creek  White Mountains</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">32160</field>
		<field name="title">Grand Traverse Bay Area</field>
		<field name="main">other destinations</field>
		<field name="name">other destinations</field>
		<field name="content">Boyne Falls  - a village on the Boyne River.   Sleeping Bear Dunes National Lakeshore    Pere Marquette State Forest</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">32161</field>
		<field name="title">Missouri</field>
		<field name="main">other destinations</field>
		<field name="name">other destinations</field>
		<field name="content">Mastodon State Historic Site , Imperial   Ste. Genevieve  – first settlement and oldest brick building still intact today west of the Mississippi River   Lake of the Ozarks    Truman Lake    Table Rock Lake    Wilsons Creek National Battlefield    Ozarks   Lewis Clark National Historic Trail  - Between May 1804 and September 1806, 32 men, one woman, and a baby traveled from the plains of the Midwest to the shores of the Pacific Ocean. They called themselves the Corps of Discovery. Ozark National Scenic Riverways. Missouris only national park consists of the Current and Jacks Fork Rivers.  This is the best area in the state for an international  backpacker .  The park has numerous places to camp.  There are many canoe and float trip operators that will provide transportation to and from the river for a reasonable price.  While canoeing or floating down the rivers, there are many caves that one can explore, but be careful as bats and the occasional poisionous snake call these home.  If you decide to swim in the rivers, be careful and wear some kind of shoe that will stay securely on your feet.  The river is full of rocks that are very painful to the feet and the current of the rivers could sweep the shoes right off your feet.  It is still a great place to go swimming, especially the Current River.  The water on a 6 foot man only rises about neck high in most places and it is spring fed and very cold even on the hottest day.  Note: Be prepared if you have an emergency on the river as your cell phone will not work on the river or near it.  There are pay phones located at some stores along the river.  Bring everything you think you may need.  Hospitals are scarce and a good drive to get to in this area.   Montauk State Park  - Located approx. 20 miles from either Salem or Licking.  The top end of the Current River (not located within the boundaries of the national park).  Contains a fish hatchery where you can feed the trout being raised there.  Also has a lodge, general store, a full service diner-style reataurant, camping and cabins for rent.     Mark Twain National Forest  - Located in various parts of the state from the southwest to the east.  Features many campgrounds, hiking trails, and lakes.  Some sites of note: Council Bluffs; on Highway DD about 3 miles north of Hwy 32 in Iron County.  Features a full campground, beach swimming, boat rentals and concessions.  Loggers Lake; approx. 10 miles from highway 72 in Bunker, follow signs as this place is not on any kind of paved road.  Features everything mentioned above except concessions.</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">32162</field>
		<field name="title">Highlands (Maine)</field>
		<field name="main">other destinations</field>
		<field name="name">other destinations</field>
		<field name="content">Moosehead Lake Region (Maine)</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">32163</field>
		<field name="title">Bluegrass Region</field>
		<field name="main">other destinations</field>
		<field name="name">other destinations</field>
		<field name="content">Fort Boonesborough State Park    Kentucky Bourbon Trail  Shaker Village of Pleasant Hill</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">32164</field>
		<field name="title">Sandusky County</field>
		<field name="main">other destinations</field>
		<field name="name">other destinations</field>
		<field name="content">Sandusky Bay  Lake Erie Sandusky Bay Sandusky River</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">32165</field>
		<field name="title">Haverford Township</field>
		<field name="main">other destinations</field>
		<field name="name">other destinations</field>
		<field name="content">Philadelphia , Pennsylvania is within a 25 minutes car ride from Haverford Township.  It is also very easy to take public transportation, SEPTA, into the city whether it be by train or bus.  Amtrak Regional Rail line the R3 and R5 go directly into the city from Haverford Township.  It is also an option to take routes 104, 112, or 123 to 69th street from the Manoa Shopping Center.  At 69th street you can transfer over to the Market Frankford Line which brings you to Center City.    Located in Ardmore, minutes away from Haverford Township is Suburban Square.  Here there is great shopping and dining.  There are stores such as Macys, Urban Outfitters, Free People, The Gap, City Sports, American Eagle, and many more.  There are also great restaurants such as Plate, Corner Bakery Cafe, and Rubys.    Within a twenty minute drive of Haverford Township there is the King of Prussia Mall.  This is one of the best malls in the country and the East Coasts premier shopping destination.  It is composed of two malls, The Plaza and The Court.  There are hundreds and stores a including: Bloomingdales, Nordstrom, HM, Forever 21, American Apparel, Louis Vuitton, Tiffany and Company, Coach, and many  more.  There are also many great restaurants such as The Cheesecake Factory, Morton Steak House and Maggianos.  It is also very easy to get to the mall by using SEPTA.  Route 123 takes you directly to the mall from the Manoa Shopping Center for a very affordable price.</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">32166</field>
		<field name="title">Del Norte County</field>
		<field name="main">other destinations</field>
		<field name="name">other destinations</field>
		<field name="content">Redwood National Park</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">32167</field>
		<field name="title">Ozarks</field>
		<field name="main">other destinations</field>
		<field name="name">other destinations</field>
		<field name="content">Buffalo River Pruitt Landing    Buffalo National River  In northern  Arkansas  is an unpolluted and free-flowing river in the heart of the Ozarks. It has both swift water and calm stretches.   Ozark National Scenic Riverways    In southern  Missouri  consists of the spring-fed Current River and Jacks Fork River.</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">32168</field>
		<field name="title">Panhandle (Nebraska)</field>
		<field name="main">other destinations</field>
		<field name="name">other destinations</field>
		<field name="content">Chimney Rock National Historic Site     Scotts Bluff National Monument  - historic Rock formations along the Oregon Trail</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">32169</field>
		<field name="title">Florida</field>
		<field name="main">other destinations</field>
		<field name="name">other destinations</field>
		<field name="content">Amelia Island    Biscayne National Park    Canaveral National Seashore    Castillo de San Marcos and Fort Matanzas    Everglades National Park    Florida Keys    Gulf Islands National Seashore    Ocala National Forest    Walt Disney World</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">32170</field>
		<field name="title">United States of America</field>
		<field name="main">other destinations</field>
		<field name="name">other destinations</field>
		<field name="content">The Grand Canyon  in  Arizona ]] These are some of the largest and most famous destinations outside of major cities.    Denali National Park  — a remote national park featuring North Americas highest peak   Grand Canyon  — the worlds longest and most visited canyon   Mesa Verde National Park  — well-preserved Ancestral Puebloan cliff dwellings   Mount Rushmore  — the iconic memorial of four former presidents carved into a cliff face   Niagara Falls  — the massive waterfalls straddling the border with Canada   Great Smoky Mountains National Park  — national park in the southern Appalachians   Walt Disney World  — the most popular vacation resort destination in the world   Yellowstone National Park  — the first national park in the U.S., and home of the Old Faithful geyser   Yosemite National Park  —  home of El Capitan and the famous Giant Sequoia trees</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">32171</field>
		<field name="title">North Shore (Minnesota)</field>
		<field name="main">other destinations</field>
		<field name="name">other destinations</field>
		<field name="content">The Range  Boundary Waters Canoe Area Wilderness  Gunflint Trail</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">32172</field>
		<field name="title">Finger Lakes</field>
		<field name="main">other destinations</field>
		<field name="name">other destinations</field>
		<field name="content">Letchworth State Park  mdash; The Grand Canyon of the East, with three beautiful waterfalls</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">32173</field>
		<field name="title">Maui</field>
		<field name="main">other destinations</field>
		<field name="name">other destinations</field>
		<field name="content">Haleakala National Park    Iao Valley State Park</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">32174</field>
		<field name="title">Alpine County</field>
		<field name="main">other destinations</field>
		<field name="name">Grover Hot Springs State Park</field>
		<field name="content">The parks main features are the hot springs which feed into two concrete swimming pools filled with 102º F (39º C) mineral waters.  the park also has hiking and camping.</field>
		<field name="directions">four miles west of Markleeville</field>
		<field name="phone">+1 209 694-2248</field>
		<field name="address">At the end Hot Springs Road</field>
		<field name="hours">Closed on Thanksgiving, Christmas and New Years.</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">32175</field>
		<field name="title">Illinois</field>
		<field name="main">other destinations</field>
		<field name="name">other destinations</field>
		<field name="content">Monks Mound at Cahokia   Cahokia Mounds  is a surprising find in Illinois - the center of a prehistoric Native American city and one of only 20 UNESCO World Heritage sites in the U.S.  Lewis and Clark Trail  - Between May 1804 and September 1806, 32 men, one woman, and a baby traveled from the plains of the Midwest to the shores of the Pacific Ocean. They called themselves the Corps of Discovery.  Casino Queen and the Gateway Geyser  - Both are located on the Mississippi River in East St. Louis, IL  Shawnee National Forest   Starved Rock State Park  Ferne Clyffe State Park Kickapoo State Park Pere Marquette State Park Anna, located along Shawnee Hills Wine Trail</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">32176</field>
		<field name="title">Massachusetts</field>
		<field name="main">other destinations</field>
		<field name="name">other destinations</field>
		<field name="content">Boston Harbor Islands    Minute Man National Historical Park  - the birthplace of the American Revolution.   Nantucket  and  Marthas Vineyard  - offshore islands   Plymouth Plantation  - landing place of the Pilgrims   Six Flags New England  - a major amusement park   Old Sturbridge Village  - where there is a recreated colonial village   Tanglewood  - the summer home of the Boston Symphony Orchestra   Beverly - beautiful suburb near historic  Salem , wonderful restaurants and home of Tom Brady and Zach Hall</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">32177</field>
		<field name="title">Navajo Nation</field>
		<field name="main">other destinations</field>
		<field name="name">other destinations</field>
		<field name="content">Monument Valley Navajo Tribal Park   Antelope Canyon Navajo Tribal Park   Little Colorado River Navajo Tribal Park   Window Rock Navajo Tribal Park   Canyon de Chelly National Monument   Bowl Canyon Recreation Center</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">32178</field>
		<field name="title">Alabama</field>
		<field name="main">other destinations</field>
		<field name="name">other destinations</field>
		<field name="content">Gulf Shores   Orange Beach  - 32 miles of beautiful sugar white sands on the prettiest beaches on the Gulf of Mexico. A visit to Gulf Shores and Orange Beach offers the perfect balance of non-stop activity and lay-around-doing-nothing time. Putter around a bit on one of our championship golf courses. Cast your line for deep-sea adventure on a one of the Orange Beach fishing charters. Travel back in history with a visit to Fort Morgan, the site of the Civil War Battle of Mobile Bay. Commune with Mother Nature as you hike wildlife trails gazing at shorebirds.    Horseshoe Bend National Military Park  - In the spring of 1814, General Andrew Jackson and an army of 3,300 men attacked 1,000 Upper Creek warriors on the Tallapoosa River. Over 800 Upper Creeks died defending their homeland.     Little River Canyon National Preserve  - Little River is unique because it flows for most of its length atop Lookout Mountain in northeast Alabama    Natchez Trace Parkway  - The 444-mile Natchez Trace Parkway commemorates an ancient trail that connected southern portions of the Mississippi River, through Alabama, to salt licks in todays central Tennessee     Russell Cave National Monument  - For more than 10,000 years, Russell Cave was home to prehistoric peoples. Russell Cave provides clues to the daily lifeways of early North American inhabitants dating from 6500 B.C. to 1650 A.D.    Selma To Montgomery National Historic Trail  - The Selma to Montgomery National Voting Rights Trail was established by Congress in 1996 to commemorate the events, people, and route of the 1965 Voting Rights March in Alabama    Trail Of Tears National Historic Trail  - Come on a journey to remember and commemorate the survival of the Cherokee people despite their forced removal from their homelands in the Southeastern United States in the 1840s    Tuskegee Airmen National Historic Site  - In the 1940s Tuskegee, Alabama became home to a "military experiment" to train Americas first African-American military pilots. In time the "experiment" became known as the Tuskegee Experience and the participants as the Tuskegee Airmen    Tuskegee Institute National Historic Site  - Tuskegee Institute National Historic Site is nestled on the campus of historic Tuskegee University. The site includes the George W. Carver Museum and The Oaks, home of Booker T. Washington    Desoto Caverns  - A cavern and small family attraction in Childersburg, Alabama.</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">32179</field>
		<field name="title">Florida Panhandle</field>
		<field name="main">other destinations</field>
		<field name="name">other destinations</field>
		<field name="content">Apalachicola National Forest    Choctawhatchee National Forest    Gulf Islands National Seashore    Saint Marks  National Wildlife Refuge   St. Vincent National Wildlife Refuge</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">32180</field>
		<field name="title">Noble County (Ohio)</field>
		<field name="main">other destinations</field>
		<field name="name">other destinations</field>
		<field name="content">Wayne National Forest</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">32181</field>
		<field name="title">North Central Idaho</field>
		<field name="main">other destinations</field>
		<field name="name">other destinations</field>
		<field name="content">Nez Perce Indian Reservation   River of No Return Wilderness</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">32182</field>
		<field name="title">Utah Valley</field>
		<field name="main">other destinations</field>
		<field name="name">other destinations</field>
		<field name="content">Sundance Resort    is accesible from Provo Canyon.</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">32183</field>
		<field name="title">Pinellas County</field>
		<field name="main">other destinations</field>
		<field name="name">other destinations</field>
		<field name="content">Anclote Key Preserve State Park is a Florida State Park and historic site, located on Anclote Key three miles off Tarpon Springs and accessible only by boat. Amenities include primitive camping on the northern portion of the island as well as picnic pavilions and grills. Wildlife includes the American Oystercatcher, Bald Eagle and Piping Plover. The park is unique in that a lighthouse, built in 1887, is on the southern end of the key. Three Rooker Island, south of Anclote and part of the preserve, remains an important Gulf coast beach-nesting bird sanctuary. The park has such amenities as beaches, birding, primitive camping, boating, fishing, hiking, picknicking areas and wildlife viewing.  Caladesi Island State Park is a Florida State Park located on Caladesi Island, across St. Joseph Sound from Dunedin, Florida and north of Clearwater Beach. It is reachable by boat and ferry. Amenities include 3 miles of nature trail, a marina, picnic pavilions, bathhouses, a park concession and a beach. Recreational activities include fishing, shelling, kayaking, boating, hiking and nature studies. In 2005 it was listed as having the 4th best beach in the country, in 2006 and 2007 the 2nd best, and in 2008 the best beach in the United States. Originally part of a large barrier island, Caladesi Island and Honeymoon Island to the north were formed in 1921 when a hurricane created Hurricane Pass, splitting the larger island into two parts. Though still referred to as an island, Hurricane Elena filled Dunedin Pass in 1985, making Caladesi Island accessible by walking north from North Clearwater Beach.  Skyway Fishing Pier State Park is a Florida State Park located on the north and south sides of the mouth of Tampa Bay. When the new Sunshine Skyway Bridge was built on I-275 (US 19) after one part of the old bridge collapsed due to a barge accident, the approaches to the old bridge were turned into the longest fishing pier in the world. The bridge is lighted at night, and the park is open 24 hours a day, 365 days a year. The only activity is fishing. Common catches include snook, tarpon, grouper, black sea bass, Spanish mackerel, king mackerel, cobia, sheepshead, red snapper, and pompano. Snacks, drinks, bait, and fishing supplies can be purchased at the park.</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">32184</field>
		<field name="title">Big Island</field>
		<field name="main">other destinations</field>
		<field name="name">other destinations</field>
		<field name="content">Ala Kahakai National Historic Trail    Hawaii Volcanoes National Park     Kaloko-Honokohau National Historical Park     Puuhonua o Honaunau National Historical Park  Puukohola Heiau National Historic Site</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">32185</field>
		<field name="title">Suffolk County (New York)</field>
		<field name="main">other destinations</field>
		<field name="name">other destinations</field>
		<field name="content">Fire Island National Seashore</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">32186</field>
		<field name="title">Lake County (Florida)</field>
		<field name="main">other destinations</field>
		<field name="name">other destinations</field>
		<field name="content">Lake Griffin State Park is a Florida State Park located two miles (3 km) north of Leesburg and 30 miles (48 km) south of Ocala on U.S. Highway 441, is home to one of the states largest live oak trees. The park is unique in connecting to Lake Griffin, the Ocklawaha River and thence to the Harris Chain of Lakes, and is made up of 500 acres (2 km²) of swampland and hardwood upland. Activities include boating and canoeing, hiking, fishing, camping, and wildlife viewing. Among the wildlife of the park are Osprey, Bald Eagle, Blue Heron, Anhinga, Ibis, American Alligator, and River Otter. Amenities include a full-facility campground, a half-mile nature trail, a boat ramp that provides access to the Dead River, and a playground for small children as well as canoe rentals, a forty (40) site campground, and a picnic area. The park is open from 8:00 am until sundown year round.  Lake Louisa State Park is a 4,372-acre (17.69 km²) Florida State Park located in the northeast corner of the Green Swamp and the southwestern shore of Lake Louisa. It is ten miles (16 km) south of Clermont, off County Route 561 on Lake Nellie Road and is made up of bald cypress, live oak and saw palmettos. In addition to Lake Louisa, the park contains Hammond Lake, Dixie Lake, Dude Lake and Bear Lake. Activities include swimming, picnicking, horeseback riding, hiking, camping, fishing, and canoeing. Amenities include a canoe/kayak ramp, 16 miles (26 km) of equestrian trails, and a primitive equestrian campground, as well as a 0.5-mile (0.80 km) nature trail, 20 miles (32 km) of hiking trails, fishing pier, canoe/kayak launch, and a picnic pavilion. The park is open from 8:00 am till sundown year round.  Rock Springs Run State Reserve is a 14,000 acre (57 km²) State Park in the Lake County, Florida, located about 30 miles northeast of Orlando in Sorrento, 3 miles west of the Wekiva River bridge on State Road 46. The park contains a number of Indian mounds, pine flatwoods, swamps and artesian springs, and a number of creeks and rivers. Among them are Seminole Creek, Wekiwa Springs Run, Rock Springs Run, the Wekiva River, and Blackwater Creek. Activities include bicycling, hiking, canoeing, kayaking, horseback riding, hunting and wildlife viewing. Among the wildlife of the park are Florida black bear, Florida scrub jay, sandhill crane, indigo snake, gopher tortoise. Amenities include a canoe and kayak, rentals, swimming, tubing, about 17 miles of trails, access to the Rock Springs Run and the Wekiva River, primitive canoe and equestrian camping facilities. The park is open from 8:00 a.m. till 6:00 p.m. year round.</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">32187</field>
		<field name="title">Montgomery County (Maryland)</field>
		<field name="main">other destinations</field>
		<field name="name">other destinations</field>
		<field name="content">Cabin John Regional Park  — regular free concerts in the woods during the summer, and younger kids will love the elaborate playgrounds.  Chesapeake and Ohio Canal National Historical Park  — a beautiful park alongside the Potomac River, home to the impressive Great Falls.  Brookside Gardens  — 50 acres of beautiful and diverse landscaped gardens, both indoor and outdoor.  Glen Echo  — a a historic amusement park by the Potomac, dating from the nineteenth century, with a still active antique carousel, a historic electic street car, and frequent festivals and plays.  Rock Creek Park  — the Maryland portion of the famous National Park, with one very long bike/pedestrian path through the woods, and plenty of small parks for sports, playgrounds, etc.</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">32188</field>
		<field name="title">South Texas Plains</field>
		<field name="main">other destinations</field>
		<field name="name">other destinations</field>
		<field name="content">Natural Bridge Caverns</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">32189</field>
		<field name="title">Harney County</field>
		<field name="main">other destinations</field>
		<field name="name">other destinations</field>
		<field name="content">One of the biggest attractions in Harney County is the Steens Mountains.  The Steens is the tallest peak in Harney County at 9773 feet.  Calling the summit of the Steens a peak is somewhat inaccuate though, as the mountain is pretty much a gettle slope up to the summit.  The summit is gently arrived at from the west side, starting at an elevation of about 3500 feet and ending at the 9773 by going up the gentle slope of over 20 miles.  This is not the case on the east face though.  On the east face the elevation drops off from the 9773 feet to about 5000 in only 3 miles.  The view is quite incredible and awe inspiring by being able to look over the edge to the valley floor of the Alvord Desert nearly 5000 feet below.  As with all tall mountain ranges, the Steens can have very strong winter storms that yearly accumulate about 7 feet of snow.  The Steens are a geological hotspot as well, offering up a cross section of the earths crust.  Kiger Gorge gives onlookers the view of the earths different layers due to the carving out of the valley by massive glaciers that have long since disappeared.  http://students.bus.oregonstate.edu/wilcw031/steens.jpg</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">32190</field>
		<field name="title">Green County</field>
		<field name="main">other destinations</field>
		<field name="name">other destinations</field>
		<field name="content">The Sugar River State Recreational Trail: A greenbelt trail alongside the Sugar River, it travels 23 miles and connects Brodhead, Albany, Monticello and New Glarus.</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">32191</field>
		<field name="title">Portage County</field>
		<field name="main">other destinations</field>
		<field name="name">other destinations</field>
		<field name="content">West Branch State Park, 5708 Esworthy Road,  Ravenna . 29 full service camping sites, 155 camping sites with 50-amp electric hook-ups, 14 non-electric sites, heated showers, flush toilets, laundry facilities, 700-foot sand beach, showerhouse, change booth, snack bar, year-round fishing, hunting,   2,650 acres lake, twelve miles of hiking trails, twenty miles of bridle trails,  horse camp, playground and volleyball court</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">32192</field>
		<field name="title">Central Oregon</field>
		<field name="main">other destinations</field>
		<field name="name">other destinations</field>
		<field name="content">Mount Bachelor</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">32193</field>
		<field name="title">Rochester and Suburbs</field>
		<field name="main">other destinations</field>
		<field name="name">other destinations</field>
		<field name="content">Hamlin Beach State Park  mdash; camping on the Lake Ontario shoreline</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">32194</field>
		<field name="title">South Central Arizona</field>
		<field name="main">other destinations</field>
		<field name="name">other destinations</field>
		<field name="content">Casa Grande Ruins National Monument    Mount Lemmon    Saguaro National Park</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">32195</field>
		<field name="title">Colorado</field>
		<field name="main">other destinations</field>
		<field name="name">other destinations</field>
		<field name="content">Aspen  - trendy ski town known for its celebrities and liberal politics.   Black Canyon of the Gunnison National Park  - 12 miles of a spectacular and scenic gorge.   Breckenridge  - most popular ski resort in the U.S.   Colorados Wine Country  - Near  Palisade . Home to some of the highest vineyards in the world  Dinosaur National Monument  - Near  Craig . massive bones of Jurassic era sauropods and allosauruses abound throughout this fossil-rich area. Also a great place for whitewater rafting.  Great Sand Dunes National Park  - includes North Americas tallest dunes, which rise over 750 feet high against the Sangre de Cristo Mountains. Near  Alamosa .   Mesa Verde National Park  - home to Ancestral Puebloan cliff dwellings. Near  Cortez .   Rocky Mountain National Park  - drive the harrowing Trail Ridge Road down the spine of the Continental Divide. Near  Estes Park .   Vail  - Second largest ski resort in  North America .</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">32196</field>
		<field name="title">Rabun County (Georgia)</field>
		<field name="main">other destinations</field>
		<field name="name">other destinations</field>
		<field name="content">Sky Valley Resort</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">32197</field>
		<field name="title">Washington County (Ohio)</field>
		<field name="main">other destinations</field>
		<field name="name">other destinations</field>
		<field name="content">Wayne National Forest</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">32198</field>
		<field name="title">Vermont</field>
		<field name="main">other destinations</field>
		<field name="name">other destinations</field>
		<field name="content">Green Mountains   Lake Bomoseen   Lake Champlain   Lake Dunmore</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">32199</field>
		<field name="title">South (United States of America)</field>
		<field name="main">other destinations</field>
		<field name="name">other destinations</field>
		<field name="content">Appalachian Trail    Blue Ridge Parkway    Cumberland Gap National Historical Park    Great Smoky Mountains National Park    Hilton Head Island , South Carolina   Mississippi Delta    Natchez Trace     Outer Banks    Shenandoah Valley</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">32200</field>
		<field name="title">Wayne County (Ohio)</field>
		<field name="main">other destinations</field>
		<field name="name">other destinations</field>
		<field name="content">Amish Country - Not as predominant as its neighbor to the south, Holmes County, Wayne County has Amish sightings through much of its central and southern regions. The southern portion of the county is where a number of Amish communities can be found. Amish themed shops and restaurants dot the landscape throughout Wayne County.</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">32201</field>
		<field name="title">Cross Timbers</field>
		<field name="main">other destinations</field>
		<field name="name">other destinations</field>
		<field name="content">Dinosaur Valley State Park  Lake Bridgeport  Lake Ray Roberts  Lake Lewisville</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">32202</field>
		<field name="title">Jackson County (Florida)</field>
		<field name="main">other destinations</field>
		<field name="name">other destinations</field>
		<field name="content">Florida Caverns State Park  Three Rivers State Park</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">32203</field>
		<field name="title">Stark County (Ohio)</field>
		<field name="main">other destinations</field>
		<field name="name">other destinations</field>
		<field name="content">Quail Hollow State Park is in  Hartville .</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">32204</field>
		<field name="title">Door County (Wisconsin)</field>
		<field name="main">other destinations</field>
		<field name="name">other destinations</field>
		<field name="content">Kangaroo Lake Located almost in the center of the peninsula, between the two shores, close to Baileys Harbor.</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">32205</field>
		<field name="title">Inyo County</field>
		<field name="main">other destinations</field>
		<field name="name">other destinations</field>
		<field name="content">Mt. Whitney  – On the east side of the Great Western Divide, Mt. Whitney stands 14,496nbsp;ft/4,418m, the tallest mountain in the contiguous United States.  Hikers reach the summit through Whitney Portal, 13 miles west of Lone Pine.  It’s a 10.7 mile hike and requires planning, a wilderness permit and careful attention to advisories regarding the precautions of hiking at high altitudes, obtained within the Eastern Sierra InterAgency Visitor’s Center, south of Lone Pine.  Rock Creek Canyon – Between Bishop and Mammoth Lakes is picture-perfect Rock Creek Canyon.  Rugged Eastern Sierra sawtooth peaks rise above emerald meadows, populated with fluttering aspens and cut my meandering clear streams.  The Backcountry – Follow CA-168 west from Bishop, 23 miles to trails that lead to the Green Lakes, Treasure Lakes and Bishop Pass.  The pass is an 11-mile hike beyond the end of the road at 11,980nbsp;ft/3,651 m.  Bring a fishing rod for entertainment along the way.   Inyo National Forest  and the  John Muir Wilderness  – For complete retreat, backpack or take a mule pack trip to the high country; to dozens upon dozens of remote glassine lakes with romantic names like Lake Helen of Troy, Elinore Lake, Moonlight Lake and the Treasure Lakes. You will understand why John Muir wrote, “Climb the mountains, and get their good tidings.”  Few experiences are as emotionally satiating as being in the rarified air of the Eastern High Sierra in settings whose beauty defy description.   Palisade Glacier  – The southernmost glacier in the U.S. and the largest in the Sierra Nevada is located west of Big Pine and is visible from U.S. 395.  The glacier sits at the base of Palisade Crest in the North Fork Basin.  The scenery attracts hikers to trails that follow the ancient glacier.   Manzanar National Historic Site  – During World War II, people of Japanese ancestry, including American citizens, were brought here to the Manzanar War Relocation Center.  An interpretive center is in the camp’s former auditorium.  Audio tours are offered.  (760) 878-2194,      Ancient Bristlecone Forest  – Thirty-six miles east of Big Pine grow the oldest living trees.  The oldest of them, Methuselah, is estimated to be nearly 4,800 years old.  Several groves of the venerable trees can be seen.</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">32206</field>
		<field name="title">Shenandoah Valley</field>
		<field name="main">other destinations</field>
		<field name="name">other destinations</field>
		<field name="content">Luray Caverns    New Market Battlefield    Natural Bridge    Shenandoah National Park</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">32207</field>
		<field name="title">Shasta County</field>
		<field name="main">other destinations</field>
		<field name="name">other destinations</field>
		<field name="content">Lassen Volcanic National Park    Whiskeytown National Recreation Area</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">32208</field>
		<field name="title">Santa Rosa County</field>
		<field name="main">other destinations</field>
		<field name="name">other destinations</field>
		<field name="content">Blackwater River State Park is a Florida State Park located fifteen miles northeast of Milton, near Harold, off U.S. 90. A favorite destination for canoeists and kayakers, Blackwater River offers opportunities for a variety of outdoor recreation. The river is one of the purest sand-bottom rivers in the nation. The park has such amenities as birding, boating, canoeing, fishing, hiking, kayaking, picnicking areas, swimming, tubing, wildlife viewing and full camping facilities. The main picnicking area has covered picnicking pavilions, restrooms, and a spacious parking lot. Bring your tubes and enjoy a leisurely float down the river to the Deaton Bridge. It is a short 1 mile hike back to the parking lot to retrieve your vehicle. Very kid friendly park with a variety of areas for swimming.</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">32209</field>
		<field name="title">St. Johns County (Florida)</field>
		<field name="main">other destinations</field>
		<field name="name">other destinations</field>
		<field name="content">Anastasia State Recreation Area, located off SR A1A, about 1.5 miles (3.3 km) from downtown St. Augustine. The park has a variety of wildlife, birds and plants in a setting of beaches, tidal salt marsh, and hammock. Recreational activities include bird watching, camping, fishing, sun bathing, surfing, sail boarding, swimming, kayaking, hiking and picnicking. Amenities include a campground and nature trails.  Faver-Dykes State Park, located 15 miles south of St. Augustine, near the intersection of I-95 and US 1, and bordering Pellicer Creek, a designated state canoe trail. Activities include fishing, picnicking, boating, canoeing, camping and wildlife viewing.  Fort Mose Historic State Park, a U.S. National Historic Landmark, located two miles north of St. Augustine, on the eastern edge of a marsh. It is also a Florida State Park. Also spelled Fort Moosa or Fort Mossa. Fort Mose was the first free black settlement legally sanctioned, in 1738, in what would become the United States.</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">32210</field>
		<field name="title">Levy County (Florida)</field>
		<field name="main">other destinations</field>
		<field name="name">other destinations</field>
		<field name="content">Cedar Key State Museum is a Florida State Park located in Cedar Key, Florida. An important feature of the museum is the St. Clair Whitman house. The house depicts life in Cedar Key circa 1920 - 1930 and focuses on the life of St. Clair Whitman and his collections of sea shells and Indian artifacts. In addition to the museum, there is a short nature trail. Among the wildlife of the park are gray squirrels, doves, mockingbirds, Blue Jays, woodpeckers, and green tree frogs. The museum is open Thursday through Monday from 9:00 a.m. to 5:00 p.m. The museum is closed on Tuesday and Wednesday, and on Christmas.   Cedar Keys National Wildlife Refuge   Cedar Key Scrub State Reserve is a Florida State Park, located six miles (10 km) northeast of Cedar Key on State Road 24, and has a picnic shelter, tables, and grills. The scrub is dominated by species such as sand live oak, myrtle oak, and Chapmans oak, along with rusty lyonia, and saw palmetto. Hikers and off-road bicyclists who want to experience a mosaic of Florida habitats will find it on the miles of trails that wind through the park. The shallow waters and numerous creeks near the salt marshes are ideal for canoeing and kayaking. Rental canoes and kayaks are available in the city of Cedar Key.   Lower Suwannee National Wildlife Refuge</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">32211</field>
		<field name="title">Le Flore County</field>
		<field name="main">other destinations</field>
		<field name="name">other destinations</field>
		<field name="content">Talimena Drive in the fall   Talimena Drive  from  Talihina ,  Oklahoma  to  Mena ,  Arkansas  54 Mile scenic drive in Oklahoma and Arkansas and a National Scenic Byway along the ridge of the Ouachita Mountains and the Ouachita National Forest.</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">32212</field>
		<field name="title">Central Idaho</field>
		<field name="main">other destinations</field>
		<field name="name">other destinations</field>
		<field name="content">Custer Ghost Town   Sun Valley  -- the first great ski resort in the U.S.  Craters of the Moon National Monument  -- volcanic park with vast fields of seemingly lifeless lava, fun lava tubes to explore  Sawtooth National Recreation Area  Largest national recreation are in the United States</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">32213</field>
		<field name="title">Upper Peninsula</field>
		<field name="main">other destinations</field>
		<field name="name">other destinations</field>
		<field name="content">Les Cheneaux Islands    Hiawatha National Forest  and  Ottawa National Forest    Huron National Wildlife Refuge       Isle Royale National Park       Seney Wildlife Refuge    Pictured Rocks National Lakeshore    Tahquamenon Falls</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">32214</field>
		<field name="title">New York (state)</field>
		<field name="main">other destinations</field>
		<field name="name">other destinations</field>
		<field name="content">Adirondack High Peaks  — the tallest mountains in the largest state park in the United States  Catskills  — Largely rural, wild, and mountainous, the Catskills are a popular vacation destination  Chautauqua Institution  — more-or-less a summer camp for adults, founded in 1874  Darien Lake  — the roller coaster capital of New York  Fire Island National Seashore  — a barrier island in  Long Island  with great beaches  Lake George  — boating, lakeside activities, and a big amusement park  Letchworth State Park  — see the Genesee River gorge and its three large, scenic waterfalls  Niagara Falls  — a powerful and awe-inspiring set of waterfalls on the Canadian border, and the "honeymoon capital of the world"  Thousand Islands  — a scenic vacation spot for the rich and famous, right on the Canadian border</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">32215</field>
		<field name="title">East Bay</field>
		<field name="main">other destinations</field>
		<field name="name">other destinations</field>
		<field name="content">Eugene ONeill National Historic Site  - Americas only Nobel Prize winning playwright, Eugene ONeill, chose to live in Northern California at the climax of his writing career. Isolated from the world and within the walls of his home, ONeill wrote his final and most memorable plays; The Iceman Cometh, Long Days Journey Into Night, and A Moon for the Misbegotten. Reservations are required to visit this site.   John Muir National Historic Site  - John Muir National Historic Site preserves the Victorian home of the noted author and preservationist. Surrounded by almost 9 acres of fruit orchards and 326 acres of oak woodland, the site today is just a small piece of the original 2,600 acre ranch. The United States is forever indebted to the "Father of the National Park Service" for helping to preserve this countries greatest treasures.   Port Chicago Naval Magazine National Memorial - Concord Naval Weapons Station  - At Port Chicago Naval Magazine, 320 men were instantly killed when the munitions ships they were loading with ammunition for the Pacific theatre troops mysteriously exploded.  Rosie the Riveter WWII Home Front National Historical Park  - Rosie the Riveter/World War II Home Front National Historical Park, located in the wartime boomtown of Richmond, preserves and interprets the stories and places of our nations home front response to World War II.</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">32216</field>
		<field name="title">Green County</field>
		<field name="main">other destinations</field>
		<field name="name">Swiss Center of North America</field>
		<field name="phone">+1 608  527-6565</field>
		<field name="address">507 Durst Rd, New Glarus</field>
		<field name="email">info@theswisscenter.org</field>
		<field name="url">http://www.theswisscenter.org/</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">32217</field>
		<field name="title">Ashtabula County</field>
		<field name="main">other destinations</field>
		<field name="name">other destinations</field>
		<field name="content">Geneva State Park, northern Ashtabula County, on Lake Erie,   4499 Padanarum Road,  Geneva .  A full facility campground with electricity, showers and flush toilets.  Deluxe Cedar Cabins on the Lake Erie lakefront, six-lane boat ramp, canteen, concession area, 383 docks, three miles of multi-use trails, 300-foot guarded swimming beach and Geneva Lake Resort Lodge and Conference Center.  Pymatuning State Park, on the north part of the border of Ohio and  Pennsylvania . 6260 Pymatuning Lake Rd., Andover. Twenty-six family cottages, thirty-two standard cottages, beach,  331 camping sites have electric hookups, 21 sites are non-electric, nature center, basketball, volleyball courts, playgrounds, 14,000 acre lake,  five boat-launch ramps, fishing, hunting, two miles of well marked trails, ice skating, ice boating, ice fishing and cross-country skiing.       Grand Valley - Scenic region in Ashtabula County made up of rural green areas and woodlands. It also includes the communities of Colebrook, Hartsgrove,  Orwell ,  Roaming Shores , Rome and Windsor. In this region you can find the worlds largest statue of Our Lady of Guadalupe at the Servants of Mary Center for Peace in Windsor, and recreational activies such as hunting, fishing and camping year round.    Pymatuning - Indian term translated as "the crooked-mouthed mans dwelling place." Lake and state park in the southeast portion of Ashtabula county which extends into Pennsylvania. Outdoor recreation in the area includes camping, boating, hiking, and swimming. The Grand River is found north of the lake off St. Rt. 322 and St. Rt. 6.</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">32218</field>
		<field name="title">Hampden County</field>
		<field name="main">other destinations</field>
		<field name="name">other destinations</field>
		<field name="content">Wales   Granville  - Granville State Forest</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">32219</field>
		<field name="title">Louisiana</field>
		<field name="main">other destinations</field>
		<field name="name">other destinations</field>
		<field name="content">Saint Bernard Parish , includes  Chalmette ,  Site of the Battle of New Orleans National Monument  Great River Road  - Between New Orleans Baton Rouge.  New Roads  - Small and Peaceful, yet energetic town on the banks of False River.  Plaquemines Parish  area furtherest down the Mississippi River  St. Tammany Parish   Terrebonne Parish   Woodworth  - One of the fastest growing communities in central Louisiana.</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">32220</field>
		<field name="title">Okaloosa County</field>
		<field name="main">other destinations</field>
		<field name="name">other destinations</field>
		<field name="content">Choctawhatchee National Forest    Gulf Islands National Seashore</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">32221</field>
		<field name="title">Rhode Island</field>
		<field name="main">other destinations</field>
		<field name="name">other destinations</field>
		<field name="content">Block Island  - Island off southern coast of RI.  This island packs great scenery and great beaches into a small, walkable and bikable area.</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">32222</field>
		<field name="title">Alaska</field>
		<field name="main">other destinations</field>
		<field name="name">other destinations</field>
		<field name="content">Cape Krusenstern National Monument  ndash; North of the Arctic Circle, Cape Krusenstern National Monument stretches 70 miles along the Chukchi Sea shoreline. Beach ridges provide evidence of 5000 years of human activity.    Denali National Park  ndash; Whether climbing or admiring, the crowning jewel of North America’s highest peak is the awe inspiring 20,320-foot Mount McKinley    Gates of the Arctic National Park  ndash; Traveling through this vast wilderness you will discover craggy ridges, glacier carved valleys and fragile flowers    Glacier Bay National Park  - marine wilderness of Glacier Bay National Park and Preserve includes tidewater glaciers, snow-capped mountain ranges, ocean coastlines, deep fjords, and freshwater rivers and lakes.    Katmai National Park  - famous for volcanoes, brown bears, pristine waterways with abundant fish, remote wilderness, and a rugged coastline    Kenai Fjords National Park  - a land where the ice age still lingers where glaciers, earthquakes, and ocean storms are the architects.    Upper Kenai River  - a great place almost every time of year to catch rainbow trout and salmon, if you know what youre doing so long as the river isnt frozen there are fish for you. Also a great place for roadside bear viewing; just dont get too close!   Kobuk Valley National Park  - noted for the Great Kobuk Sand Dunes and caribou migration routes. The park offers backcountry camping, hiking, backpacking, and dog sledding.    Lake Clark National Park and Preserve  - The Park was created to protect scenic beauty (volcanoes, glaciers, wild rivers and waterfalls), populations of fish and wildlife, watersheds essential for red salmon, and the traditional lifestyle of local residents. Lake Clarks spectacular scenery provides a true wilderness experience for those who visit.    Skilak Lake  - another great place for monster rainbow trout, also one of the most beautiful areas of the state, camping, hiking, boating, fishing, and hunting are all great  options for a fun time. Just a great place to spend a quiet weekend with family, friends, or just the fish.    Wrangell-St. Elias National Park and Preserve  - Chugach, Wrangell, and Saint Elias mountain ranges converge here in what is often referred to as the "mountain kingdom of North America." It has the continents largest assemblage of glaciers and greatest collection of peaks above 16,000 feet.    Yukon - Charley Rivers National Preserve  - along the Canadian border in central Alaska</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">32223</field>
		<field name="title">Prince William County</field>
		<field name="main">other destinations</field>
		<field name="name">other destinations</field>
		<field name="content">Manassas National Battlefield Park,   . Site of both the the first and second Battles of Bull Run.</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">32224</field>
		<field name="title">Oahu</field>
		<field name="main">other destinations</field>
		<field name="name">other destinations</field>
		<field name="content">Waikiki   Pearl Harbor</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">32225</field>
		<field name="title">Kansas</field>
		<field name="main">other destinations</field>
		<field name="name">other destinations</field>
		<field name="content">Lewis Clark National Historic Trail  - Between May 1804 and September 1806, 32 men, one woman, and a baby traveled from the plains of the Midwest to the shores of the Pacific Ocean. They called themselves the Corps of Discovery   Fort Scott National Historic site, ground zero for the Bleeding Kansas term, where the states slave policy of yesteryear can be thoroughly studied</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">32226</field>
		<field name="title">Sumter County (Florida)</field>
		<field name="main">other destinations</field>
		<field name="name">other destinations</field>
		<field name="content">Dade Battlefield Historic State Park is a Florida State Park located on County Road 603 between I-75 (Exit 314) and U.S. 301. The 80 acre park includes 40 acres of pine flatwoods and a live oak hammock. Also called the Dade Massacre site, It preserves the Second Seminole War battlefield where Seminole Indian warriors fought soldiers under the command of Major Francis L. Dade on December 28, 1835. Each year, on the weekend after Christmas (as close to the original date as possible), the Dade Battlefield Society sponsors a reenactment of the battle that started the Second Seminole War. Recreational activities include picnicking, viewing exhibits at the visitor center, and wildlife viewing. Among the wildlife of the park are gopher tortoises, woodpeckers, songbirds, hawks, and indigo snakes. Amenities include a playground, a picnic area with covered shelters, a nature trail, a 6.2 mile FVA (Florida Volksport Association) trail, and a recreation hall.</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">32227</field>
		<field name="title">Wyoming</field>
		<field name="main">other destinations</field>
		<field name="name">other destinations</field>
		<field name="content">Bighorn Canyon National Recreation Area  — Geologic forces have distorted and bowed once-level layers of rock into 1,000-foot cliffs that loom over the Bighorn Lake.    Black Hills National Forest  — The Black Hills straddle South Dakota and Wyoming and stand in contrast to the prairies, rolling from 5,000-6,000 feet in elevation.   Devils Tower National Monument  — Made famous in Steven Speilbergs "Close Encounters of the Third Kind," the 500-foot monolith is the core of an ancient volcano.    Flaming Gorge National Recreation Area  — The canyon surrounding this giant reservoir was named by explorer John Wesley, who upon first looking at the red gorge, believed that it was on fire.    Fossil Butte National Monument  — The monument contains 8,198 acres and protects a portion of the largest deposit of freshwater fish fossils in the world.   Grand Teton National Park  — This jagged range in the Rocky Mountains is a wondrous playground for climbers, hikers, skiers and all outdoor enthusiasts.    Yellowstone National Park  — The nations first national park was set aside in 1872 to preserve its geysers, hot springs and thermal areas, as well as the areas incredible wildlife and rugged beauty.</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">32228</field>
		<field name="title">Indiana</field>
		<field name="main">other destinations</field>
		<field name="name">other destinations</field>
		<field name="content">Monument Circle in Indianapolis mdash; a city full of monumental memorials   George Rogers Clark National Historical Park    Hoosier National Forest   Indiana Dunes National Lakeshore    John Mellencamps Mansion  mdash; in the small town that song was about  Lincoln Boyhood National Memorial</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">32229</field>
		<field name="title">Arctic Alaska</field>
		<field name="main">other destinations</field>
		<field name="name">other destinations</field>
		<field name="content">Arctic National Wildlife Refuge  - Yes, that one.  Gates Of The Arctic National Park  - home to six Wild and Scenic Rivers that offer opportunities for unparalleled wilderness experiences Inupiat Heritage Center - On the rooftop of the world, the Iñupiat Heritage Center in  Barrow  tells the story of the Iñupiat people   Western Arctic National Parklands  - Western Arctic National Parklands is a unit which includes:   Bering Land Bridge National Preserve  - During the Cold War the people of Beringia were separated.   Cape Krusenstern National Monument  - stretches 70 miles along the Chukchi Sea shoreline   Kobuk Valley National Park and Preserve  ndash; Ancient arctic sand dunes and a sub-arctic river that traverses the boreal forest, this park harbors archeological sites more than 10,000 years old, and supports small communities of inland Inupiat peoples.   Noatak National Preserve  ndash; As one of North Americas largest mountain-ringed river basins with an intact ecosystem, the Noatak River environs features some of the Arctics finest arrays of plants and animals.</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">32230</field>
		<field name="title">Providence County</field>
		<field name="main">other destinations</field>
		<field name="name">other destinations</field>
		<field name="content">The southern portion of the Blackstone Valley National Corridor is encompassed by Providence County.</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">32231</field>
		<field name="title">Butler County (Ohio)</field>
		<field name="main">other destinations</field>
		<field name="name">other destinations</field>
		<field name="content">Hueston Woods State Park and Resort Lodge, Southwest corner of  Preble County , northwest corner of Butler County, north of  Oxford . North of SR 27 on Route 732. Located in Butler and Preble counties, nearly 3,000 acres. Lodge: 96-rooms, dining room, snack bar, gift shop, meeting rooms, lounge, indoor, outdoor swimming pools, game room, and lighted tennis court. Cottages: 25 cottages, two bedrooms, bath, kitchen, living room, screened porch. Two Premium Cottages. Ten Efficiency Cottages. All cottages have cooking, eating utensils, towels, and bedding. Camping: 252 campsites, electrical outlets, showers, flush toilets, laundry, trailer waste station,  236 non-electric campsites, with vault-type latrines. Three camper cabins,  built-in bunks, air conditioning, and an outdoor gas grill, 28 horseman campsites and pet camping. 10 miles of hiking trails, 18 miles of bridle trails,  12 miles for mountain biking. 18-hole, 7,005-yard, par 72 golf course, driving ranges open from March until November.  Acton Lake, boating, launch ramps, public docks, fishing pier, 1,500-foot swimming beach, concession stand, bathhouse,  volleyball court, horseshoes, miniature golf, playground, basketball court, Nature Center, fossil hunts and playground.</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">32232</field>
		<field name="title">Southern Oregon</field>
		<field name="main">other destinations</field>
		<field name="name">other destinations</field>
		<field name="content">Oregon Caves National Monument - family focused opportunities to explore a marble cave, visit a National Historic Landmark (the Oregon Caves Chateau), hike trails through ancient forests, and earn a Junior Ranger Badge.   Rogue River, Umpqua, and Siskiyou National Forests make up a large part of southern Oregons mountain wilderness, including many campgrounds, picnic areas, and trails.    Crater Lake National Park  is a popular destination in the mountains, about 90 minutes northeast of Medford. One of the deepest lakes in the world, Crater Lake is also host to a network of hiking and biking trails.   The Cascade Mountains feature prominently in southern Oregons temperate landscape.</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">32233</field>
		<field name="title">Minnesota</field>
		<field name="main">other destinations</field>
		<field name="name">other destinations</field>
		<field name="content">Mall of America, Bloomington   Mall of America in  Bloomington   The Minnesota Zoo in  Apple Valley .   Minnesota Landscape Arboretum  in  Chaska    Boundary Waters Canoe Area    Flandrau State Park    Itasca State Park    Lake Superior    Pipestone National Monument    Voyageurs National Park</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">32234</field>
		<field name="title">Hillsborough County (Florida)</field>
		<field name="main">other destinations</field>
		<field name="name">other destinations</field>
		<field name="content">Alafia River State Park is a Florida State Park, located 10 miles southeast of Tampa on County Road 39. The park has such amenities as bicycling, birding, canoeing, fishing, hiking, horse trails, picnicking areas, wildlife viewing and full camping facilities. This park is especially great for mountain bikers as a Mountain bike club has developed a great amount of advanced trails.</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">32235</field>
		<field name="title">Tennessee</field>
		<field name="main">other destinations</field>
		<field name="name">other destinations</field>
		<field name="content">Appalachian National Scenic Trail    Big South Fork National River and Recreation Area    Doe River    Great Smoky Mountains National Park    Obed Wild and Scenic River    Overmountain Victory National Historic Trail    Watauga River   Land Between the Lakes National Recreation Area   Dollywood   Dollys Splash Country</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">32236</field>
		<field name="title">DeKalb County (Georgia)</field>
		<field name="main">other destinations</field>
		<field name="name">other destinations</field>
		<field name="content">Stone Mountain Park</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">32237</field>
		<field name="title">North Dakota</field>
		<field name="main">other destinations</field>
		<field name="name">other destinations</field>
		<field name="content">Theodore Roosevelt National Park  - The park has two units, the North Unit and the South Unit, both distinctly different.</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">32238</field>
		<field name="title">Mount Desert Island</field>
		<field name="main">other destinations</field>
		<field name="name">other destinations</field>
		<field name="content">Bar Harbor bay    Acadia National Park   Bar Island, off  Bar Harbor    Blue Hill    Ellsworth    Frenchboro , off  Southwest Harbor</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">32239</field>
		<field name="title">Wasatch Range</field>
		<field name="main">other destinations</field>
		<field name="name">other destinations</field>
		<field name="content">Alta  - Ski resort.  Sundance - Ski resort.  Great Salt Lake - Large saltwater lake.   Antelope Island  - An island in the Great Salt Lake.  Utah Lake - Freshwater lake in Utah Valley.</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">32240</field>
		<field name="title">Great Plains</field>
		<field name="main">other destinations</field>
		<field name="name">other destinations</field>
		<field name="content">Badlands National Park   Black Hills National Forest   Chimney Rock National Historic Site   Jewel Cave National Monument   Mount Rushmore National Memorial   Scotts Bluff National Monument   Theodore Roosevelt National Park</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">32241</field>
		<field name="title">Big Bend Country</field>
		<field name="main">other destinations</field>
		<field name="name">other destinations</field>
		<field name="content">Big Bend National Park    Guadalupe Mountains National Park    Hueco Tanks State Historic Site    Monahans Sandhills State Park</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">32242</field>
		<field name="title">Washington County (Florida)</field>
		<field name="main">other destinations</field>
		<field name="name">other destinations</field>
		<field name="content">Falling Waters State Park - a 171-acre Florida State Park located three miles south of Chipley, off State Road 77A, in northwestern Florida. The park contains a 73-foot waterfall, the highest in the state. The park has such amenities as birding, fishing, hiking, picnicking areas, swimming, wildlife viewing and full camping facilities. Concessions are also available.</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">32243</field>
		<field name="title">Iowa</field>
		<field name="main">other destinations</field>
		<field name="name">other destinations</field>
		<field name="content">Amana Colonies    Effigy Mounds National Monument    Iowa Great Lakes  "Okoboji" serves as a popular in-state getaway, for boating, beaching, theme parks and more  Lewis and Clark National Historic Trail  - Between May 1804 and September 1806, 32 men, one woman, and a baby traveled from the plains of the Midwest to the shores of the Pacific Ocean. They called themselves the Corps of Discovery</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">32244</field>
		<field name="title">Liberty County</field>
		<field name="main">other destinations</field>
		<field name="name">other destinations</field>
		<field name="content">Apalachicola National Forest</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">32245</field>
		<field name="title">Tuolumne County</field>
		<field name="main">other destinations</field>
		<field name="name">other destinations</field>
		<field name="content">Yosemite National Park</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">32246</field>
		<field name="title">Bristol County (Rhode Island)</field>
		<field name="main">other destinations</field>
		<field name="name">other destinations</field>
		<field name="content">Bristol Countrys location is spectacular. Only an hour and a half drive to the city of Boston, Massachusetts, and a three to four hour (depending on traffic) drive to New York City, New York.  However, if looking for a day trip try Providence, Rhode Island, located only 15 minutes away from Barrington from Route 114 to I-195 north. Providence has many things to offer such as the Providence Place Mall, outdoor ice rink, Thayer Street, and night life.  Also, the city of Warwick, Rhode Island provides many shops and restaurants off of Route 2, as well as the Warwick Mall.</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">32247</field>
		<field name="title">Ross County</field>
		<field name="main">other destinations</field>
		<field name="name">other destinations</field>
		<field name="content">Great Seal State Park, 635 Rocky Rd.,  Chillicothe . 15-site campground, pressurized water, vault latrines, playground, shelterhouse,  pet camping, shelterhouse, horse camp, twenty-two miles of trails, hunting,  playground equipment, disc golf course, volleyball, basketball, horseshoe court. Hopewell Culture National Historical Park in  Chillicothe . A group of 23 earthen mounds built by the Hopewell culture, 200 BC to AD 500. Roscoe Village in  Coshocton . Scioto Trail State Park, south of  Chillicothe , east of Route 23 on CR 372.  55 campsites,  40 with electricity, latrines, water, fire rings, picnic tables are provided. A secluded hike-in camp near Stewart Lake has 18 non-electric sites.  Two rustic camper cabins are available. Fishing, hunting, twelve miles of hiking trails, 17 miles of bridle trails, nature center, basketball, horseshoe courts, playground, games and sporting equipment to registered campers, basketball, horseshoe courts and volleyball court. Sugarloaf Mountain Amphitheatre - Tecumseh!  in  Chillicothe .  Huge outdoor stages. Tar Hollow State Park, east part of Ross County, east of  Chillicothe , at 16396 Tar Hollow Road, Laurelville,  71 sites with electrical hookups, 11 non-electric sites, 12 walk-in sites, and 5 primitive sites along a backpack trail. Equipped with showers, laundry facilities, pit latrines and a dump station. The beach is close by. Boating with electric motors only, permitted on the 15-acre Pine Lake. Perfect for canoes and rowboats.</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">32248</field>
		<field name="title">Clinton County (New York)</field>
		<field name="main">other destinations</field>
		<field name="name">other destinations</field>
		<field name="content">Redford</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">32249</field>
		<field name="title">North Carolina</field>
		<field name="main">other destinations</field>
		<field name="name">other destinations</field>
		<field name="content">Great Smoky Mountains National Park  - The most visited National Park in the entire country.   Appalachian National Scenic Trail    Blue Ridge Parkway  - One of the most visited units of the National Park System.  Cape Hatteras National Seashore   Cape Lookout National Seashore    Outer Banks  - Known for its famous lighthouses and wild horses.   Pinehurst  - Famous golf courses.   Outer Banks - near Corolla, NC</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">32250</field>
		<field name="title">Stewart County (Georgia)</field>
		<field name="main">other destinations</field>
		<field name="name">other destinations</field>
		<field name="content">Providence Canyon State Park  Florence Marina State Park  Eufaula National Wildlife Refugee</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">32251</field>
		<field name="title">Contra Costa County</field>
		<field name="main">other destinations</field>
		<field name="name">other destinations</field>
		<field name="content">Eugene ONeill National Historic Site  - Americas only Nobel Prize winning playwright, Eugene ONeill, chose to live in Northern California at the climax of his writing career. Isolated from the world and within the walls of his home, ONeill wrote his final and most memorable plays; The Iceman Cometh, Long Days Journey Into Night, and A Moon for the Misbegotten. Reservations are required to visit this site.   John Muir National Historic Site  - John Muir National Historic Site preserves the Victorian home of the noted author and preservationist. Surrounded by almost 9 acres of fruit orchards and 326 acres of oak woodland, the site today is just a small piece of the original 2,600 acre ranch. The United States is forever indebted to the "Father of the National Park Service" for helping to preserve this countries greatest treasures.   Port Chicago Naval Magazine National Memorial - Concord Naval Weapons Station  - At Port Chicago Naval Magazine, 320 men were instantly killed when the munitions ships they were loading with ammunition for the Pacific theatre troops mysteriously exploded.  Rosie the Riveter WWII Home Front National Historical Park  - Rosie the Riveter/World War II Home Front National Historical Park, located in the wartime boomtown of Richmond, preserves and interprets the stories and places of our nations home front response to World War II.</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">32252</field>
		<field name="title">Texas</field>
		<field name="main">other destinations</field>
		<field name="name">other destinations</field>
		<field name="content">Big Bend National Park   Big Thicket National Preserve   Guadalupe Mountains National Park   Palo Duro Canyon   South Padre Island</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">32253</field>
		<field name="title">Sussex County (New Jersey)</field>
		<field name="main">other destinations</field>
		<field name="name">other destinations</field>
		<field name="content">Fishing, Boating, Shopping and more around Lake Hopatcong -  Lake Hopatcong ,  Hopatcong ,  Sparta (New Jersey)   Camping at Stokes State Forest   , 1 Coursen Road, Branchville, NJ 07826. +1 (973) 948-3820.</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">32254</field>
		<field name="title">Atlantic County</field>
		<field name="main">other destinations</field>
		<field name="name">other destinations</field>
		<field name="content">Dorothy  (also known as Weymouth Township)</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">32255</field>
		<field name="title">Trumbull County</field>
		<field name="main">other destinations</field>
		<field name="name">other destinations</field>
		<field name="content">Mosquito Lake State Park, 1439 State Route 305, Cortland. 234 campsites, 218  have electrical hookups, boat launching area, unlimited horsepower boating on 7,850-acre lake,  fishing, hunting, several hiking trails, ten miles of bridle trails, snowmobilers access to 14 miles of shoreline and 15 miles of wooded trails, mountain biking is permitted on 5 miles of multiple-use trail, basketball, volleyball, horseshoe courts and 600-foot beach.</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">32256</field>
		<field name="title">Great Lakes</field>
		<field name="main">other destinations</field>
		<field name="name">other destinations</field>
		<field name="content">The Magnum XL200 at Cedar Point    Cedar Point   Indiana Dunes National Lakeshore   Lake Erie Islands   Mackinac Island   Prince Edward County   Sleeping Bear Dunes National Lakeshore   Thousand Islands</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">32257</field>
		<field name="title">Utah</field>
		<field name="main">other destinations</field>
		<field name="name">other destinations</field>
		<field name="content">Delicate Arch in Arches National Park .]]  Green River Overlook in Canyonlands National Park ]]  Utah has an extraordinary number of national parks and monuments.  The following is subdivided into "National parks and monuments" and "Other" as an aid to the reader:</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">32258</field>
		<field name="title">Front Range</field>
		<field name="main">other destinations</field>
		<field name="name">other destinations</field>
		<field name="content">Ground Squirrel in Rocky Mountain National Park  ]]  Arapahoe Roosevelt National Forest  Chautauqua Park  - Home of one of the few remaining Chautauqua lecture halls (a National Historic Landmark), this recreation area abuts the jutting red sandstone crags of the Flatirons, a symbol of  Boulder .  Eldora Ski Area   Grandby   Hohnholz Lakes State Wildlife Area  Murphy State Wildlife Area Owl Mountain State Wildlife Area   Rocky Mountain National Park    Routt National Forest</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">32259</field>
		<field name="title">Prince George's County</field>
		<field name="main">other destinations</field>
		<field name="name">other destinations</field>
		<field name="content">Six Flags America , amusement park featuring roller coasters, waterpark, and kids attractions  Watkins Regional Park  Joint Base Andrews  Greenbelt Park</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">32260</field>
		<field name="title">Rio Grande Valley</field>
		<field name="main">other destinations</field>
		<field name="name">other destinations</field>
		<field name="content">South Padre Island   Palo Alto Battlefield National Historical Park     World Birding Center</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">32261</field>
		<field name="title">California</field>
		<field name="main">other destinations</field>
		<field name="name">other destinations</field>
		<field name="content">Joshua Tree National Park ]]   Disneyland   Lake Tahoe  mdash; A large, gorgeous lake great for water sports and excellent skiing in the winter.  Napa Valley  mdash; Spas, wine tasting, wine tours.  Big Sur  mdash; one of the most scenic spots along the Pacific Coast Highway</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
</add>