<add>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">51305</field>
		<field name="title">Medicine Park</field>
		<field name="main">people of interest</field>
		<field name="name">people of interest</field>
		<field name="content">Elmer Thomas, the founder of Medicine Park, became a powerful politician in the State of Oklahoma. He went on to serve in the State Senate from 1907-1920, was a Member of the U.S. House of Representatives from 1923-1927 and a United States Senator from 1927-1951.  In the early 1960s Rex and Ruby “Grandma” Leath purchased from the Texas Land Company the building that was originally constructed as The Outside Inn in 1910 and later called The Grand Hotel. They named it The Old Plantation Restaurant. It was listed on the National Historic Register in the 1970s. The restaurant was known for its burgers, catfish, huge sirloin steaks that "hung off the platter," and famous rolls. Rex could always be found behind the bar or in the kitchen, Grandma at someones table telling her tall tales, promoting Medicine Park or giving out her recipe for hot rolls. She was a “one woman Chamber of Commerce.”  In the late 1960s, the need for improving and expanding the utilities infrastructure was becoming apparent to the Park’s residents. The town was officially incorporated as “The Town of Medicine Park” in 1969. Edward A. Hilliary, Jr. was elected as Chairman (mayor) and served as such for 12 years. Early members of the Town Council included: Jack Laughter, RC “Chuck” Gardener and Roy Brown, followed by Rex Leath, “Doc” Dodson and AP Tuck, who served as Police Commissioner. Hilliary installed the first water and sewer systems in Medicine Park. He also owned many businesses in Medicine Park, including Park Propane and Medicine Park Telephone Company, he also partnered with Edna Hennessee to develop Big Rock Mountain Estates.  David and Candace McCoy helped jump start the rebirth of Medicine Park through construction and renovation of businesses and residential houses as well as donations of land and time. In 1995, The Riverside Café, closed for many years, was purchased by the McCoys. The couple worked diligently to restore the café. After they opened for business in August 1996, a new breed of visitor began showing up in town. They loved the steaks, burgers, catfish, friendly atmosphere and the unique community.  Restoration of structures in town began in the late 1990s when a few historic cobblestone cabins were restored by McCoy Development Company, Charley Wright, the Hennessee Family and a few others. Cobblestone Court (a commercial grouping of shops) and the restoration and new construction of numerous cabins and homes on both sides of Medicine Creek, were accomplished through the efforts of McCoy Development Company.  The Park Tavern was opened in 1997 by Bill Patty and his brother in law Tom Zynda. The Tavern was a success and soon became a favorite watering hole for local residents and an icon in Medicine Park’s new found revitalization. Today, it plays hosts to numerous popular annual events.  In 1997, the Old Skating Rink was purchased by David Lott. The facility had originally been constructed as a dance hall in 1920 but had been re-invented as a Skating Rink in the late 1930s and operated seasonally as Medicine Park Skating Rink on an irregular basis through the late 1970s into the early 1980. The Hall hosted numerous concerts 1999-2001 to include Michael Martin Murphey, Rare Earth, Canned Heat, Mitch Ryder The Detroit Wheels, Lovin Spoonful, Iron Butterfly, Dan Hicks and the Hot Licks, The Byrds, Leon Russell, Head East, Hank Thompson, Byron Berline, Big Brother and the Holding Company, 1964-Beatles Tribute, Amazing Rhythm Aces, and more. In early 2002, with the business growing rapidly, short-term debt financing that couldn’t be refinanced in time caused the business to close. However, the public interest the Hall had generated provided a catalyst, bringing numerous new businesses and other economic successes soon following. This set the Town on its current pattern of growth as it heads into the new century.  Throughout the mid-to-late 1990s residents of Medicine Park implemented numerous improvements and established several subsidiary arms of Town government. These included formation of Medicine Park Economic Development Trust Authority (MPEDA), Medicine Park Planning Preservation Committee, a new Police Department and an outstanding Volunteer Fire Department. The Fire Department now has a new Fire Station, more than 20 dedicated and trained volunteers, several state-of-the-art fire trucks and fully equipped emergency response vehicles. In addition, business owners and residents established the Medicine Park Merchants Association and the Wichita Mountains Art Council.</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
</add>