<add>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">63065</field>
		<field name="title">Nevada</field>
		<field name="main">respect</field>
		<field name="name">brothels</field>
		<field name="content">Nevada is the only state in the US where prostitution is not outlawed at the state level, except in the counties around  Las Vegas ,  Reno  and  Carson City .  Other counties are free to allow or outlaw prostitution in licensed brothels. This is a controversial subject with some Nevadans, especially in mixed company.  Tread lightly.  Sheris Ranch, a brothel located in Pahrump.</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">63066</field>
		<field name="title">Nevada</field>
		<field name="main">respect</field>
		<field name="name">mormons</field>
		<field name="content">Members of the Church of Jesus Christ of Latter Day Saints (more commonly known as "Mormons") settled in the Salt Lake valley in Utah in 1847, and soon thereafter began to settle various different areas throughout Utah, and Nevada (which was part of the proposed state of "Deseret" at the time). A few of these settlements include Mormon Station (modern day Genoa) and Mormon Fort (modern day Las Vegas). These settlements were very active in trade with pioneers migrating west to California for the gold rush after 1949. After the state of Deseret was segregated to help form Nevada, Utah, Arizona, and Wyoming, some of the members of the church left, but many stayed. Today Nevada has a significant Mormon population, particularly in Las Vegas, Reno and the lightly populated eastern part.  Mormons, if they strictly follow church teachings, dont drink, are socially conservative and tend to have large families. They can also be well-travelled and fluent in foreign languages because many men (and some women) are sent as missionaries to nations all around the world.  The doctrine of polygamy has been officially disowned since 1890.</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">63067</field>
		<field name="title">Rhode Island</field>
		<field name="main">respect</field>
		<field name="name">respect</field>
		<field name="content">Arguably one of the most gay-friendly states in the U.S., with scores of bars and entertainment venues in Providence, and even a visible "out" community in smaller towns and villages.  Every year around June, Providence holds their Gay Pride Festival downtown. Many people throughout the city attend the festival. Things rarely happen that negatively impact the festival (other than the weather) because Providence is, for the most part, a pretty open minded place. The festival holds many attractions for many people. There are tons of different stalls to see and to buy from on the day of the festival.</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">63068</field>
		<field name="title">North Carolina</field>
		<field name="main">respect</field>
		<field name="name">respect</field>
		<field name="content">The Southern drawl in language is generally charming to most outsiders.  In most cases, mutual respect is expected and southern hospitality is a staple of the area.  This is expressed in a number of ways:  holding doors open for strangers, not honking a car horn unless necessary, and keeping ones voice down when in a crowded room.   As is common in other parts of the South, North Carolinians typically take offense at being stereotyped as "hicks" or "rednecks".  While some rural residents might apply such labels to themselves as a matter of humor, it is not expected that outsiders will follow suit.  It is very strongly advised that visitors treat the locals with the same respect that youd afford to any other group of people, and not attempt to make a joke out of age-old class discrimination.</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">63069</field>
		<field name="title">New York (state)</field>
		<field name="main">respect</field>
		<field name="name">respect</field>
		<field name="content">New York was the birthplace of the gay rights movement in the USA with the Stonewall Rebellion of 1969. New York and  New England  form part of the minority of US states where same-sex marriage is legal. The majority of New Yorkers are socially tolerant and used to diversity, even in upstate areas that are perceived to be more conservative than New York City. It is important to remember that New York City was one of the targets of the 9-11 attacks, and the memory of 9-11 is still very fresh in the minds of New Yorkers, especially in New York City. Some may not wish to discuss the topic of 9-11, while others will gladly share their personal stories with you.</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">63070</field>
		<field name="title">Warm Springs (Oregon)</field>
		<field name="main">respect</field>
		<field name="name">respect</field>
		<field name="content">Warm Springs is the primcipal settlement of the Warm Springs Indian Reservation. As this is land owned by the Native Americans, please follow all laws and regulations, do not freely attempt to "explore" the area, and use the same common-sense guidelines of respect that you would on other Indian lands.</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">63071</field>
		<field name="title">Four Corners</field>
		<field name="main">respect</field>
		<field name="name">respect</field>
		<field name="content">While traveling on Navajo land, remember that you are on a sovereign, self-governing nation. Obey all the Navajo tribal laws and regulations.  Do not litter; place your refuse in trash containers.  Visitors should be respectful when it comes to photography. Remember, the Navajo at the Monument are people, not props in your photograph. When you do take photos of people, keep in mind that a gratuity is always appreciated. Special permits are required by the Navajo nation when photographing for commercial use.  Please be sure to practice appropriate sensitivity in your dealings with any Native Americans you encounter. While both the Navajo and Utes claim the Four Corners area as their ancestral homelands, both people were subjected to forced relocation, military incursions and internment on reservations by the U.S. government. This 19th and early 20th century history is understandably still a sore spot. Most importantly, treat Native Americans with the same respect and courtesy that youd wish to receive.</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">63072</field>
		<field name="title">Allentown</field>
		<field name="main">respect</field>
		<field name="name">respect</field>
		<field name="content">As in many parts of the country, citizens may not want to share religious or political views. The city in recent years has seen an influx of Spanish speakers, mainly from Puerto Rico and The Dominican Republic.</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">63073</field>
		<field name="title">California</field>
		<field name="main">respect</field>
		<field name="name">respect</field>
		<field name="content">California is filled with a very diverse group of people.  Northern and Southern California have extremely different cultures, while the rural areas in the Central Valley and Eastern portions of the state differ even more significantly.  Like much of the US, sensitive topics include immigration, race, gay rights, and politics.</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">63074</field>
		<field name="title">New Hampshire</field>
		<field name="main">respect</field>
		<field name="name">respect</field>
		<field name="content">New Hampshires LGBT community is relatively obscure when compared with the other New England states, although the census reports it has among the highest concentrations of gay and lesbian residents of any U.S. state. Gay venues do exist in the urbanized far south, but the heavily forested and backwoods north still retain some remarkably homophobic attitudes. The situation is less friendly than in neighboring states.</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">63075</field>
		<field name="title">Idaho</field>
		<field name="main">respect</field>
		<field name="name">respect</field>
		<field name="content">Generally speaking societal norms in Idaho are similar to other areas in the United States. However, Idahoans do tend to be slightly more familiar than others in the country. Especially in rural areas, complete strangers will wave to you as you drive by. Dont be afraid to wave back.  Idahoans are extremely sensitive to any allegation that the state is somehow a neo-Nazi enclave, and will be very quick to inform you otherwise if the subject comes up. This is particularly true in the Coeur dAlene area, which experienced a very small but highly publicized group of neo-Nazis firsthand.   While Idahoans are genuinely proud of their potato-growing heritage, a litany of "spud" jokes and references tends to wear thin quickly.  Conflict between Mormons and non-Mormons is nothing new in Idaho and remains sensitive here, perhaps even more so than in Utah. While anything resembling open hostility on either side is exceptionally rare, the subject can make some people visibly uncomfortable.</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">63076</field>
		<field name="title">Louisiana</field>
		<field name="main">respect</field>
		<field name="name">respect</field>
		<field name="content">Louisiana (as much of the rest of the South), is known to display the stereotypical "Southern hospitality". However, the condition is that you give respect back. The pace of life is often more Mediterranean than other parts of the US. Approach locals with a positive attitude and you are apt to make friends; a gruff impatient attitude may generate resentment rather than promptness.   South Louisiana has a large Cajun population; while English is generally understood everywhere, French is still spoken by many people especially in South West Louisiana. Louisiana Cajun French is a distinct dialect difficult to understand for many speakers of conventional or Parisian French.  The notorious Hurricane Katrina of 2005 particularly affected the South East of Louisiana with one of the worst disasters in U.S. history. Less well known elsewhere but causing significant damage locally were  Hurricane Rita hitting Louisianas South West a month later, and other areas flooded in Hurricane Gustav in 2008. The disasters are still an emotional subject to many Louisianans.  Even those who escaped with little harm often have friends, relatives, and co-workers with more tragic stories. Jokes that you were told elsewhere blaming or insulting Louisianians will bring a negative response here. Some locals may be inclined to share disaster stories with sympathetic visitors, but others prefer not to talk about it--dont push them.</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">63077</field>
		<field name="title">Mecklenburg County (North Carolina)</field>
		<field name="main">respect</field>
		<field name="name">respect</field>
		<field name="content">Southern Comfort rules apply. Though Mecklenburg County has grown rapidly and taken in many thousands of "transplants" from other parts of the nation, it is still relatively slow-paced and polite compared to many other urban areas. This is particularly the case in smaller towns like Matthews, Pineville and Huntersville.  BE WARNED: Locals have a good relationship with newcomers (they have little choice), but they do not like being perceived as "hicks" or "bumpkins". An extremely common complaint is that outsiders tend to compare the area unfavorably to other towns, which may unintentionally come across as condescending or rude.  If you compare Charlotte (or its surrounding areas) to your hometown, be careful to do so graciously so as to avoid this impression.</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">63078</field>
		<field name="title">Iowa</field>
		<field name="main">respect</field>
		<field name="name">respect</field>
		<field name="content">Iowa has been a historically varied state, known for liberal and conservative politicians alike.  It is also an unusually political state, owing in large part to its historical large role in the presidential nomination process (perhaps because Iowans tend to be less apathetic than other states).  While Iowans tend to welcome political discussion more than most, their usual friendliness may at times give way to more hostile debate -- especially when the caucuses near their end, as Iowans have been subject to every candidate parading the state, hosting town forums and debates and soliciting their vote, for a much longer time than the rest of the states are forced to withstand.  Feel free to ask Iowans about the caucuses, and dont hesitate to offer your own opinion about political matters, but be respectful and dont take it personally if they dont want to discuss due to "caucus weariness".</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">63079</field>
		<field name="title">United States of America</field>
		<field name="main">respect</field>
		<field name="name">respect</field>
		<field name="content">Burning Man ,  Nevada  ]]   It is polite to shake hands when meeting someone or being introduced, though handshaking is often skipped in less formal situations. Kissing on the cheeks in greeting is rare and usually done only between close friends and family.  Unless it is really crowded, leave about an arms length of personal space between yourself and others.  Punctuality is valued: being five minutes late is not usually a problem, but any more should warrant a forewarning when possible.  As a result of its history of racial discrimination and the modern push toward equality, Americans are exceptionally touchy about issues of race. If you have to reference race, Black or African-American,  Asian, Latino or Hispanic, Native American or American Indian, and White or Caucasian are acceptable terms.   There are Native American reservations scattered throughout the country. Many of these reservations are home to sites that are sacred to the tribe, and certain places may be off-limits to all but tribe members. If you enter a reservation, respect its land and people.  Also see the section on  tipping , and the section on  smoking .</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">63080</field>
		<field name="title">Washington (state)</field>
		<field name="main">respect</field>
		<field name="name">respect</field>
		<field name="content">Do not litter along the freeways or highways. The fines for littering can range from several hundred to several thousand dollars depending on the scenario. It is an offense that the state takes VERY seriously. If you are caught in the act you will know what the state means by the "Litter and It Will Hurt" signs which frequently decorate its roadways.</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">63081</field>
		<field name="title">Fort Smith</field>
		<field name="main">respect</field>
		<field name="name">respect</field>
		<field name="content">Being so close to a number of military installations and bases the area boasts a large number of military families.  The city is in a very GOP concentrated district as opposed to the rest of the state, though changing political trends for both parties have caught up to the area recently.  Church attendance is very high and religious expression often encouraged but residents are often respectful of one politely declines their invitations to services. There are also small nonreligious secular social groups nearby, notably in  Fayetteville , if thats ones preference.  Being near many rural communities and woodlands one may come across, though rare, wildlife especially the nearer one is on the outskirts of the city. It is best advised to leave the wildlife be.  Local county liquor laws prohibit the sale of alcohol on Sundays.  Due to nation-wide economic changes several large scale employers have had to close or move. These events have hit the local residents very hard and as a result several have had to swallow their pride and accept public assistance.</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">63082</field>
		<field name="title">Mississippi</field>
		<field name="main">respect</field>
		<field name="name">respect</field>
		<field name="content">Being that the state is very socially and religiously conservative, it is wise to not make jokes about the predominant Christian religion practiced in the South, the Baptist denomination.  You may be asked by people whom youve only met once what religion you practice.  To most Mississippians, this isnt considered a personal question to ask another individual.  If you feel this is too personal of a question to respond to, you might reply that you are not comfortable discussing such a personal matter outside of your family and religious network.  You may also be asked to attend ones church, and if you are inclined to do so, men should be sure to wear a respectable, yet conservative, suit and tie, or a conservative dress for women.  You are not obligated to attend ones church if you do not feel comfortable doing so, but be sure to be very tactful when declining an invitation.   The state flag of Mississippi contains the Confederate flag in its upper left corner.  To many people this is an extremely emotional and sensitive image (on both sides of the political spectrum).  It is wise as an outsider of the state to avoid the discussion of the state flag (either positively or negatively) to avoid attracting unwanted attention.   As in other Southern States, when addressing people you have met for the first time (particularly those who are older than you) be sure to say either "Yes, sir / No, sir" or "Yes, maam / No, maam", in much the same manner that a soldier in the military would address a superior officer. Do not use first names until the other person uses yours, as it is considered rude to do as such without permission. Also, in many areas, saying "Mr./Ms./Mrs. (First name) is common, example: Mr. John, Msr. Jane, etc.   Be aware that many Mississippians have or are enlisted into the US military, or have relatives who are active or reserve members of either the US Military, or the Mississippi National Guard.  Pride and respect is very strong for members of the military and the economic support that the military provides to Mississippi.  Never make jokes or derogatory statements about the military, especially of its servicemen and servicewomen.</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">63083</field>
		<field name="title">Lakewood (Ohio)</field>
		<field name="main">respect</field>
		<field name="name">respect</field>
		<field name="content">Lakewood is well known an economically, culturally and ethnically diverse community.  Prejudice in any form is not appreciated, but treat other people the way you wish to be treated, regardless of any differences, and you should be fine.</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">63084</field>
		<field name="title">Montana</field>
		<field name="main">respect</field>
		<field name="name">respect</field>
		<field name="content">Montanans treasure their state, loving it for the recreational opportunities, wide open spaces, and the friendly nature of their neighbors. They, in general, welcome tourists and travellers, and will be glad to let you in on cool places to go, the best hike to take, or their favorite fishing hole. However, in South-Western Monatana, people tend to be slightly less tolerant of tourists, being very protective of their land. In addition, some Montanans are very proud of being rednecks, and may be seen sporting redneck proud T-Shirts, caps, or bumper stickers. This is not meant to be derogatory in any way, but is an expression of pride in Montanas rough and wild cultural heritage.   Be advised, however, that any disrespect of land and nature will not be tolerated. When enjoying everything Montana has to offer, please respect the lands, waterways and wildlife by following common sense. Dont litter, pollute or otherwise upset the landscape any more than you must, and though it is a cliche, do not feed the wildlife.</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">63085</field>
		<field name="title">Hilo</field>
		<field name="main">respect</field>
		<field name="name">respect</field>
		<field name="content">Haole = Caucasian: Though many think that "haole" just means white person, it refers more to an attitude than anything else. Hilo is a workaday town that sees few tourists.  Locals arent as accustomed to tourists as they are in the resort areas, so respecting the local people and culture is very important.  Treat the locals with respect, and the same respect will be returned to you. There are a few Native Hawaiians who have a generally negative attitude to Haoles, and may express this attitude through looks or comments. You are best to simply ignore comments to avoid provocation. You may also find that other Native Hawaiians are quite friendly and warm if you take the time to speak with them and be friendly, yourself.  Locals refrain from wearing aloha outfits, either full body attire or partial outfits. Clothes are very casual to resort casual at best.</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">63086</field>
		<field name="title">Oregon</field>
		<field name="main">respect</field>
		<field name="name">respect</field>
		<field name="content">Oregonians are fanatically proud of the natural beauty of their state; littering or otherwise causing harm to the scenic beauty - including wildlife - found here is bound to draw attention to you that you probably do not want, up to and including that special type which only an officer of the law can give.  That being said, keep in mind that while Portland and the rest of the Willamette Valley is very cosmopolitan and culturally similar to San Francisco and Seattle, Eastern Oregon and Southern Oregon are more akin to Idaho and Nevada; that is to say, quite conservative. Contrary to popular belief, not all Oregonians are liberal, a fact which will become abundantly clear to you on a trip to a place such as  Burns ,  La Grande , or  Prineville .  State issues in general tend to be divided along Willamette / non-Willamette lines (that is, large cities within the valley such as Eugene and Portland / smaller cities along the coast, around the mountains, and in the high desert), and some resentment between these groups may be uncovered. The State of Jefferson, a region of southern Oregon and northern California marked by a period of attempted secession during the first half of the 20th century, retains a very independent mindset: Jefferson Public Radio and the State of Jefferson Chamber of Commerce are two indicators of a retained degree of autonomy from this period.</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">63087</field>
		<field name="title">New Jersey</field>
		<field name="main">respect</field>
		<field name="name">respect</field>
		<field name="content">Culture, accent, and local dialect vary depending on what part of the state you visit. Although NJ is small, the north and south are very different. For example, a large sandwich in the northern region is called a "sub" and in the south the same sandwich is referred to as a "hoagie." Also keep in mind that the north identifies with New York culture while the south has a strong connection to Philadelphia. This loyalty extends to professional sports teams too. Please be aware of these small differences or else you may come off as very rude.  New Jersey natives are very aware of stereotypes fueled by popular television shows such as Jersey Shore and The Sopranos, and can be rather sensitive about how outsiders perceive them. Dont assume everyone from New Jersey is rude, loud, uneducated, etc. On the contrary, most people are remarkably polite and friendly.  Life in New Jersey moves at a fast pace! A lot of the bustling and quickness stems from the fact that NJ is a densely populated state, squished between two massive metropolitan areas. "Taking it slowly," which is common in other areas of the country, may be met with impatience or even anger. However, if you are looking for a slower pace in New Jersey, the shore towns and the southern end of the state (south of Atlantic City and many towns east of the Garden State Parkway) can be more relaxed as it is more seasonal and more of a vacation area.</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">63088</field>
		<field name="title">Branson</field>
		<field name="main">respect</field>
		<field name="name">respect</field>
		<field name="content">The term “Okies” is considered an offensive ethnic slur.</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">63089</field>
		<field name="title">Alaska</field>
		<field name="main">respect</field>
		<field name="name">respect</field>
		<field name="content">When you are hiking or visiting a natural area, do not pick flowers or collect natural features, particularly in a national park or forest. These are protected areas, and if everyone took something away, it would spoil it for everyone else. Picking flowers takes away nectar that is vital for insects.  Dont litter: Alaska is a beautiful state, and the best way of keeping it that way is just by respect to the land. It is easy to throw your trash and cigarette butts away, and by doing so, you are saving countless plants and animals.</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">63090</field>
		<field name="title">Massachusetts</field>
		<field name="main">respect</field>
		<field name="name">respect</field>
		<field name="content">Massachusetts, home of Northampton, Provincetown, and the first US state to legalize same-sex marriage, is arguably the most accepting state in all of the USA. Gay villages exist in abundance in Boston, and in smaller cities such as Springfield.  Massachusetts has a sports rivalry with New York, notably between the Boston Red Sox and New York Yankees (baseball), but also in American football (between the New England Patriots and New York Jets, and, to a lesser extent, the New York Giants). The Boston Celtics and Los Angeles Lakers (basketball) also have a fierce rivalry, although there are fewer visible LA fans due to distance. Finally, the Boston Bruins and Montreal Canadiens (hockey) have been rivals for a long time. While wearing merchandise of rival teams will generally only elicit mild comments or playful joking throughout New England, it can sometimes lead to harassment or confrontation, particularly before, during, or after important sports games. This is especially true of Yankees gear. It should also be noted that wearing rivals merchandise in bars or other more casual settings may result in poor service, or harassment from other tables. Many people from outside the US wear Yankees caps or t-shirts after visiting New York, unaware of the connotations in Boston/Massachusetts, and can find themselves getting yelled at for no apparent reason.</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">63091</field>
		<field name="title">Tulsa</field>
		<field name="main">respect</field>
		<field name="name">respect</field>
		<field name="content">Religion is still a very sensitive topic in Oklahoma. This accounts for some people calling Tulsa "The Buckle of The Bible Belt". As with many States in The South, this stems largely from 300 year old Christian religious traditions mixed in with Southern political, cultural and (in some rare cases) racial beliefs.</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">63092</field>
		<field name="title">Georgia (state)</field>
		<field name="main">respect</field>
		<field name="name">respect</field>
		<field name="content">Dont make jokes about Jim Crow or Shermans March to the Sea. Whistling "Marching Through Georgia" will not win you friends (this may seem obvious, but the lyrics and origins are less well known than the tune)</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
</add>