<add>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">63479</field>
		<field name="title">Disneyland</field>
		<field name="main">see and do</field>
		<field name="section">disneyland</field>
		<field name="name">main street, usa</field>
		<field name="content">Main Street Railroad Depot  Main Street U.S.A. has many shops and restaurants but few rides  Disneyland Railroad mdash; A train ride that takes you around Disneyland and stops at four stations, great for sightseeing  Main Street Cinema mdash; A theater-like attraction that shows the first six Mickey Mouse cartoons  Main Street Vehicles  Fire Engine  Horse-Drawn Streetcars  Horseless Carriage  Omnibus  The Disneyland Story Featuring Great Moments with Mr. Lincoln mdash; A theater-like attraction that shows an audio-animatronic Abraham Lincoln and a documentary on Disneyland.</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">63480</field>
		<field name="title">Disneyland</field>
		<field name="main">see and do</field>
		<field name="section">disneyland</field>
		<field name="name">new orleans square</field>
		<field name="content">Disneyland Railroad mdash; The Disneyland Railroad has a station in New Orleans Square  Haunted Mansion mdash; A scary dark ride that is based on a horror story in 18th-century New Orleans  Pirates of the Caribbean mdash; An indoor boat ride through caverns and a burning village  Fantasmic! mdash; A nighttime show with wonderful special effects.  Does not run every night during the off-season  Rafts to Pirates Island mdash; Tom Sawyers Island re-imagined with a pirate theme</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">63481</field>
		<field name="title">Disneyland</field>
		<field name="main">see and do</field>
		<field name="section">disneyland</field>
		<field name="name">fantasyland</field>
		<field name="content">Alice in Wonderland mdash; A dark ride that goes through the films storyline  Casey Jr. Circus Train mdash; A train ride that goes around the exterior of Storybook Land Canal Boats  Dumbo the Flying Elephant mdash; A spin ride on which one rides on "Dumbos"  Disney Princess Fantasy Faire mdash; Where visitors can meet three of the Disney princesses  "its a small world" mdash; An indoor boat ride that introduces visitors to singing children from all over the globe. One of Disneylands most beloved attractions. During the holiday season, this attraction is decorated all in holiday glory  King Arthur Carrousel mdash; A classic carousel ride  Mad Tea Party mdash; A spin ride on which one spins on models of tea cups  Matterhorn Bobsleds mdash; A bobsled inspired roller coaster that is based on the Matterhorn in  Switzerland  - note that for this ride there are two different tracks so ride both!  Mr. Toads Wild Ride mdash; A dark ride that goes through the scenes of the movie The Wind in the Willows  Peter Pans Flight mdash; A dark ride based on the movie  Pinocchios Daring Journey mdash; A dark ride based on the story  Snow Whites Scary Adventures mdash; A dark ride that is based on the story  Snow Whites Grotto mdash; A small spot next to Sleeping Beautys castle that showcases a set of statues of Snow White and the Seven Dwarves that were a gift to Walt alongside a small wishing well  Storybook Land Canal Boats mdash; A boat ride that goes through miniature scenes of famous Disney stories</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">63482</field>
		<field name="title">Disneyland</field>
		<field name="main">see and do</field>
		<field name="section">disneyland</field>
		<field name="name">mickeys toontown</field>
		<field name="content">Mickeys Toontown    Chip n Dale Treehouse mdash; A walk-through for kids based on the living quarters of Chip n Dale  Disneyland Railroad mdash; The Disneyland Railroad has a station in Mickeys Toontown  Donalds Boat mdash; A walk-through that is based on Donald Ducks home  Gadgets Go Coaster mdash; A roller coaster; expectant mothers should not ride  Goofys Fun House mdash; A fun-house attraction that is based on Goofys home, in the place of the former Goofys Bounce House  Mickeys House and Meet Mickey mdash; A walk-through based on Mickey Mouses house and where one can meet Mickey Mouse himself  Minnies House mdash; A walk-through based on Minnie Mouses house, Minnie appears out front quite often  Roger Rabbits Car Toon Spin mdash; A dark spin ride based on the movie Who Framed Roger Rabbit?</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">63483</field>
		<field name="title">Disneyland</field>
		<field name="main">see and do</field>
		<field name="section">disneyland</field>
		<field name="name">adventureland</field>
		<field name="content">Enchanted Tiki Room mdash; An Audio-Animatronics show that features singing birds, flowers, and various tiki figures; in the lanai out front you will also see tiki gods and goddesses  Indiana Jones Adventure mdash; A dark thrill ride based on the Indiana Jones series  Jungle Cruise mdash; A boat ride that goes through sights of isolated jungles of Asia, Africa, and South America  Tarzans Treehouse mdash; A walk-through that is based on the tree house in Tarzan</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">63484</field>
		<field name="title">Disneyland</field>
		<field name="main">see and do</field>
		<field name="section">disneyland</field>
		<field name="name">frontierland</field>
		<field name="content">Mark Twain Riverboat    Big Thunder Mountain Railroad mdash; A mine train-themed roller coaster  Tom Sawyer Island mdash; A large play area that is based on the Tom Sawyer stories  Frontierland Shootin Exposition mdash; A shooting gallery arcade  Mark Twain Riverboat mdash; A full-sized riverboat sailing around the "Rivers of America"  Rafts to Tom Sawyer Island mdash; Rafts to access Tom Sawyer Island  Sailing Ship Columbia mdash; A pirate ship themed boat sailing around the "Rivers of America"  Big Thunder Ranch mdash; A petting zoo  The Golden Horseshoe Stage mdash; A performance venue</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">63485</field>
		<field name="title">Disneyland</field>
		<field name="main">see and do</field>
		<field name="section">disneyland</field>
		<field name="name">critter country</field>
		<field name="content">Splash Mountain mdash; A log flume water ride  Davy Crocketts Explorer Canoes mdash; A canoe ride in which visitors paddle around the "Rivers of America"  The Many Adventures of Winnie the Pooh mdash; A dark ride that is based on the stories of Winnie the Pooh</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">63486</field>
		<field name="title">Disneyland</field>
		<field name="main">see and do</field>
		<field name="section">disneyland</field>
		<field name="name">tomorrowland</field>
		<field name="content">Astro Orbitor, Tomorrowland    Astro Orbitor mdash; A rocket flight where guests fly around a central futuristic-looking tower  Autopia mdash; A driving course. While many might think this to be a childrens ride, there is a height requirement, as crashing may occur  Buzz Lightyear Astro Blasters mdash; A dark ride that is a game similar to laser tag, only riders need to shoot the Zs along the way  Disneyland Monorail mdash; The first monorail built in the West connects Disneyland to Downtown Disney  Disneyland Railroad mdash; The Disneyland Railroad has a station in Tomorrowland  Finding Nemo Submarine Voyage mdash; you can see Nemo and his friends from the Pixar film Finding Nemo  Captain EO mdash; A 3D show starring Michael Jackson  Innoventions mdash; A walk through museum featuring the latest technology  Space Mountain mdash; A dark rollercoaster  Starcade mdash; An arcade, the fee to play the games is 5 tokens for $1  Star Tours: The Adventures Continue mdash; Recently revamped to take place between Episodes III and IV, this is a turbulent motion-simulator attraction in 3D which includes flights to iconic Star Wars locations, encounters with characters, and a story which ties into the timeline between the aforementioned episodes</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">63487</field>
		<field name="title">Disneyland</field>
		<field name="main">see and do</field>
		<field name="section">disneyland</field>
		<field name="name">shows and parades</field>
		<field name="content">Fantasmic! is an evening live action show that takes place on the Rivers of America.  It is a wonderful show with many of the Disney characters, animation on a screen made of jets of water, and fireworks.  Most days, there are street events along the parade route between Main Street, U.S.A. and "its a small world." Mickeys Soundsational Parade brings music to the streets with one or two performances daily. During the holiday season, "A Christmas Fantasy" Parade brings the joy of the season to the streets of Disneyland. Both parades are a must see and will be enjoyed by all age groups. Also most nights, Disneyland puts on its famous fireworks show. There are many other shows at Disneyland as well.</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">63488</field>
		<field name="title">Disneyland</field>
		<field name="main">see and do</field>
		<field name="name">disneyland</field>
		<field name="content">Disneyland Park  is the original Disney theme park which opened on July 18, 1955. While the park has changed dramatically over the years, there are still many favorite classic attractions, such as the Disneyland Railroad. Today, Disneyland boasts 57 attractions, more than any other Disney theme park.   Disneylands themed lands are Main Street, USA (modeled after 20th-century Marceline, Missouri, Walt Disneys childhood town), New Orleans Square (modeled after 18th-century  New Orleans ), Fantasyland (modeled after a Bavarian village), Mickeys Toontown (modeled after the cartoon town of Toontown in Who Framed Roger Rabbit?), Adventureland (modeled after the jungles of Asia, Africa and the South Pacific), Frontierland (modeled after the Old West), Critter Country (modeled after North American forests) and Tomorrowland (modeled after science fiction authors visions of yesterdays future).</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">63489</field>
		<field name="title">Disneyland</field>
		<field name="main">see and do</field>
		<field name="section">disney california adventure</field>
		<field name="name">buena vista street</field>
		<field name="content">The Red Car Trolley</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">63490</field>
		<field name="title">Disneyland</field>
		<field name="main">see and do</field>
		<field name="section">disney california adventure</field>
		<field name="name">condor flats</field>
		<field name="content">Soarin Over California mdash; A simulator film that shows famous California landmarks as if one was hang-gliding over California</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">63491</field>
		<field name="title">Disneyland</field>
		<field name="main">see and do</field>
		<field name="section">disney california adventure</field>
		<field name="name">grizzly peak</field>
		<field name="content">Grizzly River Run mdash; Roar down this white-water raft adventure; visitors may get very wet on this attraction  Redwood Creek Challenge Trail mdash; A large play area based on the  Mount Shasta  wilderness and the film Up</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">63492</field>
		<field name="title">Disneyland</field>
		<field name="main">see and do</field>
		<field name="section">disney california adventure</field>
		<field name="name">pacific wharf</field>
		<field name="content">Golden Vine Winery mdash; Where one can enjoy the different tastes of wine from around the world.  Can not be younger than 21 years of age to drink.  Walt Disney Imagineerings Blue Sky Cellar  The Bakery Tour mdash; A presentation of how sourdough bread is made  Ghirardelli Chocolate Store A presentation of how chocolate is made and a store</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">63493</field>
		<field name="title">Disneyland</field>
		<field name="main">see and do</field>
		<field name="section">disney california adventure</field>
		<field name="name">paradise pier</field>
		<field name="content">Mickeys Fun Wheel with California Screamin behind    California Screamin mdash; A high speed roller coaster that launches from 0–60 MPH in just 4.5 seconds!  Mickeys Fun Wheel mdash; A Ferris wheel with swinging and stationary gondolas  Games of the Boardwalk mdash; An arcade modeled after Boardwalk games  Golden Zephyr mdash; A spin ride with rocket ship models as the spinners  Goofys Sky School  King Tritons Carousel mdash; A sea-themed carousel  Jumpin Jellyfish mdash; A mini-drop ride  Silly Symphony Swings  Toy Story Midway Mania! mdash; Step right up and compete in an interactive Toy Story adventure like no other! Youll grab some 3-D glasses before boarding your ride vehicle and zipping off into a world of immersive, midway-style games  The Little Mermaid: Ariels Undersea Adventure mdash; A dark ride based on the movie The Little Mermaid  World of Color mdash; A water fountain show that is nothing you have seen before, on a scale larger than a football field, shown nightly</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">63494</field>
		<field name="title">Disneyland</field>
		<field name="main">see and do</field>
		<field name="section">disney california adventure</field>
		<field name="name">hollywood land</field>
		<field name="content">The Red Car Trolley    Monsters, Inc. Mike Sulley to the Rescue! mdash; A dark ride based on the movie, Monsters, Inc.  The Twilight Zone Tower of Terror mdash; A drop ride that drops 13 stories down, based on a 1950s TV series  Disneys Aladdin: A Musical Spectacular mdash; A musical based on Aladdin  MuppetVision 3D mdash; A 3D show featuring the Muppets  Disney Animation  Turtle Talk with Crush mdash; A show in which visitors can interact with Crush from Finding Nemo  Animation Academy mdash; A presentation on how to draw Disney characters  Character Close-Up mdash; A presentation where visitors can meet most of the famous Disney characters  Sorcerers Workshop mdash; A presentation where visitors can create their own animation  The Hollywood Backlot Stage mdash; performance venue  Red Car Trolley</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">63495</field>
		<field name="title">Disneyland</field>
		<field name="main">see and do</field>
		<field name="section">disney california adventure</field>
		<field name="name">"a bugs land"</field>
		<field name="content">Its Tough to be a Bug mdash; A 3D show about how insects protect themselves  Fliks Fun Fair  Fliks Flyers mdash; A wave swing modeled after giant food boxes  Francis Ladybug Boogie mdash; A spin ride modeled with ladybugs as spinners  Heimlichs Chew Chew Train mdash; A train that shows how Heimlich from the film, a bugs life finds food  Princess Dot Puddle Park mdash; A water play area  Tuck and Rolls Drive Em Buggies mdash; bumper cars</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">63496</field>
		<field name="title">Disneyland</field>
		<field name="main">see and do</field>
		<field name="section">disney california adventure</field>
		<field name="name">cars land</field>
		<field name="content">Cars Land   Based on Disney/Pixars Cars, this land simulates the entire town of Radiator Springs.  Radiator Spings Racers mdash; based on the same technology used on Epcots Test Track  Maters Junkyard Jamboree mdash; A spin ride modeled with tractors as spinners.  Luigis Flying Tires mdash; A hover ride modeled with tires as hovers.</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">63497</field>
		<field name="title">Disneyland</field>
		<field name="main">see and do</field>
		<field name="section">disney california adventure</field>
		<field name="name">shows and parades</field>
		<field name="content">Disney California Adventure has shows and a parade for visitors. The park is home of the Pixar Play Parade, where floats are based on the Disney/Pixar movies, The Incredibles, Toy Story, Ratatouille, A Bugs Life, Finding Nemo, and Monsters, Inc. as well as water and bubble effects. The parade is only offered on selected days.   In 2010, Disney unveiled a new water show called World of Color in the Paradise Pier area of the park.  It is highly recommended that you get a FastPass at the Grizzly River Run area to assure access to a main viewing area.</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">63498</field>
		<field name="title">Disneyland</field>
		<field name="main">see and do</field>
		<field name="name">disney california adventure</field>
		<field name="content">Grizzly Peak, the icon for California Adventure   Disney California Adventure  is Disneylands sister theme park which opened in February 2001. Initially the park struggled, with poor reviews and low attendance given the lack of focus or "Disney feel". However, the park has recently undergone a major overhaul, with new lands, new rides, and refurbished areas, and the response has been very positive. The park has a heavy California theme, with lands representing fanciful imaginings of certain parts of the state, although this is also where youll find most of the Pixar-themed attractions.  Disney California Adventure is divided into several themed lands: Buena Vista Street, modeled after 1920s Los Angeles, with Mission and Art Deco styled buildings and red streetcars running up the street Condor Flats, themed after the 1940s-1960s aviators of the  Mojave Desert  Grizzly Peak, representing the Northeastern California wilderness, oriented around the man-made Grizzly Peak, a mountain shaped like a grizzly bear Pacific Wharf, modeled on Northern Californias wharfs, with nods to Monterey and San Francisco Paradise Pier, the largest land in the park, a fanciful version of an early 20th century coastal boardwalk Hollywood Land, a recreation of a  Hollywood  studio backlot "a bugs land", based on the movie A Bugs Life, with over-sized human objects to give the impression of seeing the world from a bugs point of view Cars Land, a faithful recreation of Radiator Springs from the movie Cars</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">63499</field>
		<field name="title">Disneyland</field>
		<field name="main">see and do</field>
		<field name="name">downtown disney</field>
		<field name="content">AMC Downtown Disney 12 mdash; Catch a box-office chart-topper at this stadium seating, digital projection, and surround sound cineplex ESPN Zone mdash; Watch your favorite sports event or play one of many interactive games House of Blues mdash; As the name implies, a blues club Ralph Brennans Jazz Kitchen mdash; Experience the best of Bourbon Street outside New Orleans</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">63500</field>
		<field name="title">Teaneck</field>
		<field name="main">see and do</field>
		<field name="name">parks</field>
		<field name="content">For its size, Teaneck has quite a few parks, 22 to be exact. They are mostly small grassy spaces in residential areas with swing sets and basketball courts, but there are a few that hold significance for the entire town. Andreas Park. West Englewood Avenue will lead you down the hill to this park that sits on the edge of the Hackensack River. This park has large open space, a jungle gym and  free public tennis courts. This park is active year round with a great spot for people to push off in their boats to drift on the Hackensack River. Votee Park. The largest completely developed park in Teaneck and is located almost right in the middle of town. The park covers a huge amount of space, covering an area between Queen Anne Road and Palisade Avenue. Facilities include an in-ground swimming pool, a children’s wading pool, restrooms, an amphitheater, three soccer fields, five baseball fields, refreshment stands, a double handball court, four tennis courts, and a lighted, enclosed, two court basketball facility. There are 2 playgrounds (at either end), picnic areas, and paved walking paths. One playground is accessible for disabled children and has special equipment designed for kids with physical disabilities.</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">63501</field>
		<field name="title">Teaneck</field>
		<field name="main">see and do</field>
		<field name="name">arts and culture</field>
		<field name="content">Teaneck has a number of plays and art exhibitions happening all the time. Many are supported by The Puffin Foundation and its Puffin Cultural Forum located on Puffin Way. This includes the Teaneck International Film Festival held annually in November since 2005. The Teaneck Community Band presents a series of five outdoor summer concerts each summer, also sponsored by the Puffin Foundation. Teaneck is home to the Ethical Culture Society of Bergen County, founded in 1953.  The Teaneck Cultural Arts Coalition has organized many community-wide events.  The Garage Theater Group is Bergen County’s first non-profit professional theater company, and their members consist of mainly Teaneck residents and they perform the bulk of their shows at Farleigh Dickinson University.</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">63502</field>
		<field name="title">Walt Disney World</field>
		<field name="main">see and do</field>
		<field name="section">theme parks</field>
		<field name="name">the magic kingdom</field>
		<field name="content">The  Magic Kingdom , based on the original Disneyland in Anaheim, California, is the most popular theme park in the world. It is organized around the central landmark of Cinderella Castle, with various "lands" arrayed around a central hub: Main Street USA, Adventureland, Frontierland, Liberty Square, Fantasyland, and Tomorrowland.   The park is the oldest, most crowded, and the most child-friendly, although many adults love it as well. Adult visitors who do not enjoy rides such as its a small world, where you sit in vehicles that take you in a circle through a tunnel as animatronic figures sing childrens songs to the riders, may want to visit Epcot or Hollywood Studios instead.  On the other hand, roller coasters like Space Mountain and Big Thunder Mountain Railroad provide plenty of thrills, and dark rides like the Haunted Mansion and Pirates of the Caribbean are classics that only the most curmudgeonly would dismiss.  The lines at the Magic Kingdom can be endless, but they always keep moving.  Though the FastPass system works well, it is not available for all attractions.  Even just walking around, you will likely encounter bottlenecks where there are huge masses of people, and they all seem to be going to the same place you are.  Then theres the food and the merchandise, which can be pricey, but not too bad considering where you are.  Despite it all, most people would agree that the lines, the crowds, and the prices are worth it for the experience.</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">63503</field>
		<field name="title">Walt Disney World</field>
		<field name="main">see and do</field>
		<field name="section">theme parks</field>
		<field name="name">epcot</field>
		<field name="content">Spaceship Earth, the icon of Epcot    Epcot  is an "educational park."  It is divided into two distinct areas, Future World and World Showcase.  Future World features eight indoor pavilions, each one focused on a specific area of human achievement or endeavor.  World Showcase replicates, on a small scale but with great attention to detail, eleven of the worlds nations, complete with authentic food and merchandise.  Dont miss the cheesy but fun Gran Fiesta Tour Starring The Three Caballeros ride in the Mexico pavilion, or the extravagant Maelstrom ride in the Norway pavilion. In Future World, the Test Track, a recent addition in which visitors go through the motions of tests for new cars, is probably the most fun, and the most traditionally theme-park-y, of the Epcot rides.  Recent additions to the park include Soarin39;, a ride where visitors "hang-glide" through many landscapes, and Mission: SPACE, a centrifugal spaceflight simulator.  Epcot has a bit of a reputation as a more "grown-up" park.  While some of the slower, more intellectual attractions may be over the heads of the youngest visitors, the park still has plenty to keep them entertained.  Of course there are character greetings, especially at World Showcase, but there are also Kidcot Fun Stops, which encourage children to work on a craft and interact with cast members who are representing their home countries.  The Seas with Nemo Friends is great fun for fans of Finding Nemo, too.</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">63504</field>
		<field name="title">Walt Disney World</field>
		<field name="main">see and do</field>
		<field name="section">theme parks</field>
		<field name="name">disneys hollywood studios</field>
		<field name="content">Disneys Hollywood Studios  (formerly Disney-MGM Studios) is themed around film and television, and features a variety of live shows and attractions based on some of the most iconic productions in Hollywood history.  Disney subsidiaries Pixar, Lucasfilm, and The Muppets each have a significant presence here.  The flagship attraction is The Great Movie Ride, which takes guests inside famous film scenes both modern and nostalgic.  Among the attractions are a few exceptional thrill rides, most notably The Twilight Zone Tower of Terror (which drops you 13 stories) and the Rock n Roller Coaster Starring Aerosmith (which launches you 0ndash;60 in 2.8 seconds).  The 3-D shooting gallery Toy Story Mania! also grabs big crowds, as does the Star Wars-based simulator ride Star Tours: The Adventures Continue.</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">63505</field>
		<field name="title">Walt Disney World</field>
		<field name="main">see and do</field>
		<field name="section">theme parks</field>
		<field name="name">disneys animal kingdom</field>
		<field name="content">Disneys Animal Kingdom , a member of the Association of Zoos and Aquariums, is a wildlife discovery park, a mix between a zoo and a theme park.  Naturalistic animal exhibitions are interspersed, and sometimes integrated, with typical Disney rides.  Among these are Kilimanjaro Safaris, a jeep safari past live animal enclosures; Kali River Rapids, a raft ride through the deforestation of a tropical rainforest; Dinosaur, a time travel ride which includes close encounters with dinosaurs; and the newest and most popular ride, Expedition Everest, a roller coaster that includes an encounter with the Yeti.  The park is organized in a Magic Kingdom-like format, with different continents revolving around the central Tree of Life. While light on rides, there are also shows and plenty of animals to view (though the variety of species seems a bit sparse when compared to many larger city zoos). Animal Kingdom is more of a kid-friendly theme park, with many animals that would attract the attention of younger generations, as well as Camp Minnie-Mickey, a special space for youngsters where they can meet all of their favorite characters.</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">63506</field>
		<field name="title">Walt Disney World</field>
		<field name="main">see and do</field>
		<field name="name">theme parks</field>
		<field name="content">The four theme parks are Walt Disney Worlds bread and butter.  These are not traditional amusement parks, where age is a hindrance to full enjoyment.  The Disney parks have rides, sure, but many of them are quite sedate and can be enjoyed by everyone, not just those with a high tolerance for thrills.  And even beyond the rides, there are stage shows to watch, shops to browse, characters to meet, and atmosphere to soak in.  Most importantly, though, none of these rides, shows, and stores just "sits there".  Each one tells a story, in much the same way that Disneys animated films do, and each is crafted with the utmost care and attention to detail.  There are also the bigger stories to be found in each themed land, and in the park as a whole.  When you enter the Magic Kingdom, and the entrance tunnels give way to the vista of Main Street, with Cinderella Castle at the far end, youre raising the curtain on a new productionmdash;and youre the featured player.  You wont find dirt or peeling paint or run-down mechanics at a Disney Park, not even at the oldest attractions.  Disney takes quality very seriously, and if anything intrudes on your perception of the "show", it gets fixed quickly.  Its all about suspension of disbelief: total immersion into worlds of imagination, art, and history.  The sheer number of attractionsmdash;including rides, stage shows, parades, and fireworks displaysmdash;at Walt Disney Worlds four theme parks can be intimidating to guests.  Its usually best to have a plan going in.  Check the guide map for the park you plan to visit and decide which attractions will be your highest priorities before you leave for the park.  Keep in mind that parades and some shows occur only at specific times, and plan your route to put you nearby in time to get a seat.  Be flexible, thoughmdash;once youve hit your priority attractions, you can go back and pick up more if you have time remaining.  The traditional amusement park advice of arriving early and heading to the back of the park first tends to work well, although more and more guests are starting to catch on, so the benefit may be reduced.  Be aware that during the busiest times of year, lines can be over three hours long for the most popular attractions.  (During the least busy times, youll rarely see more than 45 minutes, though.)  As great as the attractions are, they are rarely worth standing in a three-hour line.  One option for avoiding these lines is the free service known as FastPass, available only at select attractions.  Simply insert your park ticket into the machine, and youll get a FastPass ticket with a time interval stamped on it.  At any time during that interval (usually one hour long), you may enter the attraction using a separate, shorter queue.  You cannot get another FastPass until the return time for your current one arrives (or until two hours have elapsed, whichever is earlier).  That means you cant avoid every line, but it can still be a great time-saver, especially for the most popular and crowded attractions.  One common procedure is to choose two attractions near each other and get a FastPass for one, then ride the other using the stand-by line; once done with the second ride, your return time for the first should be near.  Note that you cannot choose your own return time; return times are pushed later and later as more people acquire FastPasses.  If the demand is high, you might find that FastPasses "run out", sometimes even before noon during peak attendance seasons.  Also, be aware that the FastPass queues may bypass some or all of the scenery and theming found in the longer lines, which for some guests is a significant part of the Disney experience.  Consider what you may be missing if you choose to get a FastPass.</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">63507</field>
		<field name="title">Walt Disney World</field>
		<field name="main">see and do</field>
		<field name="name">meet the characters</field>
		<field name="content">Indy finds an idol   Especially for kids, character greetings are one of the most exciting reasons to visit Disney World.  Kids and adults alike can give hugs to, take a photo with, or get autographs from many of their favorite Disney characters.  Some kids like to bring or purchase a special autograph book in which the characters can inscribe their names.  Character appearances tend to be surprises (to avoid huge lines), so keep a close eye out.  If theres a character your child really wants to see, you can ask at Guest Relations if they know of any upcoming appearances, but nothing is ever guaranteed.  And remember that its hot inside those character costumes; sometimes the character has to leave even if there are people still waiting to say hello.  Its disappointing but necessary for safety.  Most often, character greetings will happen in the parks, in particular the Magic Kingdom, but they can happen just about anywhere!  The Magic Kingdom does have the widest variety of characters, though; everyone from Mickey Mouse to Captain Jack Sparrow.  Disneys "Big Six" (Mickey, Minnie, Donald, Daisy, Goofy, and Pluto) might be found anywhere in the parkmdash;for example, you might see Donald Duck in a Davy Crockett-like outfit in Frontierland.  Other characters stick to the themed land most appropriate for their genre: Jack Sparrow in Adventureland, Buzz Lightyear in Tomorrowland, and so on.  At the other parks, character appearances are somewhat rarer.  At Epcot, for instance, youll generally only find characters who hail from one of the themed foreign lands of World Showcasemdash;Mulan in the China pavilion, for example.  Hollywood Studios and Animal Kingdom tend to have more structured greetings, where characters will make scheduled appearances at designated locations, but stay out of sight of most of the park.  Kids looking for autographs wont want to miss Camp Minnie-Mickey at Animal Kingdom, though; there are always at least a few characters there happy to meet some young guests.  If you miss out on random encounters with the characters, be sure to look into character dining options.  While restaurants that offer character dining are extremely popular, if you can get a table, youre virtually guaranteed a few minutes of face time with the characters.  See  Character Dining  in the Eat section, below.</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">63508</field>
		<field name="title">Walt Disney World</field>
		<field name="main">see and do</field>
		<field name="name">pin trading</field>
		<field name="content">The  trading of commemorative pins  has been popular at Olympic Games for decades.  At the turn of the millennium, Disney decided to get in on the act and began creating metallic lapel pins specifically for trading.  The monster they created has endured for over a decade, and it has grown to mythic proportions.  More than 60,000 different pin designs have been produced since the beginning.  Getting started is easy.  Most every store has pins for sale ($7–$14 each), along with lanyards on which to display them.  You can also get a starter pack with pins and a lanyard for $20–$60.  These pins are generally not very valuable, so youll need to trade up to get the more interesting (and much more rare) pins.  The most reliable way to do so is to keep an eye out for Cast Members wearing pin lanyards.  Cast Members are required to trade one-for-one if asked (up to two per guest per day) and cant refuse a trade based on pin rarity or design (although they can refuse to accept another copy of a pin they already have displayed).  Cast Members with green lanyards will trade only to kids under 13.  You can also trade with your fellow guests, and here things can get interesting.  You may need to offer several more common pins to get your hands on a single rare pin.  Dedicated traders carry a supply of common pins for just this purpose.  Your best way to find people willing to trade is to head to a dedicated pin kiosk or store, such as the one underneath the Sorcerers Hat at Hollywood Studios, but there is also ample opportunity for trading while waiting in lines or while riding the monorail or bus.  Some tours and special events have unique pins that can only be obtained by participants.  These pins are thus very rare and highly coveted.  Make sure you (and especially your kids) dont trade these pins away without getting something really nice in returnmdash;but even then, think very carefully.  Many people treat these more as souvenirs than commodities.</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">63509</field>
		<field name="title">Walt Disney World</field>
		<field name="main">see and do</field>
		<field name="name">tours</field>
		<field name="content">Each of the theme parks offers at least one tour, some of which are very popular.  For an extra fee, a cast member will take you and a small group and introduce you to some of the "secrets" behind Disney operations.  Many of these tours go into backstage areas where guests are not normally allowed, although children may be restricted from these to avoid spoiling the "magic".  The gold standard among the tours is the Keys to the Kingdom tour at the  Magic Kingdom , a five-hour tour that includes a peek into the parks Utilidors.  At  Epcot , there are several tours at The Seas with Nemo Friends that take you into the huge aquarium to get up close to the animals who live there.  The newest tour offering is the Wild Africa Trek at  Animal Kingdom , which will let you go on-foot into some remote areas of the parks African savanna and forest.</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">63510</field>
		<field name="title">Walt Disney World</field>
		<field name="main">see and do</field>
		<field name="name">water parks</field>
		<field name="content">Walt Disney Worlds two water parks, Blizzard Beach near  Animal Kingdom  and Typhoon Lagoon near  Downtown Disney , are the most-visited water parks in the country (for Typhoon Lagoon, in the world), with a combined total yearly attendance of almost 4 million. Each water park has a unique central theme.  Blizzard Beach brings to life the absurdity of what would happen if a ski resort suddenly melted, while Typhoon Lagoon makes use of the runoff from a tropical storm for sliding and floating fun.  Both parks are big enough to spend several hours sliding, floating, or just soaking up the sun.  Counter-service restaurants provide for a hearty lunch.  If you have an extra $250 to spend, consider renting a private cabana for the day; they come with towels, lockers, a cabana attendant, and all the bottled water you can drink.</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">63511</field>
		<field name="title">Walt Disney World</field>
		<field name="main">see and do</field>
		<field name="name">shopping, dining, and nightlife</field>
		<field name="content">Disneys Boardwalk   Sometimes you just want to get away from the theme parks for a while.  Maybe do some shopping, have a quiet meal, or get away from the kids and go out dancing.   Downtown Disney  is just what the doctor ordered: an outdoor shopping, dining, and entertainment paradise, geared primarily toward adults. Most of the entertainment activities are found on Downtown Disney West Side; the featured attraction is the Cirque du Soleil show La Nouba. DisneyQuest, a five-story indoor theme park focusing on interactive "virtual" rides and featuring some of the most innovative technology at Disney World, is also on the West Side.  The east side, known as Downtown Disney Marketplace, is made up largely of shops and family restaurants.  Disneys BoardWalk, located next to  Epcot , is a smaller collection of nightlife themed as a 1920s Eastern Seaboard boardwalk. The Boardwalk is also home to carnival midway games, tandem bike rentals, the Atlantic Dance Hall, and the ESPN Club.</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">63512</field>
		<field name="title">Walt Disney World</field>
		<field name="main">see and do</field>
		<field name="section">sporting activities</field>
		<field name="name">golf</field>
		<field name="content">Walt Disney World is home to three 18-hole championship  golf courses , plus a nine-hole walking course and two different miniature golf experiences.  The Lake Buena Vista is in the  Downtown Disney  area; its the most scenic of the courses.  The Magnolia and Palm courses, which hosted a popular PGA tournament from 1971ndash;2012, are in the  Magic Kingdom  area, adjacent to the Shades of Green resort.  The three championship courses require standard golf attire, and metal cleats are not allowed.  Golf clubs are available for rent.  A golf cart must be used, but it is included in your greens fee.  The Oak Trail Golf Course, in the Magic Kingdom area next to the Magnolia and Palm courses, is a nine-hole walking course.  Its designed for less-experienced golfers and older children.  The same rules and regulations apply here as at the championship courses, except golf carts are prohibited.  The four golf courses can be reached only via car or, in some limited cases, walking.  The Disney-owned resorts offer complimentary taxi vouchers for their guests traveling to the golf courses.  For more information or assistance, or to reserve a tee time, call +1 407 WDW-GOLF (939-4653).  Tee times can be reserved up to 90 days in advance if youre staying at a Disney hotel (up to 60 days in advance otherwise).  The miniature golf courses are Fantasia Gardens, across the street from the Walt Disney World Swan Hotel in the  Epcot  resort area, and Winter Summerland, right next to  Blizzard Beach .  Each has two 18-hole layouts, with whimsical, kid-friendly holes and decor.</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">63513</field>
		<field name="title">Walt Disney World</field>
		<field name="main">see and do</field>
		<field name="section">sporting activities</field>
		<field name="name">watersports</field>
		<field name="content">Walt Disney World boasts a number of expansive waterways, and that means boating and other watersports can be a great way to spend a few hours away from the parks.  The  Magic Kingdom-area resorts  each have a small marina with a selection of recreational boats for rent, but its the Contemporary Resort that boasts Sammy Duvalls Watersports.  You dont have to be staying at the Contemporary to enjoy the marinas offerings; you might try waterskiing, wakeboarding, or even parasailing!  At the Yacht Club Resort (adjacent to  the Boardwalk ), Bayside Marina offers SeaRaycers, pontoon boats, and a variety of chartered cruises, including an IllumiNations fireworks cruise to Epcot.  At  Downtown Disney , Captain Jacks Marina will rent you a "water mouse" or canopy boat, or take you out for a bass fishing excursion.</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">63514</field>
		<field name="title">Walt Disney World</field>
		<field name="main">see and do</field>
		<field name="section">sporting activities</field>
		<field name="name">other</field>
		<field name="content">The Walt Disney World Speedway is located south of the  Magic Kingdom  and offers both Indy car and NASCAR-style racing experiences, although neither is cheap.  On the other hand, if spectator sports are more your speed, you may want to check out the ESPN Wide World of Sports, a state-of-the-art sports complex near  Hollywood Studios . It features a baseball stadium, two indoor arenas, various sports fields, an athletics complex and a tennis complex. Its biggest events are in late winter/early spring, with the Pro Soccer Classic (the spring training event for Major League Soccer) in February, and baseball spring training for the Atlanta Braves in March. There are a wide variety of other events all year, especially high school and collegiate-level sports.</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">63515</field>
		<field name="title">Walt Disney World</field>
		<field name="main">see and do</field>
		<field name="name">sporting activities</field>
		<field name="content">Often overlooked during a Walt Disney World vacationmdash;whether due to time constraints or just lack of knowledgemdash;are several recreational activities that have nothing to do with theme parks and rides.</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">63516</field>
		<field name="title">Walt Disney World</field>
		<field name="main">see and do</field>
		<field name="name">spas and health clubs</field>
		<field name="content">If you feel the need for a bit of pampering, Walt Disney Worlds spa facilities offer a full array of massage, skin, and nail treatments.  Senses – A Disney Spa has two locations at Walt Disney World.  The spa at Disneys Saratoga Springs Resort, near  Downtown Disney , recalls the heyday of  Saratoga Springs , New York, with its healing mineral baths. The spa and health club at Disneys Grand Floridian Resort, near  the Magic Kingdom , evokes the Victorian era. Theres no significant price difference between the two spas, although some specific treatments are unique to one or the other.   Mandara Spa  has a facility at the Walt Disney World Dolphin near  Epcot , and theres also the Buena Vista Palace Hotel Spa at the  Downtown Disney Hotel Plaza .  If you dont need a full-service spa, most of the other Deluxe resorts have smaller salons with more limited selections of services.  These can be a great way to get in some quick relaxation time without having to travel to a different hotel.  Most resorts also have at least a modest exercise room, in case you dont do enough walking around at the parks.</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">63517</field>
		<field name="title">Walt Disney World/Animal Kingdom</field>
		<field name="main">see and do</field>
		<field name="name">oasis</field>
		<field name="content">The Oasis is just the entrance area of the park, taking you from the gates to the central hub of Discovery Island.  Its a wooded setting, with several animal enclosures; look for the giant anteater, capybaras, macaws, and many others.  Make sure you take both the left and the right paths; each has different animals.</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">63518</field>
		<field name="title">Walt Disney World/Animal Kingdom</field>
		<field name="main">see and do</field>
		<field name="name">discovery island</field>
		<field name="content">Discovery Island is the central hub of Animal Kingdom. The Tree of Life is located here, as are the majority of the parks shops and a couple of very good restaurants.  "Discovery" isnt just a name, either; if you wander off the main drag youll find yourself in the Discovery Island Trails that wind around the base of the Tree.  There youll find a number of birds and other small animals on display.  Youll also be able to take a look at some of the Tree of Lifes animal carvings up-close, although the queue area for Its Tough to be a Bug provides the best vantage points.</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">63519</field>
		<field name="title">Walt Disney World/Animal Kingdom</field>
		<field name="main">see and do</field>
		<field name="section">discovery island</field>
		<field name="name">Adventurers Outpost</field>
		<field name="content">Come on in to the air-conditioning and meet Mickey and Minnie in their safari gear.</field>
		<field name="alt">character greeting</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">63520</field>
		<field name="title">Walt Disney World/Animal Kingdom</field>
		<field name="main">see and do</field>
		<field name="section">discovery island</field>
		<field name="name">Its Tough to be a Bug!</field>
		<field name="content">This is a 3-D film featuring Flik and other characters from the Pixar film A Bugs Life.  Youll meet grubs, stink bugs, wasps, and other creepy-crawlies, complete with special effects both tactile and olfactory.  Some scenes may be a little frightening for kids, or for anyone with an aversion to insects.</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">63521</field>
		<field name="title">Walt Disney World/Animal Kingdom</field>
		<field name="main">see and do</field>
		<field name="section">camp minnie-mickey</field>
		<field name="name">Festival of the Lion King</field>
		<field name="content">Acrobatic, colorful, and tuneful, this theater-in-the-round features the characters from The Lion King.  This aint Broadway, though; dont expect the elaborate costumes and choreography of that famous show.  Still, kids will enjoy seeing these favorite characters on the stage, and the music is still just as good as it was in the movie.</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">63522</field>
		<field name="title">Walt Disney World/Animal Kingdom</field>
		<field name="main">see and do</field>
		<field name="name">camp minnie-mickey</field>
		<field name="content">Themed as an old-fashioned summer camp, Camp Minnie-Mickey is a big place where kids can go to meet several popular Disney characters, though not (ironically) Mickey and Minnie (theyre at the Adventurers Outpost on  Discovery Island ).  Ask a cast member if theres a specific character youd like to see.</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">63523</field>
		<field name="title">Walt Disney World/Animal Kingdom</field>
		<field name="main">see and do</field>
		<field name="section">africa</field>
		<field name="name">Kilimanjaro Safaris</field>
		<field name="content">According to the story of this attraction, youre headed out on a two-week safari through the Harambe Wildlife Reserve.  Board your well-equipped (and very large) safari jeep, and your driver/guide will point out the animals along the route.  This area of the park covers more than 100 acres (40nbsp;ha.), with habitats representing wetlands, forest, and savanna.  Lions, elephants, giraffes, rhinos, and many more species can be seen during your trip.  Absolutely fantastic for photos; many of the herbivores will hang out just feet from the jeeps path, and there are no windows or fences between you and them.  (Note: Although Disney has posted safety restrictions for this ride, it is relatively mild, especially compared to rides like Dinosaur and Expedition Everest.)</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">63524</field>
		<field name="title">Walt Disney World/Animal Kingdom</field>
		<field name="main">see and do</field>
		<field name="section">africa</field>
		<field name="name">Wild Africa Trek</field>
		<field name="content">Reservations are now being taken for a three-hour guided expedition into the Harambe Wildlife Reserve, including areas not normally seen from the Safari or the Trail.  Guests will trek through vines on a bushwalk, cross a rope bridge over a river, peer over cliffs at hippos and crocodiles, and enjoy a private elevated safari camp right in the middle of the animals habitats.  You must be at least 9 years old and 48 inches tall, and you must weigh between 45 and 310 pounds.</field>
		<field name="price">$189 (price varies by season); park admission required</field>
		<field name="hours">Multiple expeditions daily</field>
		<field name="alt">tour</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">63525</field>
		<field name="title">Walt Disney World/Animal Kingdom</field>
		<field name="main">see and do</field>
		<field name="section">africa</field>
		<field name="name">Pangani Forest Exploration Trail</field>
		<field name="content">A walk-through area near the exit of the Kilimanjaro Safaris.  This forested area is home to hippos, meerkats, and gorillas, among other animals.  As you walk through, keep an eye out for research documents from the Harambe Reserve researchers and their student visitors, which serve to both maintain the fictional setting and provide information about the animals.</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">63526</field>
		<field name="title">Walt Disney World/Animal Kingdom</field>
		<field name="main">see and do</field>
		<field name="section">africa</field>
		<field name="name">Wildlife Express</field>
		<field name="content">This train ride is the only way to get to Rafikis Planet Watch.  The route takes you past the animal houses, where the animals get fed and spend the night.  Trains depart every 5ndash;10 minutes.</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">63527</field>
		<field name="title">Walt Disney World/Animal Kingdom</field>
		<field name="main">see and do</field>
		<field name="name">africa</field>
		<field name="content">Another jeep heads out for a two-week safari.   Welcome to Harambe, or as they say in this fictional east African town, "Jambo!"  The detail here is incredible, from the consistent overarching storyline (of a town on the outskirts of the Harambe Wildlife Reserve) all the way down to a faded Coca-Cola advertisement painted on a wall.  Take some time, if its not too crowded, and see if you cant convince yourself youre in Africa.     15px</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">63528</field>
		<field name="title">Walt Disney World/Animal Kingdom</field>
		<field name="main">see and do</field>
		<field name="section">rafikis planet watch</field>
		<field name="name">Habitat Habit!</field>
		<field name="content">This is the walkway between the train station and Conservation Station.  Youll find cottontop, golden lion, and emperor tamarins here, as well as tips on steps you can take to preserve animal habitat, no matter where you live.</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">63529</field>
		<field name="title">Walt Disney World/Animal Kingdom</field>
		<field name="main">see and do</field>
		<field name="section">rafikis planet watch</field>
		<field name="name">Affection Section</field>
		<field name="content">This is the aforementioned petting zoo, featuring some exotic but still domesticated species from around the globe.</field>
		<field name="directions">Just outside Conservation Station</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">63530</field>
		<field name="title">Walt Disney World/Animal Kingdom</field>
		<field name="main">see and do</field>
		<field name="section">rafikis planet watch</field>
		<field name="name">Conservation Station</field>
		<field name="content">This is the main attraction at Rafikis Planet Watch, housed in part of a large building that includes many of the parks animal treatment facilities.  Large glass windows even let you look in on some of the procedures as they occur.  Other exhibits focus on conservation and attempts to protect endangered species of animals.  Youll also find some character greetings in here, in particular Rafiki himself.</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">63531</field>
		<field name="title">Walt Disney World/Animal Kingdom</field>
		<field name="main">see and do</field>
		<field name="name">rafikis planet watch</field>
		<field name="content">A trainer introduces a vulture to the crowd at Rafikis Planet Watch.   Rafikis Planet Watch is accessible only via the Wildlife Express train from Africa. This is an interactive learning center documenting wildlife conservation efforts around the world. Best of all, it includes a petting zoo!</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">63532</field>
		<field name="title">Walt Disney World/Animal Kingdom</field>
		<field name="main">see and do</field>
		<field name="section">asia</field>
		<field name="name">Maharajah Jungle Trek</field>
		<field name="content">Similar to the Pangani Forest trail, this is a walk through ancient "ruins" showcasing Asian wildlife.  The Bengal tigers are the stars, but dont miss the giant fruit bats, or the countless birds inside the aviary.</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">63533</field>
		<field name="title">Walt Disney World/Animal Kingdom</field>
		<field name="main">see and do</field>
		<field name="section">asia</field>
		<field name="name">Kali River Rapids</field>
		<field name="content">This is a wild whitewater ride through a tropical forest.  Not much educational content here; its just a fun, very wet ride.  You will get soaked, guaranteed, not just from the ride but from the water guns controlled by guests on the surrounding walkways. Closed for refurbishment January 6 ndash; February 15, 2013.</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">63534</field>
		<field name="title">Walt Disney World/Animal Kingdom</field>
		<field name="main">see and do</field>
		<field name="section">asia</field>
		<field name="name">Flights of Wonder</field>
		<field name="content">See exotic birds up close in a small but shaded amphitheater. Show mixes clever humor along with facts about birds and other animales, and includes some very close up encounters with some of the birds who fly narrowly close to the audience in all sections of the amiptheater.  See the Times Guide for show times.</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">63535</field>
		<field name="title">Walt Disney World/Animal Kingdom</field>
		<field name="main">see and do</field>
		<field name="section">asia</field>
		<field name="name">Expedition Everest: Legend of the Forbidden Mountain</field>
		<field name="content">Located in the fictional village of Serka Zong. Defy local wisdom and book a train ride through the heart of yeti country, crossing the Forbidden Mountain to forge a path to Everest.  Dont say you werent warned, however, when you find the tracks are out and your train starts careening backwards!  This roller coaster is exciting and includes a number of neat twists and special effects.  The queue is also worth seeing; it takes you through an expedition-supply shop and a museum purporting to hold conclusive evidence of the yetis existence.  Very popular ride, so you might want to consider a Fastpass, especially if youve been through the standby queue once already.</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">63536</field>
		<field name="title">Walt Disney World/Animal Kingdom</field>
		<field name="main">see and do</field>
		<field name="name">asia</field>
		<field name="content">A tiger relaxing on the Maharajah Jungle Trek   Much like Africa, the Asian section is meant to represent a fictional community somewhere on that continent; in this case, its Anandapur, a South Asian village on the edge of a jungle and not far from the Himalayas.  Again, the attention to detail is incredible and worth some exploration if you have the time.     15px       15px</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">63537</field>
		<field name="title">Walt Disney World/Animal Kingdom</field>
		<field name="main">see and do</field>
		<field name="section">dinoland u.s.a.</field>
		<field name="name">Primeval Whirl</field>
		<field name="content">This is a pair of identical spinning-car roller coasters, themed to display Chester Hesters creativity in adapting automobile parts to thrill rides.  Can be a rough ride, especially if youre sitting next to someone with a lot of mass to spin around, but its fun.</field>
		<field name="directions">Dino-Rama</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">63538</field>
		<field name="title">Walt Disney World/Animal Kingdom</field>
		<field name="main">see and do</field>
		<field name="section">dinoland u.s.a.</field>
		<field name="name">Cretaceous Trail</field>
		<field name="content">A walking path that shows you some static dioramas of dinosaurs, as well as some live animals and plants that have survived from the Mesozoic Era.</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">63539</field>
		<field name="title">Walt Disney World/Animal Kingdom</field>
		<field name="main">see and do</field>
		<field name="name">dinoland u.s.a.</field>
		<field name="content">Dinosaurs play a dual role in popular culture, representing both ancient mystery and thrilling fantasy.  Both aspects are represented in DinoLand U.S.A..  As the story goes, when the Dino Institute, a dinosaur research facility, opened up along a dilapidated stretch of highway, the local service station owners, Chester and Hester, had a brilliant idea.  They collected material from the junkyard nearby and created a roadside attraction called Chester Hesters Dino-Rama!  The Institute represents the educational, realistic side of dinosaur enthusiasm, while the carnival atmosphere of Dino-Rama represents the sense of fun and excitement dinos can generate.         15px         15px</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">63540</field>
		<field name="title">Walt Disney World/Animal Kingdom</field>
		<field name="main">see and do</field>
		<field name="section">dinoland u.s.a.</field>
		<field name="name">The Boneyard</field>
		<field name="content">At the entrance to DinoLand U.S.A. is this play area for pre-schoolers, where they can dig around in the sand for "bones" and otherwise climb and jump and play.</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">63541</field>
		<field name="title">Walt Disney World/Animal Kingdom</field>
		<field name="main">see and do</field>
		<field name="section">dinoland u.s.a.</field>
		<field name="name">TriceraTop Spin</field>
		<field name="content">A Dumbo-like ride with Triceratops-shaped vehicles that spin around a central axis and move up and down with a joystick. Great for kids too small to go on Primeval Whirl.</field>
		<field name="directions">Dino-Rama</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">63542</field>
		<field name="title">Walt Disney World/Animal Kingdom</field>
		<field name="main">see and do</field>
		<field name="section">dinoland u.s.a.</field>
		<field name="name">Finding Nemo: The Musical</field>
		<field name="content">This popular show adds inventive music to an abbreviated version of the story from the film. Acrobatics and puppetry give a feeling of being underwater. Check the Times Guide for show times.</field>
		<field name="directions">Theater in the Wild</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">63543</field>
		<field name="title">Walt Disney World/Animal Kingdom</field>
		<field name="main">see and do</field>
		<field name="section">dinoland u.s.a.</field>
		<field name="name">Fossil Fun Games</field>
		<field name="content">This is Dino-Ramas midway, with all of the impossible games and plush prizes youd expect from any self-respecting carnival.</field>
		<field name="directions">Dino-Rama</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">63544</field>
		<field name="title">Walt Disney World/Animal Kingdom</field>
		<field name="main">see and do</field>
		<field name="section">dinoland u.s.a.</field>
		<field name="name">Dinosaur</field>
		<field name="content">Head back in time to the late Cretaceous, come face-to-face with a variety of dinosaurs, then race against time to escape the asteroid impact that ended their reign.  Pretty rough but fun.  Very dark and probably too scary for little kids, with lots of "gotcha" moments.</field>
		<field name="directions">Dino Institute</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">63545</field>
		<field name="title">Walt Disney World/Animal Kingdom</field>
		<field name="main">see and do</field>
		<field name="section">parkwide</field>
		<field name="name">Wilderness Explorers</field>
		<field name="content">Stop by the main station on the bridge to Discovery Island to pick up your handbook and take the Wilderness Explorers pledge, inspired by the Disney/Pixar film Up.  Then wander the park and keep an eye out for the activity stations and interpretive exhibits scattered throughout.  There are thirty "merit badge" stickers to acquire, and getting them all would be a true accomplishment.  The cast members at each station are friendly and have tons of information to share; even adults will be engaged and interested in the discussions they lead.</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">63546</field>
		<field name="title">Walt Disney World/Animal Kingdom</field>
		<field name="main">see and do</field>
		<field name="section">parkwide</field>
		<field name="name">Mickeys Jammin Jungle Parade</field>
		<field name="content">This afternoon parade celebrates the animal spirit that is the reason for Animal Kingdom, featuring plenty of Disney characters, abstract animal puppets, and other visual surprises.  As with all Disney parades, if you want a good vantage point, stake one out early; likewise, plan to be far from the parade route if you want to avoid the crowds.  Check your Times Guide to see when the parade will occur.  Becomes Mickeys Jingle Jungle Parade in November and December.</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">63547</field>
		<field name="title">Walt Disney World/Animal Kingdom</field>
		<field name="main">see and do</field>
		<field name="section">blizzard beach</field>
		<field name="sub-section">disneys winter summerland</field>
		<field name="name">Winter Summerland</field>
		<field name="content">Just outside the Blizzard Beach gates is this inventive pair of miniature golf courses.  Winter Summerland makes good use of the snow and ice theme; as the story goes, Santa Claus and his elves have created a vacation resort-away-from-home here in Florida.  Half of the elves wanted something resembling home, so they borrowed winter-themed elements from Blizzard Beach to create the "Snow" course; the other half wanted to feel like they were actually in Florida and created the "Sand" course.  There are sight gags galore, and the courses are great for kids and adults alike.  Be warned: you can take the Blizzard Beach bus during that parks operating hours, and bus service to the All-Star Resorts and Epcot continues until 9PM, but after that youll need to have a car handy.</field>
		<field name="phone">+1 407 560-3000</field>
		<field name="price">Adults $12, children $10 per 18 holes (second round, same day, is half price). Before 4PM, a Water Park Fun More option can be used for one round of golf</field>
		<field name="address">1548 W Buena Vista Dr</field>
		<field name="hours">10AM-11PM</field>
		<field name="url">http://disneyworld.disney.go.com/recreation/miniature-golf/</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">63548</field>
		<field name="title">Walt Disney World/Animal Kingdom</field>
		<field name="main">see and do</field>
		<field name="section">blizzard beach</field>
		<field name="name">Snow Stormers</field>
		<field name="content">Three slalom-style mat slides, designed for racing.</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">63549</field>
		<field name="title">Walt Disney World/Animal Kingdom</field>
		<field name="main">see and do</field>
		<field name="section">blizzard beach</field>
		<field name="name">Tikes Peak</field>
		<field name="content">A play area for younger children.</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">63550</field>
		<field name="title">Walt Disney World/Animal Kingdom</field>
		<field name="main">see and do</field>
		<field name="section">blizzard beach</field>
		<field name="name">Slush Gusher</field>
		<field name="content">Go over two "moguls" down the mountainside.</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">63551</field>
		<field name="title">Walt Disney World/Animal Kingdom</field>
		<field name="main">see and do</field>
		<field name="section">blizzard beach</field>
		<field name="name">Chairlift</field>
		<field name="content">Whats a ski resort without a chairlift? You can use this to get from the park entrance to Summit Plummet, Slush Gusher, Teamboat Springs, Toboggan Racers, and Snow Stormers.</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">63552</field>
		<field name="title">Walt Disney World/Animal Kingdom</field>
		<field name="main">see and do</field>
		<field name="section">blizzard beach</field>
		<field name="name">Toboggan Racers</field>
		<field name="content">Ride a "toboggan" down a slippery, melting slope, racing up to seven other sliders.</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">63553</field>
		<field name="title">Walt Disney World/Animal Kingdom</field>
		<field name="main">see and do</field>
		<field name="section">blizzard beach</field>
		<field name="name">Downhill Double Dipper</field>
		<field name="content">A pair of racing speed slides on which you ride inner tubes.</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">63554</field>
		<field name="title">Walt Disney World/Animal Kingdom</field>
		<field name="main">see and do</field>
		<field name="section">blizzard beach</field>
		<field name="name">Summit Plummet</field>
		<field name="content">At 120nbsp;feet (37nbsp;m) high, this is the second-tallest and second-fastest water slide in the world. Guests who dare will plummet at over 55nbsp;mph (89nbsp;km/h) straight down an 85-degree angle.  Exhilarating, but creates monster wedgies.</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">63555</field>
		<field name="title">Walt Disney World/Animal Kingdom</field>
		<field name="main">see and do</field>
		<field name="section">blizzard beach</field>
		<field name="name">Melt-Away Bay</field>
		<field name="content">The parks largest pool.  Has some gentle waves, but nothing remotely like Typhoon Lagoons wave pool.</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">63556</field>
		<field name="title">Walt Disney World/Animal Kingdom</field>
		<field name="main">see and do</field>
		<field name="section">blizzard beach</field>
		<field name="name">Runoff Rapids</field>
		<field name="content">Three "ski slopes" into a pool of melted "snow".</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">63557</field>
		<field name="title">Walt Disney World/Animal Kingdom</field>
		<field name="main">see and do</field>
		<field name="name">blizzard beach</field>
		<field name="content">Teamboat Springs. Its not as cold as it looks, really!   Whats a ski resort doing in central Florida? The Disney Imagineers who created  Blizzard Beach  claim that they built it after an unusual freak winter storm blanketed the area, only to have it experience a massive meltdown shortly thereafter.  When a stray alligator splashed down the former ski jump on his belly, they realized the area would make a swell water park!  Blizzard Beach is the second-most-visited water park in the U.S. (behind only its sister park  Typhoon Lagoon ), and the incredibly inventive theme is a big reason why.  Its almost eerie to see guests walking around in swimsuits while theres snow everywhere.  Enjoy the cognitive dissonance by going on some great water slides, including the tallest and fastest body slide on the continent.  Blizzard Beach is not far from Animal Kingdom, and the two parks share bus routes.  The park is usually open from 10AMndash;5PM (closing for a couple of months each winter and, ironically, whenever the temperature dips close to freezing), and admission is $52 for adults or $44 for kids ages 3-10.  Admission to the water park counts as one of your "Fun Visits" if youve added the Water Park Fun More option to your  Magic Your Way tickets mdash;and note that just one admission almost pays for the cost of the option.</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">63558</field>
		<field name="title">Walt Disney World/Animal Kingdom</field>
		<field name="main">see and do</field>
		<field name="section">blizzard beach</field>
		<field name="name">Teamboat Springs</field>
		<field name="content">A family water slide, with 4- to 6-passenger rafts.</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">63559</field>
		<field name="title">Walt Disney World/Animal Kingdom</field>
		<field name="main">see and do</field>
		<field name="section">blizzard beach</field>
		<field name="name">Ski Patrol Training Camp</field>
		<field name="content">A play area for older children.</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">63560</field>
		<field name="title">Walt Disney World/Animal Kingdom</field>
		<field name="main">see and do</field>
		<field name="section">blizzard beach</field>
		<field name="name">Cross Country Creek</field>
		<field name="content">A relaxing inner tube ride around the whole park.</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">63561</field>
		<field name="title">Walt Disney World/Downtown Disney</field>
		<field name="main">see and do</field>
		<field name="section">annual events</field>
		<field name="name">Car Masters Weekend</field>
		<field name="content">The Muscle Car Network of Central Florida comes to Downtown Disney each June for a classic car show, and the stars of Disney/Pixars Cars films also make an appearance.  Theres a sock hop at Splitsville, and all sorts of other special events going on all weekend.  Some events and experiences carry an extra fee, but viewing the cars (and the Cars) is free.</field>
		<field name="directions">West Side</field>
		<field name="hours">Annually, mid-Jun, 9:30AM-6PM</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">63562</field>
		<field name="title">Walt Disney World/Downtown Disney</field>
		<field name="main">see and do</field>
		<field name="name">typhoon lagoon</field>
		<field name="content">The Crush n Gusher is not your normal water slidemdash;see how it actually goes up there?   According to Disney Imagineering legend, years ago, a fishing trawler named Miss Tilly found itself caught in a powerful hurricane.  When the torrent subsided, the boat found itself perched precariously atop Mt. Mayday, with water still gushing down through channels and valleys to a lake below.  What else was there to do but for the survivors to create  Typhoon Lagoon ?  Typhoon Lagoon is the most-visited water park in the world, and is a great place to beat the Summer heat from June through September.  While its theme is not as whimsically inventive as that of its sister park,  Blizzard Beach , Typhoon Lagoon excels at providing guests a consistent and energetic setting for some of the best water rides in the world.  But do keep an eye out for the unique touches the Imagineers have brought to the decor, including scattered remnants of ships cargoes and even palm trees supposedly bent low by the hurricane!  Typhoon Lagoon is not far from Downtown Disney, and the two often share bus routes.  The park is usually open from 10AMndash;5PM, and admission is $52 for adults or $44 for kids ages 3-10.  Admission to the water park counts as one of your "Fun Visits" if youve added the Water Park Fun More option to your  Magic Your Way tickets mdash;and note that just one admission almost pays for the cost of the option.  The direct telephone number for Typhoon Lagoon is +1 407 560-4141.  Typhoon Lagoon closes for annual refurbishment every fall or winter, almost always including the month of December (during which Blizzard Beach remains open to provide a bit of Christmas-in-Florida atmosphere).  For example, the park will be closed from October 28, 2012, through January 5, 2013.</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">63563</field>
		<field name="title">Walt Disney World/Downtown Disney</field>
		<field name="main">see and do</field>
		<field name="section">typhoon lagoon</field>
		<field name="name">Keelhaul Falls</field>
		<field name="content">A whitewater rafting experience.</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">63564</field>
		<field name="title">Walt Disney World/Downtown Disney</field>
		<field name="main">see and do</field>
		<field name="section">typhoon lagoon</field>
		<field name="name">Gangplank Falls</field>
		<field name="content">A family ride, in four-passenger tubes.</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">63565</field>
		<field name="title">Walt Disney World/Downtown Disney</field>
		<field name="main">see and do</field>
		<field name="section">typhoon lagoon</field>
		<field name="name">Crush n Gusher Water Rollercoaster</field>
		<field name="content">What do you get when you cross a water slide with a roller coaster? This!</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">63566</field>
		<field name="title">Walt Disney World/Downtown Disney</field>
		<field name="main">see and do</field>
		<field name="section">typhoon lagoon</field>
		<field name="name">Castaway Creek</field>
		<field name="content">A 2,000 foot tubing river that winds through the whole park.</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">63567</field>
		<field name="title">Walt Disney World/Downtown Disney</field>
		<field name="main">see and do</field>
		<field name="section">typhoon lagoon</field>
		<field name="name">Ketchakiddee Creek</field>
		<field name="content">A childrens play area.</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">63568</field>
		<field name="title">Walt Disney World/Downtown Disney</field>
		<field name="main">see and do</field>
		<field name="section">typhoon lagoon</field>
		<field name="name">Shark Reef</field>
		<field name="content">A snorkel pool featuring tropical fish, rays, small (non-threatening) sharks, and a mock sunken ship.</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">63569</field>
		<field name="title">Walt Disney World/Downtown Disney</field>
		<field name="main">see and do</field>
		<field name="section">typhoon lagoon</field>
		<field name="name">Surf Pool</field>
		<field name="content">One of the worlds largest wave pools with some of the largest artificially created waves. Take advantage of the surfing lessons offered here.</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">63570</field>
		<field name="title">Walt Disney World/Downtown Disney</field>
		<field name="main">see and do</field>
		<field name="section">typhoon lagoon</field>
		<field name="name">Storm Slides</field>
		<field name="content">Three 30 mph slides through dark caverns.</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">63571</field>
		<field name="title">Walt Disney World/Downtown Disney</field>
		<field name="main">see and do</field>
		<field name="section">typhoon lagoon</field>
		<field name="name">Mayday Falls</field>
		<field name="content">Inner tube slide winding down the side of an artificial mountain.</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">63572</field>
		<field name="title">Walt Disney World/Downtown Disney</field>
		<field name="main">see and do</field>
		<field name="section">typhoon lagoon</field>
		<field name="name">Humunga Kowabunga</field>
		<field name="content">Three 214 foot long slides send you plummeting straight down, at a terrifying five stories per second!</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">63573</field>
		<field name="title">Walt Disney World/Downtown Disney</field>
		<field name="main">see and do</field>
		<field name="name">golf</field>
		<field name="content">There is one 18-hole championship golf course in the Downtown Disney area.  See " Golf " in the overview for rules and regulations.  Monday through Friday, 18 holes will cost $89 if youre staying at a Disney hotel, and $104 otherwise.  On weekends, add $10.  During the summer, 10AM-3PM tee times are discounted; ask for the "Summer Price Slice" when you call.  Late afternoon tee times are $59 on weekdays and $69 on weekends for everyone.  Call +1 407 WDW-GOLF (939-4653) to reserve a tee time.</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">63574</field>
		<field name="title">Walt Disney World/Downtown Disney</field>
		<field name="main">see and do</field>
		<field name="section">golf</field>
		<field name="name">Lake Buena Vista Golf Course</field>
		<field name="content">This golf course meanders throughout the area north of Downtown Disney, starting adjacent to the Saratoga Springs Resort, crossing the Sassagoula River, and running right through the middle of the Old Key West Resort.  At 6,819 yards, with narrow fairways and even a challenging island green on hole 7, this golf course will give a great tour of the scenery around the Downtown Disney-area resorts.</field>
		<field name="directions">off Buena Vista Dr, north of Saratoga Springs</field>
		<field name="address">2200 Club Lake Dr</field>
		<field name="url">http://disneyworld.disney.go.com/golf/lake-buena-vista-golf-course/</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">63575</field>
		<field name="title">Walt Disney World/Downtown Disney</field>
		<field name="main">see and do</field>
		<field name="section">spa</field>
		<field name="name">Senses – A Disney Spa</field>
		<field name="content">Saratoga Springs , New York, was once known for its healing and relaxing mineral waters, a tradition carried forward at this full-service spa and health club.  The expected wide array of massages, facial and full-body treatments, and manicures and pedicures are all available here, and theyre not restricted to guests staying at the resort.</field>
		<field name="phone">+1 407-WDW-SPAS</field>
		<field name="price">Expect to pay about $140 for a 50-minute treatment, or $200 for an 80-minute treatment, with plenty of more expensive packages available</field>
		<field name="hours">8AM-8PM</field>
		<field name="phoneextra">+1 407-939-7727</field>
		<field name="url">https://disneyworld.disney.go.com/spas/saratoga-springs-resort-and-spa/spa-at-saratoga-springs-resort/</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">63576</field>
		<field name="title">Walt Disney World/Epcot</field>
		<field name="main">see and do</field>
		<field name="section">future world</field>
		<field name="name">imagination!</field>
		<field name="content">Imagine what you might find underneath those glass pyramids!   The name says it all; the possibilities of imagination are on display here. The pavilion represents the importance of new ideas and innovative thought to the progress of humanity. Be sure to check out the jumping fountains and the backwards waterfall outside.</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">63577</field>
		<field name="title">Walt Disney World/Epcot</field>
		<field name="main">see and do</field>
		<field name="section">future world</field>
		<field name="sub-section">imagination!</field>
		<field name="name">Captain EO</field>
		<field name="content">The classic 3-D short film that played in the pavilions theater from 1986ndash;1994 made a return engagement in Summer 2010. Its a musical science fiction adventure starring the late Michael Jackson. Directed by Francis Ford Coppola, produced by George Lucas, and featuring a host of Disney-designed alien creatures, its a film everyone should see at least once. Its not yet known when this return engagement will end, or if "Honey I Shrunk the Audience" will return.</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">63578</field>
		<field name="title">Walt Disney World/Epcot</field>
		<field name="main">see and do</field>
		<field name="section">future world</field>
		<field name="sub-section">imagination!</field>
		<field name="name">Journey Into Imagination with Figment</field>
		<field name="content">A classic Disney dark ride, starring Eric Idle and the iconic purple dragon named Figment. The ride is much improved since its 1999 revamp, but still pales compared to the original 1982 ride. Even so, its still fun to explore the senses and what your imagination can conceive with just a little sensory push.</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">63579</field>
		<field name="title">Walt Disney World/Epcot</field>
		<field name="main">see and do</field>
		<field name="section">future world</field>
		<field name="sub-section">imagination!</field>
		<field name="name">ImageWorks</field>
		<field name="content">This is an interactive play area at the end of the Journey Into Imagination ride, allowing you to put into practice some of the imaginative ideas you saw in the ride. Youll explore the senses of sight and sound, using your imagination to take those sensory inputs and create something new.</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">63580</field>
		<field name="title">Walt Disney World/Epcot</field>
		<field name="main">see and do</field>
		<field name="section">future world</field>
		<field name="name">innoventions</field>
		<field name="content">Divided into two buildings, Innoventions East and Innoventions West, this pavilion sits in the middle of Future World, with the fabulous Fountain of Nations in its central plaza. The buildings contain a constantly-changing series of hands-on exhibits featuring the latest in cutting-edge technology and how its finding its way into every aspect of our lives. The exact items youll see depend on which companies are exhibiting at the time; as such, quality varies widely. Worth a walk-through, at least, since you never know what might pique your curiosity.</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">63581</field>
		<field name="title">Walt Disney World/Epcot</field>
		<field name="main">see and do</field>
		<field name="section">future world</field>
		<field name="sub-section">innoventions</field>
		<field name="name">Fountain of Nations</field>
		<field name="content">This large show fountain was christened in 1982 with water from 22 different nations. Every 15 minutes, it presents one of several music-synchronized shows; its powerful jets spray water up to 150 feet in the air. If its windy, you may get damp.</field>
		<field name="directions">Innoventions Plaza</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">63582</field>
		<field name="title">Walt Disney World/Epcot</field>
		<field name="main">see and do</field>
		<field name="section">future world</field>
		<field name="sub-section">the land</field>
		<field name="name">Soarin</field>
		<field name="content">A simulated aerial flight over California, imported from  Disneys California Adventure . This is more than just a movie, thoughmdash;your feet will be dangling with apparently open sky below, and youll feel the wind in your face and smell the orange groves as you fly overhead. Likely the most popular ride in the park, so youll probably want a FastPass (although the standby queue does have some interactive shadow-games to while away the time).</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">63583</field>
		<field name="title">Walt Disney World/Epcot</field>
		<field name="main">see and do</field>
		<field name="section">future world</field>
		<field name="sub-section">the land</field>
		<field name="name">Behind the Seeds</field>
		<field name="content">A one-hour guided walking tour through the greenhouses. More informative and in-depth than the Living with the Land boat ride, but it costs extra.</field>
		<field name="phone">+1 407 939-8687</field>
		<field name="price">Adults $16, children (3-9) $12</field>
		<field name="alt">walking tour</field>
		<field name="url">http://disneyworld.disney.go.com/tours-and-experiences/behind-the-seeds/</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">63584</field>
		<field name="title">Walt Disney World/Epcot</field>
		<field name="main">see and do</field>
		<field name="section">future world</field>
		<field name="name">the land</field>
		<field name="content">Mickey-shaped pumpkins dont just grow that way naturally, you know.   Perhaps the pavilion that most closely resembles Walts original EPCOT concept, The Land is more than just a set of theme park attractions. The rear of the pavilion is actually a large working greenhouse, and it grows much of the food served at the pavilions restaurants (and some items for other restaurants throughout Walt Disney World). The greenhouses are also involved in agricultural research, exploring new ways to grow food more efficiently.</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">63585</field>
		<field name="title">Walt Disney World/Epcot</field>
		<field name="main">see and do</field>
		<field name="section">future world</field>
		<field name="sub-section">the land</field>
		<field name="name">Living with the Land</field>
		<field name="content">A slow-moving educational boat ride through Disneys hydroponic and aeroponic greenhouses, with a lesson on how we can live in peace with the land.</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">63586</field>
		<field name="title">Walt Disney World/Epcot</field>
		<field name="main">see and do</field>
		<field name="section">future world</field>
		<field name="sub-section">the land</field>
		<field name="name">Circle of Life</field>
		<field name="content">A straightforward movie about conservation, starring The Lion King characters Simba, Pumbaa, and Timon. It might teach kids a thing or two, and it has a bit of humor to keep parents from dozing off.</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">63587</field>
		<field name="title">Walt Disney World/Epcot</field>
		<field name="main">see and do</field>
		<field name="section">future world</field>
		<field name="name">mission: space</field>
		<field name="content">15px</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">63588</field>
		<field name="title">Walt Disney World/Epcot</field>
		<field name="main">see and do</field>
		<field name="section">future world</field>
		<field name="sub-section">mission: space</field>
		<field name="name">Mission: SPACE</field>
		<field name="content">A centrifugal flight simulator lets you feel what it would be like to train for a journey to Mars, but its not just a passive ridemdash;you and the others in your capsule have tasks to do during the flight. The spinning of the centrifuge is effective at generating g-forces, but it can induce motion sickness (bags are available). It helps if you keep your head back against the headrest and focus on the images on the screen, which show straight-line acceleration; looking away removes the visual cues and makes it feel more like rotation. If you really want to avoid the spinning and the g-forces, look for the "Green Team" queue, which will put you in a capsule that doesnt spin; its still a fun ride but not as thrilling. Gary Sinise appears as your mission controller.</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">63589</field>
		<field name="title">Walt Disney World/Epcot</field>
		<field name="main">see and do</field>
		<field name="section">future world</field>
		<field name="sub-section">mission: space</field>
		<field name="name">Advanced Training Lab</field>
		<field name="content">If you didnt get enough training on the ride, try this interactive area with games and displays that highlight some of the challenges and innovations of space exploration. Mission: SPACE Race is especially fun, with large teams racing their spacecraft back to Earth using teamwork and puzzle-solving.</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">63590</field>
		<field name="title">Walt Disney World/Epcot</field>
		<field name="main">see and do</field>
		<field name="section">future world</field>
		<field name="sub-section">the seas with nemo friends</field>
		<field name="sub-sub-section">tours</field>
		<field name="name">Seas Aqua Tour</field>
		<field name="content">A rare chance to snorkel along the surface of the giant aquarium. Learn about the dozens of species in residence, then view them up-close as you swim along. The snorkel system uses supplied air; instruction and wetsuits provided. 2.5 hours, 30 minutes of which is in the water. Must be 8 or older. No park admission required.</field>
		<field name="price">$140</field>
		<field name="hours">daily 12:30PM</field>
		<field name="url">http://disneyworld.disney.go.com/tours-and-experiences/seas-aqua-tour/</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">63591</field>
		<field name="title">Walt Disney World/Epcot</field>
		<field name="main">see and do</field>
		<field name="section">future world</field>
		<field name="sub-section">the seas with nemo friends</field>
		<field name="sub-sub-section">tours</field>
		<field name="name">DiveQuest</field>
		<field name="content">This is a special opportunity for certified SCUBA divers only. This is the tour that really lets you get down into the aquarium and swim among the fish, sharks, turtles, and more. That also means you become part of the show, as the land-lubbers inside Sea Base and in the Coral Reef restaurant will be waving at you; make their day by waving back. All diving equipment is provided. 2.5 hours, 30 minutes of which is in the water. Must be 10 or older and have proof of SCUBA certification.</field>
		<field name="price">$175+</field>
		<field name="hours">daily 4:30PM, 5:30PM</field>
		<field name="url">http://disneyworld.disney.go.com/tours-and-experiences/epcot-dive-quest/</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">63592</field>
		<field name="title">Walt Disney World/Epcot</field>
		<field name="main">see and do</field>
		<field name="section">future world</field>
		<field name="sub-section">the seas with nemo friends</field>
		<field name="name">tours</field>
		<field name="content">There are a number of tours that get you out of the normal guest areas and in close on the aquarium and its inhabitants. Call +1 407 WDW-TOUR (939-8687) to book a tour. No park admission is required for these tours; youll meet outside the gates and be escorted into the backstage area of The Seas pavilion.</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">63593</field>
		<field name="title">Walt Disney World/Epcot</field>
		<field name="main">see and do</field>
		<field name="section">future world</field>
		<field name="sub-section">the seas with nemo friends</field>
		<field name="sub-sub-section">tours</field>
		<field name="name">Dolphins in Depth</field>
		<field name="content">Learn about the aquariums dolphin population, including how theyre being trained and the research thats being done to learn more about them. Then get waist-deep in the aquarium for a chance to interact with the dolphins themselves (though contact is not guaranteed; the dolphins can choose whether or not to participate). Wetsuits provided. 3 hours. Must be 13 or older.</field>
		<field name="price">$194</field>
		<field name="hours">Tu-Sa 9:45AM</field>
		<field name="url">http://disneyworld.disney.go.com/tours-and-experiences/dolphins-in-depth/</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">63594</field>
		<field name="title">Walt Disney World/Epcot</field>
		<field name="main">see and do</field>
		<field name="section">future world</field>
		<field name="sub-section">the seas with nemo friends</field>
		<field name="name">Turtle Talk with Crush</field>
		<field name="content">Part of Disneys Living Character Initiative, this is an interactive show featuring the sea turtle character. Kids get to ask Crush questions, and he responds in real time. Great fun, especially for young kids, but very popular.</field>
		<field name="directions">inside Sea Base</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">63595</field>
		<field name="title">Walt Disney World/Epcot</field>
		<field name="main">see and do</field>
		<field name="section">future world</field>
		<field name="name">the seas with nemo friends</field>
		<field name="content">Wheres Nemo?   The aquarium within this pavilion was once the largest saltwater aquarium in the world; its still impressively huge. Like the greenhouses at The Land, this is more than just a theme park attractionmdash;the aquarium staff is engaged in research that is helping to maintain marine environments and protect ecosystems around the world. Two rescued West Indian manatees, members of one of Floridas most critically endangered species, can be found here.</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">63596</field>
		<field name="title">Walt Disney World/Epcot</field>
		<field name="main">see and do</field>
		<field name="section">future world</field>
		<field name="sub-section">the seas with nemo friends</field>
		<field name="name">The Seas with Nemo Friends</field>
		<field name="content">The title attraction is a slow-moving but cute ride; the finale uses state-of-the-art display technology to show characters from Finding Nemo swimming with real fish. After the ride, youll head into the Sea Base.</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">63597</field>
		<field name="title">Walt Disney World/Epcot</field>
		<field name="main">see and do</field>
		<field name="section">future world</field>
		<field name="sub-section">the seas with nemo friends</field>
		<field name="name">Sea Base</field>
		<field name="content">This is a representation of an underwater base and serves as the primary viewing location for the main aquarium. Turtle Talk with Crush is located here, along with a number of exhibits and displays typical of what you might see in other aquarium buildings. One of the best sights into the aquarium is from a circular platform that sticks out into the tank, so youre surrounded by fish on almost all sides. Aquarium staff give presentations periodically, including dolphin training sessions.</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">63598</field>
		<field name="title">Walt Disney World/Epcot</field>
		<field name="main">see and do</field>
		<field name="section">future world</field>
		<field name="name">spaceship earth</field>
		<field name="content">Spaceship Earth  Yes, the ride really does go all the way up to the top inside that giant "golf ball", the geodesic sphere that is the icon of Epcot. This pavilion is centrally located because its focus is on human communication, without which all of the other innovations in Future World would be meaningless.</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">63599</field>
		<field name="title">Walt Disney World/Epcot</field>
		<field name="main">see and do</field>
		<field name="section">future world</field>
		<field name="sub-section">spaceship earth</field>
		<field name="name">Spaceship Earth</field>
		<field name="content">This dark ride through the history of communication was revamped in 2007 with new scenes and new narration by Dame Judi Dench, but its message is the same as it was when it first opened in 1982: communication is the key to all human achievement. Kids might get bored; keep them occupied looking for humorous vignettes scattered among the Audio-Animatronic scenes. Closing for refurbishment August 18ndash;28, 2013.</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">63600</field>
		<field name="title">Walt Disney World/Epcot</field>
		<field name="main">see and do</field>
		<field name="section">future world</field>
		<field name="sub-section">spaceship earth</field>
		<field name="name">Project Tomorrow</field>
		<field name="content">After riding Spaceship Earth, youll end up here. This space houses several inventive games based on technology from communications company Siemens AG, which sponsors the pavilion.</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">63601</field>
		<field name="title">Walt Disney World/Epcot</field>
		<field name="main">see and do</field>
		<field name="section">future world</field>
		<field name="sub-section">test track</field>
		<field name="name">Test Track</field>
		<field name="content">Get an idea of what it might feel like to be a crash-test dummy in this unique thrill ride. Start off by designing your own custom test vehicle, then hop into one of the pre-built cars for a ride through the testing course. Your custom design gets put through its paces, virtually, at the same time as the "real" test vehiclemdash;with you inside. Perfectly safe, but the 60nbsp;mph (100nbsp;km/h) speed your car gets up to feels a lot faster. Lots of fun and extremely popular; youll want a FastPass. Because the cars seat six, theres often room left over from parties of two or four; the single-rider line, from which the cast fills those spaces, can get you on the ride quicker if the FastPasses are gone and you dont mind splitting your party.</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">63602</field>
		<field name="title">Walt Disney World/Epcot</field>
		<field name="main">see and do</field>
		<field name="section">future world</field>
		<field name="name">test track</field>
		<field name="content">15px</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">63603</field>
		<field name="title">Walt Disney World/Epcot</field>
		<field name="main">see and do</field>
		<field name="section">future world</field>
		<field name="sub-section">universe of energy</field>
		<field name="name">Ellens Energy Adventure</field>
		<field name="content">This attraction starts off as a film with Ellen DeGeneres dreaming shes on Jeopardy! and facing a question about energy. Bill Nye, "the Science Guy", drops in to show her, and you, all about energy. Suddenly you find the very theater in which you sit is moving, and it takes you and the rest of the audience into a large animatronic replica of the Mesozoic Era. (Thats why a lot of people just call this "The Dinosaur Ride".) If you like Ellens humor, this is a great ride; otherwise, its still worth it for the amazing dinosaur scenes. And you might learn something along the way. Also stars Alex Trebek and Jamie Lee Curtis.</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">63604</field>
		<field name="title">Walt Disney World/Epcot</field>
		<field name="main">see and do</field>
		<field name="section">future world</field>
		<field name="name">universe of energy</field>
		<field name="content">The very construction of this pavilion exemplifies its message regarding the importance of energy. Look up at the sloped roof of this building before you go in; those are solar panels, and they partially power the attraction inside.</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">63605</field>
		<field name="title">Walt Disney World/Epcot</field>
		<field name="main">see and do</field>
		<field name="name">future world</field>
		<field name="content">Future World is an almost park-like setting, with broad expanses of grass and/or water separating the impressively large pavilions. Each pavilion is a monument to one area of human innovation, from communication and imagination to energy and transportation. Inside the pavilions youll find some combination of a showcase ride, a theater presentation, and/or an activity area with a number of smaller hands-on exhibits. Each pavilion can be done in 30ndash;90 minutes, depending on crowds.  Check the Times Guide to see when and where the JAMMitors will be playingmdash;theyre a percussion ensemble disguised as janitors, using their trash cans as drums.</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">63606</field>
		<field name="title">Walt Disney World/Epcot</field>
		<field name="main">see and do</field>
		<field name="section">world showcase</field>
		<field name="sub-section">mexico</field>
		<field name="name">Gran Fiesta Tour Starring The Three Caballeros</field>
		<field name="content">A recent much-needed update to this gentle boat ride added the Three Caballeros, from the 1944 Disney film of the same name. Join Panchito and José Carioca on a gentle boat ride across all of Mexico, searching for Donald Duck, the last member of the trio, who has been distracted by all the commotion and gone missing.</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">63607</field>
		<field name="title">Walt Disney World/Epcot</field>
		<field name="main">see and do</field>
		<field name="section">world showcase</field>
		<field name="name">mexico</field>
		<field name="content">left   The  Mexican  pavilion is dominated by a pyramid, loosely modeled after the pre-Columbian pyramid in  Teotihuacan  known as the Temple of the Feathered Serpent, dating back to 150-200 CE. Its use is still a mystery, but more than 200 sacrificial burials have been found around the original temple. The head of the mythical serpent creature Quetzalcoatl has been included in this replica along the entrance stairs. Inside the pyramid is a nighttime square with stars twinkling above, some Spanish-era colonial buildings, a restaurant, and a market selling various Mexican items.</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">63608</field>
		<field name="title">Walt Disney World/Epcot</field>
		<field name="main">see and do</field>
		<field name="section">world showcase</field>
		<field name="name">norway</field>
		<field name="content">The Stave Church at Norway   left   This area is built as a square representing a few  Norwegian  towns. The fortress-like restaurant building is modeled and named after the Akershus fortress in  Oslo , guarding the sea approach to the city. The huge wooden church is a replica of the traditional Stave Church in  Gol  in Western Norway, dating back to 1212; the original is one of very few surviving ancient wooden churches left in the world. A mock-up of a Viking longboat sits outside and serves as a playground for kids.</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">63609</field>
		<field name="title">Walt Disney World/Epcot</field>
		<field name="main">see and do</field>
		<field name="section">world showcase</field>
		<field name="sub-section">norway</field>
		<field name="name">Maelstrom</field>
		<field name="content">Ride a Viking boat through Norways storybook lands, with Vikings, cursing trolls and oil platforms! Mostly indoors. The ships are loosely modeled after those sailed by Eric The Red, who colonized  Greenland  and was central to the Vikings discovery of  North America , five centuries before Christopher Columbus. You can enjoy a travel film afterward.</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">63610</field>
		<field name="title">Walt Disney World/Epcot</field>
		<field name="main">see and do</field>
		<field name="section">world showcase</field>
		<field name="name">china</field>
		<field name="content">left   Walk through the large Paifang gate. These gates were used in ancient  China  to mark entry into a new division (called Fang in Chinese), and this one is a replica of one in  Beijing s summer palace. The courtyard is dominated by a large recreation of the Temple of Heaven in Beijing; it was used by the emperors to pray for a good harvest. The 12 columns supporting the roof represent the 12 months of the Chinese year, and the four columns in the center represent the four seasons. Many of the smaller buildings are recreations of the Forbidden City, also in Beijing. If all the Asian culture gets you in a meditative mood, the rough Chinese gardens are one of the most peaceful spots in Epcot.</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">63611</field>
		<field name="title">Walt Disney World/Epcot</field>
		<field name="main">see and do</field>
		<field name="section">world showcase</field>
		<field name="sub-section">china</field>
		<field name="name">Reflections of China</field>
		<field name="content">A Circle-Vision 360, 13-minute travel movie of Chinas most well-known sights, from  Shanghai  and  Inner Mongolia , to the Forbidden City and the  Great Wall of China .</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">63612</field>
		<field name="title">Walt Disney World/Epcot</field>
		<field name="main">see and do</field>
		<field name="section">world showcase</field>
		<field name="name">germany</field>
		<field name="content">left   Germany  is a federation of 16 states, each with a separate and distinct culture and identity. The architecture of the German pavilion reflects styles from various regions of the country; for example, the Biergarten restaurant is  Bavaria n, but the statue of St. George slaying the dragon represents the state of  North Rhine-Westphalia . Of course, the influence of German architecture on Disney parks goes all the way back to 1955; Neuschwanstein Castle in Bavaria, commissioned in 1869 by King Ludwig II, was the inspiration for Disneylands Sleeping Beauty Castle.  There are no rides here, and the only show is the band inside the Biergarten, but theres plenty of shopping to be had.</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">63613</field>
		<field name="title">Walt Disney World/Epcot</field>
		<field name="main">see and do</field>
		<field name="section">world showcase</field>
		<field name="name">italy</field>
		<field name="content">left   The  Italian  pavilion is a scaled-down replica of St. Marks Square in  Venice , right down to the bell tower (one-fifth scale) and the gondolas floating in World Showcase Lagoon. The original Doges Palace makes heavy use of marble; Disney recreated the effect with fiberglass. In addition to the Venetian architecture, a stucco building with tile roof represents  Tuscany .  The pavilion has no rides or theater shows; the main attractions are the shops and the restaurants. You might also catch the World Showcase Players performing their audience-participation comedy skit Kiss Me Shrew.</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">63614</field>
		<field name="title">Walt Disney World/Epcot</field>
		<field name="main">see and do</field>
		<field name="section">world showcase</field>
		<field name="sub-section">the american adventure</field>
		<field name="name">The American Adventure</field>
		<field name="content">It turns out that the best show in World Showcase is the one for the host nation. This inspirational and informative presentation combines film and Audio-Animatronics to take you through every era of American history, with Ben Franklin and Mark Twain as your hosts. Dont mistake this show for the Hall of Presidents; the latter is impressive for putting 43 presidents on stage at the same time, but The American Adventure has a wider variety of on-stage effects and scenery. The theater is cavernous (and air-conditioned) but never crowded.</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">63615</field>
		<field name="title">Walt Disney World/Epcot</field>
		<field name="main">see and do</field>
		<field name="section">world showcase</field>
		<field name="sub-section">the american adventure</field>
		<field name="name">America Gardens Theater</field>
		<field name="content">Across from the main building, on the shores of the lagoon, is this amphitheater, where any number of events might be scheduled. Check your Times Guide for details.</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">63616</field>
		<field name="title">Walt Disney World/Epcot</field>
		<field name="main">see and do</field>
		<field name="section">world showcase</field>
		<field name="name">the american adventure</field>
		<field name="content">left   The  United States of America  pavilion is housed in a building inspired by the colonial period of the 18th century. Inside, keep an ear out for the Voices of Liberty chorus, who perform throughout the day.</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">63617</field>
		<field name="title">Walt Disney World/Epcot</field>
		<field name="main">see and do</field>
		<field name="section">world showcase</field>
		<field name="sub-section">the american adventure</field>
		<field name="name">American Heritage Gallery</field>
		<field name="content">Inside the pavilion is this exhibit space, which changes occasionally to spotlight different aspects of American art or history. The current exhibit is  "Re-Discovering America: Family Treasures from the Kinsey Collection" , which focuses on African-American people and history.</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">63618</field>
		<field name="title">Walt Disney World/Epcot</field>
		<field name="main">see and do</field>
		<field name="section">world showcase</field>
		<field name="sub-section">japan</field>
		<field name="name">Bijutsu-Kan Gallery</field>
		<field name="content">Inside this replica of the White Heron Castle, modeled after part of the famous  Himeji  castle in Japan, are changing exhibits on Japanese culture. The current exhibit is "Spirit Beasts: From Ancient Stories to Anime Stars", which traces the influence of ancient Japanese folklore on todays anime and manga.</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">63619</field>
		<field name="title">Walt Disney World/Epcot</field>
		<field name="main">see and do</field>
		<field name="section">world showcase</field>
		<field name="name">japan</field>
		<field name="content">left   Mitsukoshi, a Japanese retailer founded in 1673, is the sponsor of the  Japan  pavilion. All the touristy classics of Japan are recreated, in a way that has little to do with reality. Start your visit by walking through the Torii gate. In Japan you walk through these gates before entering a Shinto shrine, to mark the passing into the spiritual world. The five-story Goju-no-to Pagoda was inspired by the Horyuji Temple in  Nara , Japans ancient capital. Rather oddly, it is named after the five Chinese elements, but built in five stories to represent the 5 Japanese elements: Earth, Water, Fire, Wind and Void. Surrounding it all is a large Japanese inspired garden, complete with koi fish swimming around in the ponds.</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">63620</field>
		<field name="title">Walt Disney World/Epcot</field>
		<field name="main">see and do</field>
		<field name="section">world showcase</field>
		<field name="sub-section">morocco</field>
		<field name="name">Gallery of Arts and History</field>
		<field name="content">This gallery features exhibits of Moroccan science, music and technology.</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">63621</field>
		<field name="title">Walt Disney World/Epcot</field>
		<field name="main">see and do</field>
		<field name="section">world showcase</field>
		<field name="name">morocco</field>
		<field name="content">The recreation of the Koutoubia Minaret at Morocco   left    Morocco s is the only pavilion sponsored by a government. King Hassan II was heavily involved in the construction, and he dispatched native craftsmen to build the pavilion. The minaret (or tower) towering over the area is a recreation of the unique Koutoubia Minaret in  Marrakech , which has inspired thousands of church towers across Europe. In Muslim countries priests call for prayers (fard) from these towers five times a day. The pavilion also holds a small recreation of parts of the Chellah necropolis, a burial place located in  Rabat  that is actually an ancient Roman structure. There is also a replica of the Nejjarine fountain in  Fez , a very intricate mosaic fountain. Also from Fez, the evenly-tiled Bab Boujouloud gate marks the border between the old town (the Medina) and the new town. Inside the Medina, there is a bustling market place, or bazaar. Because many of the structures, even as replicas, holds great religious significance to Muslims, the buildings are not lighted during the IllumiNations show.</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">63622</field>
		<field name="title">Walt Disney World/Epcot</field>
		<field name="main">see and do</field>
		<field name="section">world showcase</field>
		<field name="name">france</field>
		<field name="content">left   The  French  pavilion re-creates a  Paris ian street scene, complete with a miniature Eiffel Tower that uses forced perspective to appear as if its off in the distance. Designed to represent Paris during La Belle Epoque, the pavilion features many of the typical Parisian sightsmdash;a sidewalk cafe, beautiful fountains, and distinctive architecture. Theres a park, next to the International Gateway canal, based on Seurats A Sunday Afternoon on the Island of La Grande Jatte. Le Petit Rue, The Little Street in the back of the pavilion, represents rural France.  The World Showcase Players stop by France now and then, performing their comedic audience-participation skit, Cyranose de Bergerac. Serveur Amusant! is a humorous acrobatic show played out on the street of the pavilion five times a week.</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">63623</field>
		<field name="title">Walt Disney World/Epcot</field>
		<field name="main">see and do</field>
		<field name="section">world showcase</field>
		<field name="sub-section">france</field>
		<field name="name">Impressions de France</field>
		<field name="content">A travel movie through the French countryside with a classical music soundtrack.</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">63624</field>
		<field name="title">Walt Disney World/Epcot</field>
		<field name="main">see and do</field>
		<field name="section">world showcase</field>
		<field name="name">united kingdom</field>
		<field name="content">left   This pavilions street contains one building for each century of  British  history. The largest structure, a recreation of the royal Hampton Court Palace in southwest  London , is massive patchwork of different periods architecture, since it was successively expanded to compete with the French palace of  Versailles . Elsewhere the adorable little thatched roof house is a model of Anne Hathaway’s cottage in  Stratford-upon-Avon . Anne was the wife of William Shakespeare. There is also a traditional hedge maze, modelled after the Somerleyton Hall Maze in  Lowestoft , which dates back to 1846. Dont forget to get a photo of yourself in front of the iconic red British phone booths.  Keep an eye out for the World Showcase Players, who perform either King Arthur The Holy Grail or My Unfair Lady, which are audience-participation comedy sketches.  The United Kingdom stage is where youll find the British Revolution, a tribute band playing "British Invasion" pop and rock music from the 1960s and 70s. Check the Times Guide for the schedule.</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">63625</field>
		<field name="title">Walt Disney World/Epcot</field>
		<field name="main">see and do</field>
		<field name="section">world showcase</field>
		<field name="sub-section">canada</field>
		<field name="name">O Canada!</field>
		<field name="content">A Circle-Vision 360 travel movie, named after Canadas national anthem and narrated by Martin Short.</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">63626</field>
		<field name="title">Walt Disney World/Epcot</field>
		<field name="main">see and do</field>
		<field name="section">world showcase</field>
		<field name="name">canada</field>
		<field name="content">left   The mountains, Indian wood carvings, and the (fake) hotel all represent various regions of  Canada . Victoria Gardens was inspired by Butchart Gardens in  Victoria  in British Columbia, while the Hotel du Canada features a 19th-century chateau-style design. Around the base of the hotel is a village-like atmosphere evoking the  Maritime Provinces . The totem pole was carved in 1998 by David Boxley, working "on-stage" in front of guests at the Canada pavilion.     Between the United Kingdom and Canada pavilions is the stage for  Off Kilter , a hard-driving Celtic rock band with kilts and a bagpiper. Well worth a listen; check your Times Guide for the schedule.</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">63627</field>
		<field name="title">Walt Disney World/Epcot</field>
		<field name="main">see and do</field>
		<field name="name">world showcase</field>
		<field name="content">World Showcase is the back area of the park, with pavilions representing eleven countries from around the world, all themed with architecture, food, drink and culture to match. Most of the pavilions have a ride or a film (or both) designed to highlight the nations attractions, but the real attractions are sampling the authentic food, conversing with the cast members who come from each nation, and browsing the imported goods.   The host nations pavilionmdash;the American Adventure   World Showcase is where youll find the International Gateway, Epcots back entrance, located between the United Kingdom and France pavilions. If youre coming in from Disneys Hollywood Studios, the Swan/Dolphin, Yacht/Beach Clubs, or BoardWalk, you can walk or take the ferry to Epcot and enter here.  Each of the pavilions will have some sort of entertainment occurring periodically throughout the day, from jugglers and "living statues" to musical groups and dancers. Some of the highlights are noted below, but check your Times Guide for the details of whats happening on any particular day.</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">63628</field>
		<field name="title">Walt Disney World/Epcot</field>
		<field name="main">see and do</field>
		<field name="section">parkwide</field>
		<field name="sub-section">tours</field>
		<field name="name">The UnDISCOVERed Future World</field>
		<field name="content">A lengthy walking tour around all of Future World, including some backstage areas. Learn about the history and design principles behind each pavilion, meet an International Ambassador, and see how things are done behind-the-scenes. 4ndash;4.5 hours. Must be 16 or older.</field>
		<field name="price">$45</field>
		<field name="hours">M W F 9AM</field>
		<field name="url">http://disneyworld.disney.go.com/tours-and-experiences/un-discovered-future-world/</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">63629</field>
		<field name="title">Walt Disney World/Epcot</field>
		<field name="main">see and do</field>
		<field name="section">parkwide</field>
		<field name="name">tours</field>
		<field name="content">Some very popular tours are available at  The Land  and, especially, at  The Seas with Nemo Friends . There is also a park-wide tour. All tours can be booked by calling +1 407 WDW-TOUR (939-8687).  For the park-wide tour, you will need separate admission to the park.  ndash;115nbsp;kg). }}  15px  --></field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">63630</field>
		<field name="title">Walt Disney World/Epcot</field>
		<field name="main">see and do</field>
		<field name="section">parkwide</field>
		<field name="name">Agent Ps World Showcase Adventure</field>
		<field name="content">An interactive adventure, designed to be both entertaining and educational. Agent P, the secret-agent platypus from Phineas and Ferb, needs your help. Your assignment: save the world from Dr. Heinz Doofenshmirtz in adventures across seven World Showcase pavilions (Mexico, Norway, China, Germany, Japan, France, United Kingdom). Pick up your FONE communications device at locations throughout the park.</field>
		<field name="alt">formerly Kim Possible World Showcase Adventure</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">63631</field>
		<field name="title">Walt Disney World/Epcot</field>
		<field name="main">see and do</field>
		<field name="section">parkwide</field>
		<field name="name">Kidcot Fun Stops</field>
		<field name="content">Designed for preschoolers, there are 13 of these craft stations throughout the park; theres one at each World Showcase pavilion, plus one at The Land and one at The Seas with Nemo Friends. Kids can meet cast members from around the world and decorate paper-puppets of Duffy the Disney Bear (or Agent P) with elements specific to each location. Theyll also find "Race Around World Showcase" stations, which tie into the film Cars 2. Great fun for the littlest visitors, and it allows them to connect with the message of Epcot in a way more suited to their level of understanding.</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">63632</field>
		<field name="title">Walt Disney World/Epcot</field>
		<field name="main">see and do</field>
		<field name="section">parkwide</field>
		<field name="name">IllumiNations: Reflections of Earth</field>
		<field name="content">At park closing, enjoy this extravagant display of fireworks, lasers, fountains and electric lighting over World Showcase Lagoon.</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">63633</field>
		<field name="title">Walt Disney World/Epcot</field>
		<field name="main">see and do</field>
		<field name="name">parkwide</field>
		<field name="content">IllumiNations</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">63634</field>
		<field name="title">Walt Disney World/Epcot</field>
		<field name="main">see and do</field>
		<field name="name">annual events</field>
		<field name="content">Epcot is home to two annual festivals, several concert series, and an annual holiday presentation. Both of the festivals have things to see and do throughout the park, while the Candlelight Processional is a nightly event at one location. All three are quite popular; some people make it a point to attend one or more of these each year, sometimes without even visiting the rest of Walt Disney World. The concert series are more of a bonus to visitors who are already there (in particular, two of them coincide with the festivals) but if the timings right, youre in for a treat.</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">63635</field>
		<field name="title">Walt Disney World/Epcot</field>
		<field name="main">see and do</field>
		<field name="section">annual events</field>
		<field name="name">Epcot International Food Wine Festival</field>
		<field name="content">The centerpiece of this festival is the international marketplace and promenade, with more than 25 kiosks serving dishes and drinks from six continents. Seminars, demonstrations, wine tastings, and all sorts of shopping are also available throughout the festival. The evening "Eat to the Beat!" concert series at the America Gardens Theater focuses on jazz, funk, and RB.</field>
		<field name="directions">parkwide</field>
		<field name="hours">Oct - mid-Nov</field>
		<field name="url">http://disneyworld.disney.go.com/parks/epcot/special-events/epcot-international-food-and-wine-festival/</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">63636</field>
		<field name="title">Walt Disney World/Epcot</field>
		<field name="main">see and do</field>
		<field name="section">annual events</field>
		<field name="name">Sounds Like Summer Concert Series</field>
		<field name="content">Tribute bands take the stage, each for a week of three shows nightly, to play the hits of favorite artists from the last fifty years. The 2011 series featured, among others, bands playing the music of U2, Eagles, Janet Jackson, and the Bee Gees.</field>
		<field name="directions">at the America Gardens Theater in World Showcase</field>
		<field name="hours">Nightly, mid Jun - late Jul: 5:45PM, 7PM, 8:15PM; Jul 4: 5:15PM, 6:30PM, 7:45PM, 9PM</field>
		<field name="url">http://disneyworld.disney.go.com/parks/epcot/special-events/sounds-like-summer-concerts/</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">63637</field>
		<field name="title">Walt Disney World/Epcot</field>
		<field name="main">see and do</field>
		<field name="section">annual events</field>
		<field name="name">Epcot International Flower Garden Festival</field>
		<field name="content">With millions of flowers on displaymdash;rotated three times during the festival to account for different blooming timesmdash;Epcot is a sight to see in the spring. Check out the butterfly garden, attend horticultural demonstrations and instructional programs, or just wander aroundmdash;nearly every pavilion has a special event or feature during the festival. Weekend nights, the Flower Power Concert Series at the America Gardens Theater features classic rock and pop musicians from the 60s and 70s. Dozens of other special events are on the schedule, too many to list here.</field>
		<field name="directions">parkwide</field>
		<field name="hours">Early Mar - mid-May</field>
		<field name="url">http://disneyworld.disney.go.com/parks/epcot/special-events/epcot-international-flower-and-garden-festival/</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">63638</field>
		<field name="title">Walt Disney World/Epcot</field>
		<field name="main">see and do</field>
		<field name="section">annual events</field>
		<field name="name">Candlelight Processional</field>
		<field name="content">Every night between Thanksgiving and New Years, a celebrity narrator reads the Christmas story accompanied by a 50-piece orchestra and a choir. The narrators in 2011 included Geena Davis, Edward James Olmos, Neil Patrick Harris, and Marlee Matlin, and others. Disneys theatrical flair is applied well to this celebratory but sedate event.</field>
		<field name="directions">at the America Gardens Theater in World Showcase</field>
		<field name="hours">Nightly, late Nov - late Dec: 5PM, 6:45PM, 8PM</field>
		<field name="url">http://disneyworld.disney.go.com/parks/epcot/special-events/candlelight-processional/</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">63639</field>
		<field name="title">Walt Disney World/Epcot</field>
		<field name="main">see and do</field>
		<field name="name">disneys boardwalk</field>
		<field name="content">Disneys BoardWalk is just a short walk or ferry ride beyond Epcots International Gateway. Its a resort, yes, but the side facing Crescent Lake is themed as a 1920s Eastern Seaboard boardwalk, with shops, amusements, dining, and nighttime entertainment. Rent a pedaled "surrey bike" and circle the lake, purchase a caricature of yourself, watch an impromptu magic show, buy some cotton candy, or just sit on a bench and watch the people go by. Be sure to check out the  Buy ,  Eat , and  Drink  sections for all the details.</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">63640</field>
		<field name="title">Walt Disney World/Epcot</field>
		<field name="main">see and do</field>
		<field name="section">disneys boardwalk</field>
		<field name="name">Bayside Marina</field>
		<field name="content">Just around the bend from the BoardWalk is the Yacht Clubs Bayside Marina, where a huge array of boats are available for rent or charter. Rental options range from single-person Sea Raycers ($24/half-hour) to 10-passenger pontoon boats ($42/half-hour). Chartered options run the gamut, from fishing and dining cruises, to a cruise down the way to Epcot to watch IllumiNations from the World Showcase Lagoon. Send the kids on a treasure-hunting pirate cruise, or customize your own excursion. (Advance reservations strongly suggested for any chartered excursion; call +1 407 WDW-PLAY to make them.)</field>
		<field name="directions">at the Yacht Club</field>
		<field name="price">$24 and up</field>
		<field name="hours">10AM-5PM</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">63641</field>
		<field name="title">Walt Disney World/Epcot</field>
		<field name="main">see and do</field>
		<field name="section">fantasia gardens</field>
		<field name="name">Fantasia Gardens</field>
		<field name="content">Just southwest of the Walt Disney World Swan hotel is a whimsical pair of 18-hole miniature golf courses. True to the name, the area is themed around the 1940 animated feature Fantasia. The "Fantasia Gardens" course is the more traditional of the two, with big, colorful courses and obstacles and a few special surprises to boot. The "Fantasia Fairways" course is like a real golf course in miniaturemdash;rolling fairways, sand traps, and no rails to keep your ball from going off into the rough. Its much harder, too; young kids should stick to the Gardens course or head to Winter Summerland at Blizzard Beach.</field>
		<field name="directions">walk west, then south from the Swan</field>
		<field name="phone">+1 407 560-8760</field>
		<field name="price">Adults $12, children $10 per 18 holes (second round, same day, is half price). Before 4PM, a Water Park Fun More option can be used for one round of golf</field>
		<field name="hours">10AM-11PM</field>
		<field name="url">http://disneyworld.disney.go.com/recreation/miniature-golf/</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">63642</field>
		<field name="title">Walt Disney World/Hollywood Studios</field>
		<field name="main">see and do</field>
		<field name="section">hollywood boulevard</field>
		<field name="name">The Great Movie Ride</field>
		<field name="content">A slow-moving ride through scenes from some of the greatest movies, recreated using Audio-Animatronics, including Alien, The Wizard of Oz, Raiders of the Lost Ark, and Mary Poppins.  But remember: in the movies, not everything is as it seems!  This is a great choice for your first ride of the day, to really get you in the mood and mindset of the whole park.  The incredible attention to detail means you see something new every time you ride it.</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">63643</field>
		<field name="title">Walt Disney World/Hollywood Studios</field>
		<field name="main">see and do</field>
		<field name="name">hollywood boulevard</field>
		<field name="content">Hollywood Boulevard is mostly a location for shops, restaurants, and Streetmosphere, but at its far end is where youll find the parks centerpiece attraction, the Great Movie Ride.  While youre at the Chinese Theater, be sure to check out the cement plaza in frontmdash;just like at the real Chinese Theater in Hollywood, youll find a number of celebrities have placed their handprints and signatures there.  Everyone from Donald Duck and R2-D2 to Carol Burnett and Michael Jackson has left his or her mark.</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">63644</field>
		<field name="title">Walt Disney World/Hollywood Studios</field>
		<field name="main">see and do</field>
		<field name="section">sunset boulevard</field>
		<field name="name">Beauty and the Beast: Live on Stage</field>
		<field name="content">A 20-minute condensation of the popular animated film.  Its more "cartoony" than the Broadway musical you may have seen, but its great for kids who may not sit through a longer production.  Colorful costumes and the classic songs make for an entertaining time.</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">63645</field>
		<field name="title">Walt Disney World/Hollywood Studios</field>
		<field name="main">see and do</field>
		<field name="section">sunset boulevard</field>
		<field name="name">The Twilight Zone Tower of Terror</field>
		<field name="content">Rod Serling himself welcomes you into this mystery, involving an elevator on the thirteenth floor, a late-night lightning strike, and vanished guests.  Most people ignore the story, though, and just go on this ride for the 13-story free-fall down the elevator shaft, followed by a random sequence of sudden rising and falling.  Not for the faint of stomach, period.  The view from the top is quite a sight, if you can open your eyes long enough to look.  The pre-ride area of the attraction is filled with references both obscure and subtle to various episodes of the TV show.</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">63646</field>
		<field name="title">Walt Disney World/Hollywood Studios</field>
		<field name="main">see and do</field>
		<field name="section">sunset boulevard</field>
		<field name="name">Fantasmic!</field>
		<field name="content">Watch as Mickey Mouse uses the power of imagination to defeat some of Disneys nastiest villains.  Live-action nighttime extravaganza with outstanding film and lighting effects, fireworks, and a 50-foot animatronic dragon.  The theater fills up quickly, so get there early if you want a seat.  Reserved seating is available if you purchase a dining package.</field>
		<field name="hours">Performed nightly after dark; check the Times Guide for details</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">63647</field>
		<field name="title">Walt Disney World/Hollywood Studios</field>
		<field name="main">see and do</field>
		<field name="name">sunset boulevard</field>
		<field name="content">In addition to more shops, restaurants, and Streetmosphere, Sunset Boulevard is home to the Studios two major stage shows and its two popular mega-thrill rides.         15px      15px</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">63648</field>
		<field name="title">Walt Disney World/Hollywood Studios</field>
		<field name="main">see and do</field>
		<field name="section">sunset boulevard</field>
		<field name="name">Rock n Roller Coaster Starring Aerosmith</field>
		<field name="content">Hop into your "limousine" and take a wild ride through the streets of Los Angeles to get to Aerosmiths concert.  The only roller coaster at Walt Disney World with inversions, this indoor launched coaster accelerates you from zero to 60 miles per hour in three seconds.  An exciting but fairly smooth ride, its accompanied by the (very loud) music of Aerosmith and decorated with bright fluorescent signs that obscure any view of the track, so you never know where youre headed next.</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">63649</field>
		<field name="title">Walt Disney World/Hollywood Studios</field>
		<field name="main">see and do</field>
		<field name="section">animation courtyard/pixar place</field>
		<field name="name">Voyage of the Little Mermaid</field>
		<field name="content">Go "Under The Sea" with Ariel and friends in this live stage show featuring black-lit puppets and costumes.  Very imaginative and colorful, with some intriguing special effects.  Fairly popular, it can get crowded at times.</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">63650</field>
		<field name="title">Walt Disney World/Hollywood Studios</field>
		<field name="main">see and do</field>
		<field name="name">animation courtyard/pixar place</field>
		<field name="content">Through the iconic gate is this courtyard, which segues into Mickey Avenue and Pixar Place as it heads toward the back of the park.  There used to be working sound stages along Mickey Avenue, but theyve been converted into semi-permanent exhibit space and, of course, Toy Story Mania!.</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">63651</field>
		<field name="title">Walt Disney World/Hollywood Studios</field>
		<field name="main">see and do</field>
		<field name="section">animation courtyard/pixar place</field>
		<field name="name">Walt Disney: One Mans Dream</field>
		<field name="content">A walk-through exhibition of Walts life and career, including how he built the global entertainment empire that bears his name.  Artifacts and diagrams galore, so Disney history fans will have a ball.  Your average kid or thrill-seeker, on the other hand, is likely to get bored five minutes in.</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">63652</field>
		<field name="title">Walt Disney World/Hollywood Studios</field>
		<field name="main">see and do</field>
		<field name="section">animation courtyard/pixar place</field>
		<field name="name">Pirates of the Caribbean: The Legend of Jack Sparrow</field>
		<field name="content">A walk-through attraction takes you into the wildly popular film series, with actual artifacts from the production.  Some scenes may be too intense for young children.</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">63653</field>
		<field name="title">Walt Disney World/Hollywood Studios</field>
		<field name="main">see and do</field>
		<field name="section">animation courtyard/pixar place</field>
		<field name="name">Toy Story Mania!</field>
		<field name="content">Possibly the most popular attraction in all of Walt Disney World, this 3-D virtual midway game, complete with moving targets and special effects, is themed around the characters from Toy Story.  Great fun for all ages, but visitors with aiming skills honed by years of video game playing will get higher scores.  Due to its popularity, Fastpasses go very quickly, especially on weekends.</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">63654</field>
		<field name="title">Walt Disney World/Hollywood Studios</field>
		<field name="main">see and do</field>
		<field name="section">animation courtyard/pixar place</field>
		<field name="name">Disney Junior ndash; Live on Stage!</field>
		<field name="content">A cute audience-participation (dancing and singing) stage show featuring characters from the Disney Channels programs for preschoolers.  Dont even bother bringing anyone over the age of 7.  Warning to parents with creaky knees: seating is on the floor.</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">63655</field>
		<field name="title">Walt Disney World/Hollywood Studios</field>
		<field name="main">see and do</field>
		<field name="section">animation courtyard/pixar place</field>
		<field name="name">The Magic of Disney Animation</field>
		<field name="content">Once upon a time, this was a tour that offered guests a peek at an actual working animation studio.  The studio is gone but the name remains, to some a sad reminder of what once was (both for the park and for Disney animation in general).  The attraction still lets you view mock-ups of a couple of animators workspaces, but now leads to a large open area where various Disney characters are available for photos and autographs.  There are also several computer workstations allowing you to insert your own voice or image into brief film clips, and an instructional class that teaches you the basics of drawing a Disney character.</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">63656</field>
		<field name="title">Walt Disney World/Hollywood Studios</field>
		<field name="main">see and do</field>
		<field name="name">backlot/streets of america</field>
		<field name="content">A motorcycle stunt from Lights, Motors, Action!   The Backlot is mostly a gateway to the Studio Backlot Tour, serving to connect Pixar Place with the Streets of America.  In the Streets of America, youll find façades set up to give the illusion of walking down streets in New York City and San Francisco, using the movie-making technique called "forced perspective".  These streets are also where youll find the  Osborne Family Spectacle of Dancing Lights  every holiday season.  Cars fans will find Lightning McQueen and Tow Mater parked at The Winners Circle, ready to pose for pictures.</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">63657</field>
		<field name="title">Walt Disney World/Hollywood Studios</field>
		<field name="main">see and do</field>
		<field name="section">backlot/streets of america</field>
		<field name="name">Lights, Motors, Action! Extreme Stunt Show</field>
		<field name="content">Imported from Disneyland Resort Paris, this live show features high-intensity (and highly dangerous) live action stunt driving.  Kids, dont try this at home!  A new segment features Lightning McQueen from the Cars films.</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">63658</field>
		<field name="title">Walt Disney World/Hollywood Studios</field>
		<field name="main">see and do</field>
		<field name="section">backlot/streets of america</field>
		<field name="name">MuppetVision 3-D</field>
		<field name="content">A hilarious show featuring the Muppet characters, shown in a detailed replica of the Muppet Theater.  You have to see it to believe it.  The combination of a 3-D film, in-theater animatronics and special effects, and a special live-action appearance makes for an immersive show.  The pre-show, held in a staging area while the previous main show runs, is just as good as the main show; if its not too crowded, ask a cast member if you can stay to see the whole thing.  The queue area and the pre-show area are overflowing with sight gags and bad puns.  You will never see them all in just one trip. Closing for refurbishment August 6 ndash; September 2, 2013.</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">63659</field>
		<field name="title">Walt Disney World/Hollywood Studios</field>
		<field name="main">see and do</field>
		<field name="section">backlot/streets of america</field>
		<field name="name">Honey, I Shrunk the Kids - Movie Set Adventure</field>
		<field name="content">A huge play area that makes you look and feel like youre a quarter of an inch tall.  Totally safe for kids to run around and climb on everything, from spider webs to anthills.  Older folks can look for giant-sized versions of famous objects like a roll of Kodak film and a can of Play-Doh, but watch out for the dogs nosemdash;hes been known to sneeze! Closing for refurbishment September 3 ndash; November 19, 2013.</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">63660</field>
		<field name="title">Walt Disney World/Hollywood Studios</field>
		<field name="main">see and do</field>
		<field name="section">backlot/streets of america</field>
		<field name="name">Studio Backlot Tour</field>
		<field name="content">Starts off with a demonstration of special effects techniques in a giant water tank, with one lucky tour-goer getting to star in a water-soaked film clip.  You will then board a tram for a tour of old Disney and Lucasfilm movie props and the former production studios.  The highlight of the tour is Catastrophe Canyon, where you can experience some disastrous special effects up-closemdash;its water cannons, for example, are strong enough to shoot a basketball over the Empire State Building.</field>
		<field name="hours">Continuous 25-minute tours</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">63661</field>
		<field name="title">Walt Disney World/Hollywood Studios</field>
		<field name="main">see and do</field>
		<field name="section">echo lake</field>
		<field name="name">Star Tours: The Adventures Continue</field>
		<field name="content">The much-loved (but 23-year-old) Star Tours ride closed in 2010, but this "prequel" to the original takes Star Wars fans to new locations in that galaxy far, far away.  An upgraded motion-simulation system, a 3D screen, and over fifty combinations of scene sequences mean that this ride will remain crowded for years to come.</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">63662</field>
		<field name="title">Walt Disney World/Hollywood Studios</field>
		<field name="main">see and do</field>
		<field name="name">echo lake</field>
		<field name="content">On one side of Echo Lake is a large steamboat, known as Min and Bills Dockside Diner; on the other is a large dinosaur, with Dinosaur Gerties Ice Cream of Extinction.  Around the perimeter of the area are attractions based on Lucasfilm properties, restaurants, and a couple of soundstages.</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">63663</field>
		<field name="title">Walt Disney World/Hollywood Studios</field>
		<field name="main">see and do</field>
		<field name="section">echo lake</field>
		<field name="name">Indiana Jones Epic Stunt Spectacular</field>
		<field name="content">An exciting 35-minute live-action stunt show recreating some of the best scenes from Raiders of the Lost Ark.  A few lucky audience members might even get to appear on stage as extras.</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">63664</field>
		<field name="title">Walt Disney World/Hollywood Studios</field>
		<field name="main">see and do</field>
		<field name="section">echo lake</field>
		<field name="name">The Academy of Television Arts Sciences Hall of Fame Plaza</field>
		<field name="content">Not much of an attraction or even an exhibit, this plaza between the ABC Sound Studio and American Idol showcases a gigantic Emmy statue and busts of famous television personalities from Milton Berle to Bill Cosby.  Its nothing exciting, but might be worth five minutes to look at while youre waiting for your Fastpass time.</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">63665</field>
		<field name="title">Walt Disney World/Hollywood Studios</field>
		<field name="main">see and do</field>
		<field name="section">echo lake</field>
		<field name="name">The American Idol Experience</field>
		<field name="content">Sure, you can sit in the audience and watch this attraction, but wouldnt you rather be up there on stage?  You can!  Sign up first thing in the day for an audition slot, and you might find yourself singing on-stage in front of your fellow park guests and an entertaining panel of judges, competing for the grand prize: a Dream Ticket to audition for the actual American Idol TV show!</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">63666</field>
		<field name="title">Walt Disney World/Hollywood Studios</field>
		<field name="main">see and do</field>
		<field name="section">annual events</field>
		<field name="name">Disney STEP Classic</field>
		<field name="content">Youth step teams from around the country come to Hollywood Studios to enjoy workshops and a big competition on the last day.</field>
		<field name="directions">Premiere Theater, Streets of America</field>
		<field name="hours">Early Sep</field>
		<field name="url">http://www.disneyyouth.com/step-classic/</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">63667</field>
		<field name="title">Walt Disney World/Hollywood Studios</field>
		<field name="main">see and do</field>
		<field name="section">annual events</field>
		<field name="name">Osborne Family Spectacle of Dancing Lights</field>
		<field name="content">Each year, the Streets of America are transformed into an enormous Christmas display.  At Walt Disney World in December, Christmas decorations are all over the place, but the Osborne Family display (moved here when it got too big for the Osborne family home) takes them to the next level.  Its very popular; be ready for wall-to-wall people.</field>
		<field name="directions">Streets of America</field>
		<field name="hours">mid Nov-early Jan</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">63668</field>
		<field name="title">Walt Disney World/Hollywood Studios</field>
		<field name="main">see and do</field>
		<field name="section">annual events</field>
		<field name="name">Star Wars Weekends</field>
		<field name="content">For four weekends every spring, stormtroopers and Rebel heroes descend on Hollywood Studios to meet their fans.  These very popular weekends feature a parade, character appearances throughout the park, trivia events, the Jedi Training Academy for kids, and special events with selected actors from the films.</field>
		<field name="directions">parkwide</field>
		<field name="hours">F-Su, mid May-mid Jun</field>
		<field name="url">http://disneyworld.disney.go.com/parks/hollywood-studios/special-events/star-wars-weekend/</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">63669</field>
		<field name="title">Walt Disney World/Hollywood Studios</field>
		<field name="main">see and do</field>
		<field name="section">espn wide world of sports</field>
		<field name="name">Old Spice Classic</field>
		<field name="content">Since 2006, college basketball fans have been able to catch eight top Division I teams playing a total of twelve games in this early-season tournament.</field>
		<field name="hours">Late Nov</field>
		<field name="alt">college basketball</field>
		<field name="url">http://www.oldspiceclassic.com</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">63670</field>
		<field name="title">Walt Disney World/Hollywood Studios</field>
		<field name="main">see and do</field>
		<field name="section">espn wide world of sports</field>
		<field name="name">ESPN RISE Games</field>
		<field name="content">Two weeks of competition featuring some of the best young athletes in the country.  High school athletes compete in basketball, soccer, lacrosse, and football; youth teams will show what they can do in baseball, basketball, field hockey, lacrosse, and track field.</field>
		<field name="hours">Mid- to late-Jul</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">63671</field>
		<field name="title">Walt Disney World/Hollywood Studios</field>
		<field name="main">see and do</field>
		<field name="section">espn wide world of sports</field>
		<field name="name">Champion Stadium</field>
		<field name="content">A 9,500-seat baseball stadium.  The Atlanta Braves play their spring training games here, and the Rookie-league GCL Braves play here all summer.  Other events occur throughout the year.</field>
		<field name="directions">World Dr to Osceola Pkwy, east to Victory Way</field>
		<field name="price">$0–$32</field>
		<field name="address">700 S Victory Way</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">63672</field>
		<field name="title">Walt Disney World/Hollywood Studios</field>
		<field name="main">see and do</field>
		<field name="section">espn wide world of sports</field>
		<field name="name">Walt Disney World Pro Soccer Classic</field>
		<field name="content">In whats shaping up to be an annual event, six Major League Soccer teams and two local minor-league teams take part in a spring training tournament.</field>
		<field name="directions">Hess Sports Field</field>
		<field name="price">$15.50 per session (2 games per session, 2 sessions per day), $99 for entire event; discounts for supporters of participating teams</field>
		<field name="hours">throughout February</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">63673</field>
		<field name="title">Walt Disney World/Hollywood Studios</field>
		<field name="main">see and do</field>
		<field name="name">espn wide world of sports</field>
		<field name="content">South of Hollywood Studios is the ESPN Wide World of Sports complex (formerly Disneys Wide World of Sports), a state-of-the-art sports complex with fields, stadiums, and arenas for a variety of sporting events.   The complex is the flagship facility of the  Amateur Athletic Union , which has its headquarters on Hotel Plaza Boulevard in the Downtown Disney area. Regularly-scheduled AAU-sanctioned events are held at the complex from January to August. Outside of that time-frame, whether youll find something going on is hit-or-miss.  If there is something happening, its probably a high school game with just a handful of spectators.  Admission to the complex counts as one of your "Fun Visits" if youve added the Water Park Fun More option to your  Magic Your Way tickets , however, considering the low cost of admission it could be said that its better to save your "Fun Visits" for one of the more expensive options. Admission is $15.50 for adults and $10.50 for children ages 3ndash;9.</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">63674</field>
		<field name="title">Walt Disney World/Magic Kingdom</field>
		<field name="main">see and do</field>
		<field name="name">main street, u.s.a.</field>
		<field name="content">Modeled after a stereotypical early 20th-century small town, Main Street, U.S.A. is the gateway into the Magic Kingdom; the view straight down the street to Cinderella Castle serves to draw you inward upon arrival. It is also, of course, the exit, which means shopping galore, the better to entice you with souvenirs on the way out. Youll find most of the basic services, like Guest Relations, here, but not much in the way of attractions.  Do stop in at the Crystal Arts glass shop, though, as they often have glass blowers working in the shop and watching them is fascinating. And keep an eye out for some of the colorful characters who make appearances from time to time, especially the Dapper Dans barbershop quartet.</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">63675</field>
		<field name="title">Walt Disney World/Magic Kingdom</field>
		<field name="main">see and do</field>
		<field name="section">main street, u.s.a.</field>
		<field name="name">Sorcerers of the Magic Kingdom</field>
		<field name="content">Merlin needs help saving the shards of his crystal ball from the forces of evil! Kids and adults alike can battle up to twenty Disney Villains in this interactive park-wide adventure game. With seventy "spells" to collect, eight different adventures, and adventure portals located throughout the Magic Kingdom, replay value is high.</field>
		<field name="directions">start at Main Street Fire Station</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">63676</field>
		<field name="title">Walt Disney World/Magic Kingdom</field>
		<field name="main">see and do</field>
		<field name="section">main street, u.s.a.</field>
		<field name="name">Harmony Barber Shop</field>
		<field name="content">This may not seem like much of an attraction, but for many guests an old-fashioned barber shop is indeed a novelty. Everything is done the way they did it a century agomdash;except the prices! The Harmony Barber Shop specializes in first haircuts; bring your never-shorn toddler in and the barbers will take extra-special care to make it an exciting and memorable experience.</field>
		<field name="price">Adult haircut $19, children 12 and under $15, first haircuts $18, beard trim $10</field>
		<field name="hours">Daily 9AM-5PM</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">63677</field>
		<field name="title">Walt Disney World/Magic Kingdom</field>
		<field name="main">see and do</field>
		<field name="section">main street, u.s.a.</field>
		<field name="name">Town Square Theater</field>
		<field name="content">Mickey is preparing to give a magic show at this old-time theater, but hes always up for greeting guests backstage. (Theres no actual magic show... just the meet-and-greet with Mickey.) The Disney Princesses also can be found nearby, as they wait for the Princess Fairytale Hall to open in 2013. Fastpasses are available and highly recommended.</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">63678</field>
		<field name="title">Walt Disney World/Magic Kingdom</field>
		<field name="main">see and do</field>
		<field name="section">main street, u.s.a.</field>
		<field name="name">Walt Disney World Railroad</field>
		<field name="content">A 19th-century steam train that circles the park, with stops at Frontierland and the Storybook Circus area of Fantasyland. Closing for refurbishment September 30 ndash; November 20, 2013.</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">63679</field>
		<field name="title">Walt Disney World/Magic Kingdom</field>
		<field name="main">see and do</field>
		<field name="section">main street, u.s.a.</field>
		<field name="name">Main Street Vehicles</field>
		<field name="content">Ride a horse car, omnibus, jitney, horseless carriage, or fire engine from the entrance to Cinderella Castle and back. Note that these vehicles only run if crowd levels permit.</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">63680</field>
		<field name="title">Walt Disney World/Magic Kingdom</field>
		<field name="main">see and do</field>
		<field name="section">adventureland</field>
		<field name="name">Pirates of the Caribbean</field>
		<field name="content">The classic swashbuckling adventure along the Spanish Main now features Captain Jack Sparrow from the blockbuster film series. A bit spooky at the beginning, but once the pillaging starts, things start to get silly.</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">63681</field>
		<field name="title">Walt Disney World/Magic Kingdom</field>
		<field name="main">see and do</field>
		<field name="section">adventureland</field>
		<field name="name">The Magic Carpets of Aladdin</field>
		<field name="content">Guide your carpet up and down as it spins around and around, but if you dont watch out for the spitting camels, youre going to get a little wet!</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">63682</field>
		<field name="title">Walt Disney World/Magic Kingdom</field>
		<field name="main">see and do</field>
		<field name="section">adventureland</field>
		<field name="name">Enchanted Tiki Room</field>
		<field name="content">The original Tropical Serenade show is back! A roomful of wise-cracking Audio-Animatronic birds serenade you with classic tunes. After years "Under New Management", a minor fire in early 2011 prompted the Imagineers to take the opportunity to restore the older show, which is nearly identical to the one Walt Disney created for Disneyland.</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">63683</field>
		<field name="title">Walt Disney World/Magic Kingdom</field>
		<field name="main">see and do</field>
		<field name="section">adventureland</field>
		<field name="name">Jungle Cruise</field>
		<field name="content">Tour the worlds jungle rivers, from the Amazon to the Nile to the Irawaddy. The cruises pilots are well-armed, both with pistols and with the worst puns mankind has ever known. View the back side of water, and visit "head" salesman Trader Sam, but please, no "hand outs" to the crocodiles! Closing for refurbishment August 19 ndash; September 30, 2013.</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">63684</field>
		<field name="title">Walt Disney World/Magic Kingdom</field>
		<field name="main">see and do</field>
		<field name="section">adventureland</field>
		<field name="name">Swiss Family Treehouse</field>
		<field name="content">Tour the shipwrecked Robinson familys ingenious home. Be warned: lots of stairs.</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">63685</field>
		<field name="title">Walt Disney World/Magic Kingdom</field>
		<field name="main">see and do</field>
		<field name="section">adventureland</field>
		<field name="name">A Pirates Adventure: Treasures of the Seven Seas</field>
		<field name="content">Would-be pirates can pick up a treasure map and help Captain Jack Sparrow find the Treasures of the Seven Seas. Its an interactive scavenger-hunt game that takes players of all ages across Adventureland to seek the treasures.</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">63686</field>
		<field name="title">Walt Disney World/Magic Kingdom</field>
		<field name="main">see and do</field>
		<field name="name">adventureland</field>
		<field name="content">Adventureland recalls the Victorian-era tales of exotic adventure in far-off locales. Near Main Street, the environment evokes the jungles of deepest  Africa , of the type explored by David Livingstone and H.M. Stanley in the late 19th century. Walking westward, youll pass through the  Middle East  and the  South Pacific  before arriving at the Spanish outposts on the  Caribbean Sea  during the Golden Age of Piracy. Just around the corner are the Spanish flavors of the  American Southwest  in Frontierland.  The Disney Fairies (Tinker Bell and her friends) have taken up residence in the Adventureland Veranda near the entrance to this land, where they greet guests and pose for pictures.</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">63687</field>
		<field name="title">Walt Disney World/Magic Kingdom</field>
		<field name="main">see and do</field>
		<field name="section">frontierland</field>
		<field name="name">Walt Disney World Railroad</field>
		<field name="content">A 19th-century steam train that circles the park, with stops at Main Street, U.S.A. and the Storybook Circus area of Fantasyland. Closing for refurbishment September 30 ndash; November 20, 2013.</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">63688</field>
		<field name="title">Walt Disney World/Magic Kingdom</field>
		<field name="main">see and do</field>
		<field name="name">frontierland</field>
		<field name="content">Frontierland celebrates the United States west of the Mississippi in its 19th-century frontier years (with just a bit of rural Southern flavor). From Mark Twains Missouri to the California Gold Rush, theres a lot of adventure packed into a small area.     15px         15px</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">63689</field>
		<field name="title">Walt Disney World/Magic Kingdom</field>
		<field name="main">see and do</field>
		<field name="section">frontierland</field>
		<field name="name">Tom Sawyer Island</field>
		<field name="content">Take a raft ride across the Rivers of America to a pair of heavily wooded islands perfect for imaginative and adventurous play. Winding paths, a spooky cavern, a barrel bridge, and even the rustic frontier Fort Langhorn are among the many places to explore. Go ahead and let the kids run around freely; the islands are completely isolated from the rest of the park.</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">63690</field>
		<field name="title">Walt Disney World/Magic Kingdom</field>
		<field name="main">see and do</field>
		<field name="section">frontierland</field>
		<field name="name">Frontierland Shootin Arcade</field>
		<field name="content">Grab a rifle and pretend youre in a shootout at the O.K. Corral. The animated targets react only to the special infrared rifles, so theres no safety concern for little ones.</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">63691</field>
		<field name="title">Walt Disney World/Magic Kingdom</field>
		<field name="main">see and do</field>
		<field name="section">frontierland</field>
		<field name="name">Big Thunder Mountain Railroad</field>
		<field name="content">A roller coaster with a runaway mine train theme. No inversions, but the hairpin turns, fast hills, and frequent tunnels make for an exciting ride.</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">63692</field>
		<field name="title">Walt Disney World/Magic Kingdom</field>
		<field name="main">see and do</field>
		<field name="section">frontierland</field>
		<field name="name">Splash Mountain</field>
		<field name="content">A log flume ride based on Song of the South, with a thrilling 50-foot drop into the briar patch! You will get wet, and you may get soaked; one way to avoid that fate is to buy a rain poncho at a gift shop and wear it onto the ride. Closed for refurbishment January 6 ndash; March 22, 2014.</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">63693</field>
		<field name="title">Walt Disney World/Magic Kingdom</field>
		<field name="main">see and do</field>
		<field name="section">frontierland</field>
		<field name="name">Country Bear Jamboree</field>
		<field name="content">Live stage show with country music-singing Audio-Animatronic bears. Best enjoyed with lots of hand-clapping and foot-stomping from the audience.</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">63694</field>
		<field name="title">Walt Disney World/Magic Kingdom</field>
		<field name="main">see and do</field>
		<field name="name">liberty square</field>
		<field name="content">The Liberty Square Riverboat sets off for another voyage.   Step back into colonial America in Liberty Square, where freedom and independence are buzzwords and powdered wigs are the height of fashion. Even the flower beds are red, white, and blue in this patriotic harbor town. A replica of the Liberty Bell sits in the central square, along with a majestic live oak serving as the local Liberty Tree, where patriots would gather to debate and plan.</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">63695</field>
		<field name="title">Walt Disney World/Magic Kingdom</field>
		<field name="main">see and do</field>
		<field name="section">liberty square</field>
		<field name="name">Haunted Mansion</field>
		<field name="content">A stately Dutch Gothic mansion sits on a hill to the north of Liberty Square, representing the Hudson River estates of the 19th century. Observant visitors will, however, note some decidedly eerie sounds coming from the mansion; those who venture inside will find themselves immersed in a creepy but occasionally wacky house of horrors. A mostly ride-through attraction featuring 999 happy haunts (which means theres room for one moremdash;did you bring your death certificate?) and the only Disney cast members who never smile. The latest round of renovations in 2008 have done wonders in updating the innovative special effects. In 2012, interactive games were added to the entrance queue. You can choose to go straight in to the ride or take a different path and play the games first.</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">63696</field>
		<field name="title">Walt Disney World/Magic Kingdom</field>
		<field name="main">see and do</field>
		<field name="section">liberty square</field>
		<field name="name">Liberty Square Riverboat</field>
		<field name="content">Ride a steam-powered stern-wheeler down the Rivers of America, all the way around Tom Sawyer Island. Gives you some unique views of attractions like the Haunted Mansion and Big Thunder Mountain that you cant otherwise see, and there are also some dioramas scattered around that are only viewable from the riverboat.</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">63697</field>
		<field name="title">Walt Disney World/Magic Kingdom</field>
		<field name="main">see and do</field>
		<field name="section">liberty square</field>
		<field name="name">Hall of Presidents</field>
		<field name="content">This attraction starts with an inspirational ultra-widescreen film on the history of the U.S. presidency. At the climax, the screen rises to reveal all 43 presidents on the stage, presented in lifelike Audio-Animatronics. Washington, Lincoln, and Obama give brief speeches.</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">63698</field>
		<field name="title">Walt Disney World/Magic Kingdom</field>
		<field name="main">see and do</field>
		<field name="section">fantasyland</field>
		<field name="sub-section">castle courtyard</field>
		<field name="name">Princess Fairytale Hall</field>
		<field name="content">Snow Whites Scary Adventures, an opening-day attraction, is gone, but Snow White herself and many of her Disney Princess friends have gathered at the Fairytale Hall to meet their young fans.</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">63699</field>
		<field name="title">Walt Disney World/Magic Kingdom</field>
		<field name="main">see and do</field>
		<field name="section">fantasyland</field>
		<field name="sub-section">castle courtyard</field>
		<field name="name">Prince Charming Regal Carrousel</field>
		<field name="content">This carousel was built in 1917, making it the oldest ride in the park. Found dilapidated and no longer operational in 1967 in  Maplewood, New Jersey , it has been meticulously restored to its splendor. Non-riders can play a bit of name-that-tune as they listen to the creative band-organ arrangements of classic Disney music.</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">63700</field>
		<field name="title">Walt Disney World/Magic Kingdom</field>
		<field name="main">see and do</field>
		<field name="section">fantasyland</field>
		<field name="sub-section">castle courtyard</field>
		<field name="name">Mad Tea Party</field>
		<field name="content">The Mad Hatter and the March Hare invite you for a spin in a giant teacup. You can spin your teacup around its center axis at whatever speed you like, but thats not the only thing thatll be moving; each group of five cups also spins around a common axis, and then the whole shebang rotates around a giant teapot. Riders with plenty of arm strength can get their teacup spinning to ridiculous speeds; know your limits!</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">63701</field>
		<field name="title">Walt Disney World/Magic Kingdom</field>
		<field name="main">see and do</field>
		<field name="section">fantasyland</field>
		<field name="sub-section">castle courtyard</field>
		<field name="name">its a small world</field>
		<field name="content">Set sail on the happiest cruise around the world, to be serenaded by stylized Audio-Animatronics of children from every continent. This was originally Pepsi and Bank of Americas pavilion at the 1964 New York Worlds Fair. The cheerful theme song is known all over the world, both for its message of unity and peace as well as for its relentlessly catchy tune. Closing for refurbishment December 1ndash;8, 2013.</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">63702</field>
		<field name="title">Walt Disney World/Magic Kingdom</field>
		<field name="main">see and do</field>
		<field name="section">fantasyland</field>
		<field name="sub-section">castle courtyard</field>
		<field name="name">Mickeys PhilharMagic</field>
		<field name="content">A computer-animated 3D movie. You think youre in for a magical concert conducted by Mickey Mouse, but Donald Duck swipes Mickeys sorcerer hat, and things go hilariously awry. The audience follows Donald into iconic scenes from Fantasia, The Little Mermaid, Aladdin, and more.</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">63703</field>
		<field name="title">Walt Disney World/Magic Kingdom</field>
		<field name="main">see and do</field>
		<field name="section">fantasyland</field>
		<field name="name">castle courtyard</field>
		<field name="content">Cinderella Castle  This area of Fantasyland, closest to the castle, has most of the pre-2012 Fantasyland rides and has remained fairly unchanged during the lands expansion. From rides based on classic Disney animated features to the inimitable "its a small world" boat ride, the attractions here are among Disneys most beloved and iconic.  For the time being, FastPasses for Princess Fairytale Hall must be obtained at Peter Pans Flight.</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">63704</field>
		<field name="title">Walt Disney World/Magic Kingdom</field>
		<field name="main">see and do</field>
		<field name="section">fantasyland</field>
		<field name="sub-section">castle courtyard</field>
		<field name="name">Peter Pans Flight</field>
		<field name="content">Experience the story of Peter Pan from your own flying pirate ship. Soar over the rooftops of London, and on to Neverland. Hit this attraction early, as the line can get very long. Closing for refurbishment September 30 ndash; November 13, 2013.</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">63705</field>
		<field name="title">Walt Disney World/Magic Kingdom</field>
		<field name="main">see and do</field>
		<field name="section">fantasyland</field>
		<field name="sub-section">enchanted forest</field>
		<field name="name">Under the Sea - Voyage of the Little Mermaid</field>
		<field name="content">In the classic Disney dark-ride style, guests revisit the story of the 1989 film that ushered in the Silver Age of Disney animated films. Ariels Grotto, just outside, lets guests meet and take pictures with the mermaid herself.</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">63706</field>
		<field name="title">Walt Disney World/Magic Kingdom</field>
		<field name="main">see and do</field>
		<field name="section">fantasyland</field>
		<field name="name">enchanted forest</field>
		<field name="content">Unused and underused space in the northeastern part of the landmdash;some of which was once the 20,000 Leagues Under the Sea ridemdash;is being transformed into a lush fairy-tale setting that stands in stark contrast to the fair-like atmosphere of the Castle Courtyard. Beauty and the Beast and The Little Mermaid are the focus of the first new attractions to open, and the existing Winnie The Pooh ride is being incorporated into the area as well. A new Snow White and the Seven Dwarfs mine-cart roller coaster will provide some thrills starting in 2014. All in all, the Enchanted Forest represents the biggest addition to Walt Disney World since Disneys Animal Kingdom opened in 1998.  Note that if you want FastPasses for Winnie the Pooh or Under the Sea, you must get them outside Mickeys PhilharMagic for the time being.</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">63707</field>
		<field name="title">Walt Disney World/Magic Kingdom</field>
		<field name="main">see and do</field>
		<field name="section">fantasyland</field>
		<field name="sub-section">enchanted forest</field>
		<field name="name">The Many Adventures of Winnie the Pooh</field>
		<field name="content">Follow Pooh and his friends on an adventure through the Hundred Acre Wood. Might be the most popular ride in the park, at least for the under-5 set.</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">63708</field>
		<field name="title">Walt Disney World/Magic Kingdom</field>
		<field name="main">see and do</field>
		<field name="section">fantasyland</field>
		<field name="sub-section">enchanted forest</field>
		<field name="name">Enchanted Tales with Belle</field>
		<field name="content">Guests walk through the cottage where Belles father lives, making use of a magic mirror to enter the Beasts castle. There, Lumiere and the Wardrobe have arranged a surprise for Belle, and all the guests—kids and adults alike—are welcome to participate in the story. This experience is much more than just the typical autograph and photo session.</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">63709</field>
		<field name="title">Walt Disney World/Magic Kingdom</field>
		<field name="main">see and do</field>
		<field name="section">fantasyland</field>
		<field name="sub-section">storybook circus</field>
		<field name="name">Casey Jr. Splash N Soak Station</field>
		<field name="content">Kids can play and splash around the circus train from Dumbo. They will get very wet, and you probably will too, even if you just sit around the perimeter. Consider bringing a change of clothes.</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">63710</field>
		<field name="title">Walt Disney World/Magic Kingdom</field>
		<field name="main">see and do</field>
		<field name="section">fantasyland</field>
		<field name="sub-section">storybook circus</field>
		<field name="name">Dumbo the Flying Elephant</field>
		<field name="content">Dumbo spreads his giant ears and flies around and around, and you can make him go up and down as you spin. This classic attraction has been the very first "thrill ride" for countless kids over the years. Now, with two carousels and an indoor "virtual" queuing area with activities and games, the days of insufferable waits for Dumbo are over. (Note that guests with FastPasses will bypass the activities inside the big tent.)</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">63711</field>
		<field name="title">Walt Disney World/Magic Kingdom</field>
		<field name="main">see and do</field>
		<field name="section">fantasyland</field>
		<field name="sub-section">storybook circus</field>
		<field name="name">Petes Silly Sideshow</field>
		<field name="content">Mickeys pals have all been working hard at the Storybook Circus, and you can meet them here, in their circus personae: "Minnie Magnifique", "Daisy Fortuna", "The Great Goofini", and "The Amazing Donaldo". (Mickey himself still holds court down at the Town Square Theater.)</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">63712</field>
		<field name="title">Walt Disney World/Magic Kingdom</field>
		<field name="main">see and do</field>
		<field name="section">fantasyland</field>
		<field name="sub-section">storybook circus</field>
		<field name="name">The Barnstormer Featuring the Great Goofini</field>
		<field name="content">A childrens roller coaster. Perfect alternative for those too short to ride Space Mountain or Big Thunder Mountain Railroad.</field>
		<field name="alt">formerly The Barnstormer at Goofys Wiseacres Farm</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">63713</field>
		<field name="title">Walt Disney World/Magic Kingdom</field>
		<field name="main">see and do</field>
		<field name="section">fantasyland</field>
		<field name="name">storybook circus</field>
		<field name="content">In 1988, for Mickey Mouses 60th birthday, he and his pals opened up Mickeys Birthdayland, so all their fans could come celebrate with them. Originally meant to be temporary, the idea was such a hit that they kept the place open long after the birthday party ended. The land that became known as Mickeys Toontown Fair closed forever in February 2011, and was subsequently replaced by this new mini-land, which opened in March 2012 as the first phase of the ambitious Fantasyland expansion effort.</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">63714</field>
		<field name="title">Walt Disney World/Magic Kingdom</field>
		<field name="main">see and do</field>
		<field name="section">fantasyland</field>
		<field name="sub-section">storybook circus</field>
		<field name="name">Walt Disney World Railroad</field>
		<field name="content">A 19th-century steam train that circles the park, with stops at Main Street, U.S.A. and Frontierland. Closing for refurbishment September 30 ndash; November 20, 2013.</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">63715</field>
		<field name="title">Walt Disney World/Magic Kingdom</field>
		<field name="main">see and do</field>
		<field name="name">fantasyland</field>
		<field name="content">In the courtyard, around the forest, or at the circus, Fantasyland is where Disneys classic animated fairy tales come to life. It is home to many of the most iconic Disney attractions, and is nearly always very crowded. In 2012, Fantasyland underwent an extreme makeover, the biggest changes to hit the Magic Kingdom in its 40-year history. The land is now divided into three distinct sections: the Castle Courtyard, Enchanted Forest, and Storybook Circus.</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">63716</field>
		<field name="title">Walt Disney World/Magic Kingdom</field>
		<field name="main">see and do</field>
		<field name="section">tomorrowland</field>
		<field name="name">Stitchs Great Escape!</field>
		<field name="content">The little genetically engineered terror, Experiment 626, is on the rampage, and youre locked into your seat and at his mercy. This attraction gets very mixed reviews; adults often find the effects trite and the storyline boring, while young kids could very well be scared out of their wits. And very few people enjoy smelling Stichs chili-dog breath. Try it if you want, but know what youre getting into, especially if you have kids.</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">63717</field>
		<field name="title">Walt Disney World/Magic Kingdom</field>
		<field name="main">see and do</field>
		<field name="section">tomorrowland</field>
		<field name="name">Space Mountain</field>
		<field name="content">The classic rocket-themed indoor roller coaster. Its quite dark, which enhances the thrill because you dont know whats coming next. (And those whove been on it with the lights on will assure you that you probably dont want to see how close you get to the structure above you!) Closing for refurbishment September 3ndash;5, 10ndash;12, and 23ndash;26, 2013.</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">63718</field>
		<field name="title">Walt Disney World/Magic Kingdom</field>
		<field name="main">see and do</field>
		<field name="section">tomorrowland</field>
		<field name="name">Carousel of Progress</field>
		<field name="content">A four-part Audio-Animatronic production taking you through a century of technological progress. Housed in a unique rotating show building. This show originally debuted as General Electrics pavilion at the 1964 New York Worlds Fair and holds the record of being the longest-running stage show in history. Its a bit dated, but it was one of Walt Disneys favorites and very much embodies his approach to human progress.</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">63719</field>
		<field name="title">Walt Disney World/Magic Kingdom</field>
		<field name="main">see and do</field>
		<field name="section">tomorrowland</field>
		<field name="name">Tomorrowland Transit Authority PeopleMover</field>
		<field name="content">Take a round-trip sightseeing tour on an elevated track around all of Tomorrowland. The nearly silent PeopleMover vehicles are an innovative prototype for an efficient and comfortable transport system. The ride goes inside several of the show buildings, giving you behind-the-scenes peeks at both Space Mountain and Buzz Lightyear.</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">63720</field>
		<field name="title">Walt Disney World/Magic Kingdom</field>
		<field name="main">see and do</field>
		<field name="name">tomorrowland</field>
		<field name="content">The futuristic spires of Space Mountain   Take a glance into the future in Tomorrowland, Disneys homage to the dreams and innovations that will keep humanity moving forward. Very different from the other lands of the Magic Kingdom, Tomorrowland is all about smooth chrome architecture, strange and bizarre creatures, and thrilling spaceflight.             15px       15px</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">63721</field>
		<field name="title">Walt Disney World/Magic Kingdom</field>
		<field name="main">see and do</field>
		<field name="section">tomorrowland</field>
		<field name="name">Tomorrowland Speedway</field>
		<field name="content">You dont need a drivers license to drive these real gas-powered cars; you just need to be able to reach the gas pedal. Drive around a 0.4-mile (640 m) racetrack (safely secured to a guiderail) and try not to bump into the car in front of you.</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">63722</field>
		<field name="title">Walt Disney World/Magic Kingdom</field>
		<field name="main">see and do</field>
		<field name="section">tomorrowland</field>
		<field name="name">AstroOrbiter</field>
		<field name="content">Climb into a rocketship and control your altitude as you spin around a central pillar. Quite similar to Dumbo the Flying Elephant in Fantasyland, but the AstroOrbiter is positioned much higher, allowing for some very nice views. It can be a great way to watch the nightly fireworks, if you can time it right.</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">63723</field>
		<field name="title">Walt Disney World/Magic Kingdom</field>
		<field name="main">see and do</field>
		<field name="section">tomorrowland</field>
		<field name="name">Buzz Lightyears Space Ranger Spin</field>
		<field name="content">An indoor dark ride with a laser gun game. Help Buzz Lightyear beat the evil Emperor Zurg by firing your laser at targets scattered throughout the ride. Some targets are worth more than others, but you wont know which are which! Youll want to ride multiple times to try to beat your scores.</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">63724</field>
		<field name="title">Walt Disney World/Magic Kingdom</field>
		<field name="main">see and do</field>
		<field name="section">tomorrowland</field>
		<field name="name">Monsters, Inc. Laugh Floor</field>
		<field name="content">Interactive comedy show featuring characters from Monsters, Inc. The animated monsters on the screen will pick on specific audience members and even call them by name. Audience members can also submit jokes via cell phone for the monsters to tell!</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">63725</field>
		<field name="title">Walt Disney World/Magic Kingdom</field>
		<field name="main">see and do</field>
		<field name="section">parkwide</field>
		<field name="name">holiday events</field>
		<field name="content">In recent years, the Magic Kingdom has been host to two extremely popular "hard-ticket" holiday events. On selected days from September through December, the park closes early, but guests who pay extra get to stick around and see special shows and go on rides with shorter lines. These events are held three or four nights a week (although the exact schedule varies). Tickets are very limited, so plan well in advance for the night you want to go.  Not all attractions are open during these special events, but most of the most popular ones will be.       Note that after the last Christmas Party, about a week before Christmas, the holiday parade and fireworks show are run in place of the usual events, allowing guests to experience them without buying a ticket to a special event. Alternatively, you can listen to and watch the fireworks shows from the Contemporary, the Polynesian, or the Grand Floridian resorts without needing admission to the parties.</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">63726</field>
		<field name="title">Walt Disney World/Magic Kingdom</field>
		<field name="main">see and do</field>
		<field name="section">parkwide</field>
		<field name="sub-section">holiday events</field>
		<field name="name">Mickeys Very Merry Christmas Party</field>
		<field name="content">A five-hour party with two special Christmas parades, the Holiday Wishes fireworks show, complimentary hot cocoa, and snow falling on Main Street U.S.A.</field>
		<field name="price">Advance purchase: adults $54, ages 3-9 $48; $6 more day-of</field>
		<field name="hours">early Nov - mid-Dec; 7PM-midnight</field>
		<field name="url">http://disneyworld.disney.go.com/parks/magic-kingdom/special-events/mickeys-very-merry-christmas-party/</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">63727</field>
		<field name="title">Walt Disney World/Magic Kingdom</field>
		<field name="main">see and do</field>
		<field name="section">parkwide</field>
		<field name="sub-section">holiday events</field>
		<field name="name">Mickeys Not-So-Scary Halloween Party</field>
		<field name="content">A five-hour party with two special Halloween parades, the Happy HalloWishes fireworks show, costumed characters wearing costumes of their own, and trick-or-treating throughout the park. Feel free to wear your own costumes, too!</field>
		<field name="price">Advance purchase: adults $54, ages 3-9 $48; $6 more day-of</field>
		<field name="hours">mid-Sep - Nov 1; 7PM-midnight</field>
		<field name="url">http://disneyworld.disney.go.com/parks/magic-kingdom/special-events/mickeys-not-so-scary-halloween-party/</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">63728</field>
		<field name="title">Walt Disney World/Magic Kingdom</field>
		<field name="main">see and do</field>
		<field name="section">parkwide</field>
		<field name="sub-section">tours</field>
		<field name="name">Family Magic Tour</field>
		<field name="content">If youve got kids, they cant go on the Keys to the Kingdom tour (and for good reason); this, then, is your next-best alternative. The two-hour tour works like a scavenger hunt, looking for themed clues in each of the Magic Kingdoms lands. Ends with a visit from a Disney character.</field>
		<field name="price">$27</field>
		<field name="hours">daily 10AM</field>
		<field name="url">http://disneyworld.disney.go.com/tours-and-experiences/disneys-family-magic/</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">63729</field>
		<field name="title">Walt Disney World/Magic Kingdom</field>
		<field name="main">see and do</field>
		<field name="section">parkwide</field>
		<field name="sub-section">tours</field>
		<field name="name">The Magic Behind Our Steam Trains</field>
		<field name="content">Walt Disney was a big fan of steam trains, and this tour lets you get an up-close view of the real trains in operation at the Magic Kingdom. You can also go behind the scenes to the roundhouse and maintenance facilities, while learning about the history behind each of the locomotives. Three hours. Must be 10 or older.</field>
		<field name="price">$49</field>
		<field name="hours">M Tu Th-Sa 7:30AM</field>
		<field name="url">http://disneyworld.disney.go.com/tours-and-experiences/steam-trains-tour/</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">63730</field>
		<field name="title">Walt Disney World/Magic Kingdom</field>
		<field name="main">see and do</field>
		<field name="section">parkwide</field>
		<field name="name">tours</field>
		<field name="content">Guided tours of the Magic Kingdom are quite popular. All tours can be booked by calling +1 407 WDW-TOUR (939-8687). You will need to have admission to the park to take these tours.</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">63731</field>
		<field name="title">Walt Disney World/Magic Kingdom</field>
		<field name="main">see and do</field>
		<field name="section">parkwide</field>
		<field name="sub-section">tours</field>
		<field name="name">Keys to the Kingdom</field>
		<field name="content">This is the ultimate Disney tour, which goes over, under, and behind the scenes to illustrate Disney history, show you tricks of the trade, and reveal "secrets" of Disney operations. Includes a trip through the Utilidors and other backstage areas. Be warned, though: if this is your first visit to the Magic Kingdom, do not take this tour. Spend at least two days just enjoying yourself and experiencing the Magic. The tour will forever change the way that you look at the Magic Kingdom, like pulling apart a flower to see how it grows: you end up knowing more, but in your mind you will never look at a flower the same way. 4.5ndash;5 hours, including a break for lunch at the Columbia Harbour House (order at beginning of tour). Must be 16 or older.</field>
		<field name="price">$70</field>
		<field name="hours">daily 8:30AM, 9AM, 9:30AM</field>
		<field name="url">http://disneyworld.disney.go.com/tours-and-experiences/keys-to-the-kingdom/</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">63732</field>
		<field name="title">Walt Disney World/Magic Kingdom</field>
		<field name="main">see and do</field>
		<field name="name">parkwide</field>
		<field name="content">"Wishes" fireworks show   The parades and shows at all of the parks garner big crowds, but the Magic Kingdom really takes the cake, perhaps due to its relatively narrow streets and the sheer popularity of the park. Unless the park is practically deserted, youll need to stake out a viewing location well in advance of show time (check your Times Guide for the schedule). If you want to sit on the curb or grab a bench seat, youll want to get there at least an hour ahead of time; if youre willing to deal with a lesser view, you may get lucky and find a decent spot as little as 15 minutes beforehand. (If youre running late for a parade, aim for the end of the route, as the parade takes up to 20 minutes to get there.)  Most importantly, though, if you arent planning on watching the parade or the show, stay well away from the prime viewing locations. The rides and other attractions will have much shorter lines during these times, so pick a few well away from Main Street and enjoy.  The parades start in the entrance plaza and travel up Main Street, then through the hub to Liberty Square and west through Frontierland, ending near Splash Mountain. Fireworks are visible throughout the park, but they work best with Cinderella Castle as a backdrop, so most people view them from Main Street on their way out of the park for the night.            Theres also a special annual parkwide event:</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">63733</field>
		<field name="title">Walt Disney World/Magic Kingdom</field>
		<field name="main">see and do</field>
		<field name="section">parkwide</field>
		<field name="name">Main Street Electrical Parade</field>
		<field name="content">The classic nighttime parade that ran for many years here made an exciting return in Summer 2010, and Disney has not yet decided when its special engagement will end and SpectroMagic will return. Until that time arrives, enjoy this blast from the past, with thousands of colorful lights and the unforgettable "Baroque Hoedown" soundtrack!</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">63734</field>
		<field name="title">Walt Disney World/Magic Kingdom</field>
		<field name="main">see and do</field>
		<field name="section">parkwide</field>
		<field name="name">Celebrate a Dream Come True Parade</field>
		<field name="content">Daytime parade of classic Disney moments.</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">63735</field>
		<field name="title">Walt Disney World/Magic Kingdom</field>
		<field name="main">see and do</field>
		<field name="section">parkwide</field>
		<field name="name">Celebrate the Magic</field>
		<field name="content">Each night before the fireworks, enjoy a 10-minute show in which Cinderella Castle undergoes a series of spectacular transformations, with the details changing seasonally. See the castle become a Scottish fortress right before your eyes, or watch as Wreck-It Ralph knocks the bricks right out of the walls.</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">63736</field>
		<field name="title">Walt Disney World/Magic Kingdom</field>
		<field name="main">see and do</field>
		<field name="section">parkwide</field>
		<field name="name">Wishes: A Magical Gathering of Disney Dreams</field>
		<field name="content">At park closing there is a fireworks show to send everyone home with a great memory. The best viewing areas generate very crowded conditions, not surprisingly. If you really want to avoid the crowds, try watching the fireworks from one of the Magic Kingdom resorts; the shows audio is piped into speakers in some of the prime viewing locations.</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">63737</field>
		<field name="title">Walt Disney World/Magic Kingdom</field>
		<field name="main">see and do</field>
		<field name="section">parkwide</field>
		<field name="name">Night of Joy</field>
		<field name="content">A Christian music festival, with contemporary Christian bands and soloists performing on stages throughout the park. This is a hard-ticket event, meaning the park closes at 7PM, with only Night of Joy ticket holders allowed to stay in the park. Several of the parks attractions will be open after 7PM, but not all of them; the main attraction is supposed to be the music.</field>
		<field name="price">$53 per night ($63 at the door), or $95 for both nights</field>
		<field name="hours">6-7 Sep 2013; 4PM-1AM</field>
		<field name="url">http://disneyworld.disney.go.com/parks/magic-kingdom/special-events/night-of-joy/</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">63738</field>
		<field name="title">Walt Disney World/Magic Kingdom</field>
		<field name="main">see and do</field>
		<field name="section">at the resorts</field>
		<field name="name">Francks Bridal Studio</field>
		<field name="content">Oh yes. You can get married at Walt Disney World. If youre willing to spend enough, you can get married just about anywhere in the resort, and add any number of special Disney touches. Francks Bridal Studio is where you can plan it all out, and its right next to Disneys Wedding Pavilion, a 300-seat non-denominational chapel on the shores of Seven Seas Lagoon.</field>
		<field name="directions">between Grand Floridian Polynesian</field>
		<field name="phone">+1 321 939-4610</field>
		<field name="price">$4,500+</field>
		<field name="url">http://disneyweddings.disney.go.com</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">63739</field>
		<field name="title">Walt Disney World/Magic Kingdom</field>
		<field name="main">see and do</field>
		<field name="name">at the resorts</field>
		<field name="content">Lounge on the beach by the Grand Floridian.   Like all Deluxe Resorts, the ones near the Magic Kingdom offer plenty of things for guests to do each day. But a few options stand out as worth a trip even if youre not staying nearby.         There are also smaller boats like Sea Raycers and pontoon boats available at the Contemporary Resorts marina. Some of the other resorts also have small marinas. $20+.        15px</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">63740</field>
		<field name="title">Walt Disney World/Magic Kingdom</field>
		<field name="main">see and do</field>
		<field name="section">at the resorts</field>
		<field name="name">Wilderness Back Trail Adventure</field>
		<field name="content">This is a fantastic opportunity to try out a Segway Personal Transporter, and to explore the wilds around the campground. The tour starts at the Bike Barn with an hour of training on how to use the Segway, but then the fun begins. Your guides will take you out for an hour-long tour around the campground, where you can see the stables, scenery, and lots of wildlife. The guides are experts and very good teachers. Great fun. Must be 16 or older and weigh between 100 and 250 pounds (45ndash;115nbsp;kg).</field>
		<field name="directions">at Fort Wilderness</field>
		<field name="price">$85</field>
		<field name="hours">Tu-Sa 8:30AM, 11:30AM</field>
		<field name="alt">Segway tour</field>
		<field name="url">http://disneyworld.disney.go.com/recreation/wilderness-back-trail-adventure/</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">63741</field>
		<field name="title">Walt Disney World/Magic Kingdom</field>
		<field name="main">see and do</field>
		<field name="section">at the resorts</field>
		<field name="name">Senses – A Disney Spa</field>
		<field name="content">The Grand Floridians spa has an enormous array of indulgent ways to relax, from kid-friendly facials to multi-hour full-body experiences, including just about any type of massage or manicure you can imagine. Of special note are the Grand Romantic Couples Massage and the Couples Instructional Massage. Treatments last 25, 50, or 80 minutes. Ages 12+ for full treatments; ages 4-12 for kids treatments; ages 14+ for fitness center. Children under 18 must be accompanied by an adult.</field>
		<field name="directions">at the Grand Floridian</field>
		<field name="phone">+1 407-WDW-SPAS (939-7727)</field>
		<field name="price">$25-$500</field>
		<field name="address">4111 N Floridian Way</field>
		<field name="hours">Treatments: daily 8AM-8PM; fitness center: daily 6AM-9PM</field>
		<field name="url">http://disneyworld.disney.go.com/spa/senses-spa-grand-floridian-resort/</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">63742</field>
		<field name="title">Walt Disney World/Magic Kingdom</field>
		<field name="main">see and do</field>
		<field name="section">at the resorts</field>
		<field name="name">Electrical Water Pageant</field>
		<field name="content">Dating back over forty years to Walt Disney Worlds opening month, the Electrical Water Pageant remains a little-known treat for guests staying in Magic Kingdom-area resorts. The Pageant involves a convoy of barges that make stops on the water in front of each of the resorts, performing a 10-minute light-and-music show that ends with a red-white-and-blue tribute to the United States. Ask at the front desk what time the Pageant will be visible from your guest room.</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">63743</field>
		<field name="title">Walt Disney World/Magic Kingdom</field>
		<field name="main">see and do</field>
		<field name="section">at the resorts</field>
		<field name="name">Tri-Circle-D Ranch</field>
		<field name="content">This is where the horses who work at the Magic Kingdom stay in their off-hours, and its open to the public! They have their own blacksmith shop, where you might see a blacksmith working, or you can visit the free petting zoo. Pony rides are $2.00. Guided horseback rides are available, too, but they start at the Livery near the campgrounds main entrance; for reservations, call +1 407 824-2832 up to 30 days in advance.</field>
		<field name="directions">at Fort Wilderness, near Pioneer Hall</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">63744</field>
		<field name="title">Walt Disney World/Magic Kingdom</field>
		<field name="main">see and do</field>
		<field name="section">at the resorts</field>
		<field name="name">Sammy Duvalls Watersports</field>
		<field name="content">You can rent personal watercraft here, and go tooling around Bay Lake, or you can get a bit more adventurous. Try waterskiing or wakeboarding ($165/hour), or go for the highest "ride" at Walt Disney World: parasailing ($95–$130 single, $170–$195 tandem)! The parasailing in particular is highly recommended; takeoff and landing are smooth as silk thanks to the special platform on the boat, and the line lets you sail 450ndash;600 feet above Bay Lake, showing you views you simply cant get anywhere else on-property.</field>
		<field name="directions">at the Contemporary</field>
		<field name="phone">+1 407 939-0754</field>
		<field name="price">$80+</field>
		<field name="fax">+1 407 939-0756</field>
		<field name="url">http://www.sammyduvall.com</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">63745</field>
		<field name="title">Walt Disney World/Magic Kingdom</field>
		<field name="main">see and do</field>
		<field name="section">golf</field>
		<field name="name">Palm Golf Course</field>
		<field name="content">Palm is Magnolias twin in many respects, although slightly less difficult and slightly shorter. Reportedly, water hazards are the primary obstacle on this course. Watch out in particular for the 18th hole; its a doozy. Closed through November 2013 for refurbishment.</field>
		<field name="url">http://disneyworld.disney.go.com/golf/palm-golf-course/</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">63746</field>
		<field name="title">Walt Disney World/Magic Kingdom</field>
		<field name="main">see and do</field>
		<field name="section">golf</field>
		<field name="name">Magnolia Golf Course</field>
		<field name="content">This aptly-named course set among the magnolia trees features a Mickey-shaped bunker on the sixth hole. Speaking of bunkers, this course has a ton of them, including fourteen on the fourth hole alone. Its the longest and probably the most difficult of the four Walt Disney World courses.</field>
		<field name="url">http://disneyworld.disney.go.com/golf/magnolia-golf-course/</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">63747</field>
		<field name="title">Walt Disney World/Magic Kingdom</field>
		<field name="main">see and do</field>
		<field name="name">golf</field>
		<field name="content">There are two 18-hole championship golf courses in the Magic Kingdom area, as well as a nine-hole walking course. All three courses are located in the same area, west of the Polynesian near Shades of Green. See " Golf " in the overview for rules and regulations. Monday through Friday, 18 holes will cost $89 if youre staying at a Disney hotel, and $104 otherwise. On weekends, add $10. During the summer, 10AM-3PM tee times are discounted; ask for the "Summer Price Slice" when you call. Late afternoon tee times are $59 on weekdays and $69 on weekends for everyone. Call +1 407 WDW-GOLF (939-4653) to reserve a tee time.</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">63748</field>
		<field name="title">Walt Disney World/Magic Kingdom</field>
		<field name="main">see and do</field>
		<field name="section">golf</field>
		<field name="name">Oak Trail Golf Course</field>
		<field name="content">This course is a nine-hole walking course (at the 18-hole courses, carts are not just allowed, but required). Its perfect for families, or for duffers looking for a quick nine holes. One round of golf also counts as one of your "Fun Visits" if youve added the Water Park Fun More option to your  Magic Your Way tickets .</field>
		<field name="price">Adults $38; under 18 $20</field>
		<field name="url">http://disneyworld.disney.go.com/golf/oak-trail-golf-course/</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">63749</field>
		<field name="title">Walt Disney World/Magic Kingdom</field>
		<field name="main">see and do</field>
		<field name="section">walt disney world speedway</field>
		<field name="name">Richard Petty Driving Experience</field>
		<field name="content">Long before he voiced "The King" in Disney/Pixars Cars, Richard Petty lent his name to the NASCAR driving experience at the WDW Speedway. Youve got several choices here, depending on your thrill tolerance and the size of your wallet. The Ride-Along Program puts you in the passenger seat for three qualifying-type laps at 150nbsp;MPH (240nbsp;km/h). The Rookie Experience lets you do the driving for eight laps in a real NASCAR-style car with 600 horses under the hood. The King Experience starts off the same but adds another 10 laps, at a higher speed. And if you really love racingmdash;or think you willmdash;try the Experience of a Lifetime, a full half-day session featuring three sets of ten laps each, with detailed one-on-one training and advice in between each set. Must be 16 or older for the Ride-Along Program; must be 18 (with a valid drivers license) for the others.</field>
		<field name="phone">+1-800-BE-PETTY</field>
		<field name="price">$99 (ride-along); $449-$2099 (driving); teens ages 14-19 can accompany an adult for free</field>
		<field name="hours">Daily (except Easter, Thanksgiving, Christmas) 9AM-5PM</field>
		<field name="url">http://www.drivepetty.com</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">63750</field>
		<field name="title">Walt Disney World/Magic Kingdom</field>
		<field name="main">see and do</field>
		<field name="section">walt disney world speedway</field>
		<field name="name">Indy Racing Experience</field>
		<field name="content">Climb into a customized 2-seater Indy car and let a professional driver take you for a 3-lap spin around the track. Or, if youre really seeking a thrill, get behind the wheel of a real Indy car and show your own driving skills as you go around eight times!</field>
		<field name="phone">+1-888-357-5002 x106</field>
		<field name="price">$109 (riding) or $399 (driving)</field>
		<field name="email">skennedy@indyracingexperience.com</field>
		<field name="hours">Daily (except New Years Day, Thanksgiving, Christmas Eve, Christmas, New Years Eve, and during the Childrens Miracle Network Classic) 4PM-dusk</field>
		<field name="url">http://www.indyracingexperience.com/</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">63751</field>
		<field name="title">Walt Disney World/Magic Kingdom</field>
		<field name="main">see and do</field>
		<field name="section">walt disney world speedway</field>
		<field name="name">Exotic Driving Experience</field>
		<field name="content">Get behind the wheel of a high-speed "supercar" from Lamborghini, Porsche, Audi, or Ferrari. Take 6, 8, or 10 laps on the new road-course section of the speedway, or ride along as a professional driver takes you on a "Thrill Ride". Reservations required for driving; no reservations for the Thrill Ride. Drivers must be 18 or older and have a valid drivers license; riders must be 14 or older.</field>
		<field name="phone">+1 815 822-0149</field>
		<field name="price">$99 (Thrill Ride) or $199-$629 (driving) depending on car and number of laps</field>
		<field name="hours">Starts 16 Jan 2012; Thrill Rides: daily 9AM-4PM; Exotic Driving: every other day, hourly 8AM-2PM</field>
		<field name="url">http://exoticdriving.com</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">63752</field>
		<field name="title">Walt Disney World/Magic Kingdom</field>
		<field name="main">see and do</field>
		<field name="name">walt disney world speedway</field>
		<field name="content">The Walt Disney World Speedway (affectionately dubbed the "Mickyard") is a real, live tri-oval racetrack situated just south of the Magic Kingdom parking lot. The Indy Racing League and the NASCAR Truck Series used to hold events here, but there have been no professional races here in over ten years.  Today, the speedway hosts only a few unique "racing" experiences for the public:</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">63753</field>
		<field name="title">Childs</field>
		<field name="main">see and do</field>
		<field name="name">see and do</field>
		<field name="content">The First Universalist Church was built in 1834 in the Federal style and is the oldest building in the complexmdash;and also claims to be the oldest cobblestone church in the country.  It serves as the headquarters for the museum and houses the museum gift shop in its basement.  The Ward House was erected around 1836, probably as a parsonage for the church next door.  Once owned by publisher Horace Greeley (of "Go west, young man" fame), the house has been furnished and decorated in a style befitting a late 19th-century home.  The one-room District No. 5 Schoolhouse, a Greek Revival structure from 1849, is a popular destination for fourth-grade classes learning about local history.  Its actually a wood-frame building, with the cobblestones only serving as a veneer rather than being structural.  The blacksmith shop, print shop, harness shop, and farmers hall are not cobblestone buildings, but they represent other types of structures that were in use in rural communities in the 1800s.  Each has been outfitted with the tools of the corresponding trade or, in the case of the farmers hall, agricultural implements of all types.  The brick house (built 1836) between the convenience store and the church houses the museums Resource Center and is not part of the tours.  But if you want to do research into cobblestone architecture, the wealth of information within is available for your perusal, by appointment.</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">63754</field>
		<field name="title">Moorhead</field>
		<field name="main">see and do</field>
		<field name="name">Heritage Hjemkomst Interpretive Center</field>
		<field name="content">A conference center combined with a museum, this facility includes conference rooms, a replica Viking ship that actually sailed across the Atlantic, a Scandinavian Stave Church, and cultural and historical exhibits.</field>
		<field name="phone">+1 218 299-5511</field>
		<field name="price">free</field>
		<field name="fax">(218) 299-5510</field>
		<field name="url">http://www.hjemkomst-center.com/</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">63755</field>
		<field name="title">Teaneck</field>
		<field name="main">see and do</field>
		<field name="name">see and do</field>
		<field name="content">Teaneck has four main shopping areas located on Cedar Lane, Teaneck Road, DeGraw Avenue, West Englewood Avenue, and Queen Anne Road, most commonly known as "The Plaza."  Cedar Lane. One of the more popular and conveniently located streets is one of the busiest streets in town. There are over 15 restaurants, clothing stores, shoe stores, salons, and the ever so popular.  Cedar Lane Cinemas (currently closed and undergoing renovations). It is the town’s only movie theater and they occasionally host live performances by local performance groups. Many restaurant on the street are Kosher. A farmers market is held every week, even into the winter months, and has become one of the most popular events in town. Free dance lessons are also given outdoors in the summer months as a community outreach program to bring people of all ages and backgrounds together. Teaneck Road. This is another popular street for residents to shop for the essentials without having to get on any highways. This road stretches all the way through town, connecting Teaneck to its bordering towns. There is also direct access to the highway from many points on this road. West Englewood Avenue. The west portion of this street stretches from the train tracks all the way down to the Hackensack River and is mostly residential, but east of the tracks, the street is part of the Queen Anne Road "Plaza" business district and is lined with restaurants and shops. Queen Anne Road (“The Plaza”). This is the most popular road in town next to Cedar Lane because of its diversity. There is something for every demographic, whether it is a Kosher chain of places to eat, a bank, a pharmacy, and the most popular restaurant in town Mexicali Blues Café. Live bands will come and play at the café once or twice a month and the place will stay open until well passed two in the morning. The younger crowd tends to hang out down there, but up the road is referred to as “The Plaza” where families gather. Several Kosher eateries are found in the area where families can go and have their choice of pizza, falafel, chicken, bagels, pasta, chinese, sushi, Persian, Italian, burgers, salads, and even a Starbucks-like coffee house.</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">63756</field>
		<field name="title">Walt Disney World/Magic Kingdom</field>
		<field name="main">see and do</field>
		<field name="name">see and do</field>
		<field name="content">The Magic Kingdom includes many attractions that are similar, or identical, to ones found in its sister parks around the world, but also has some that are original to the Florida park, and others that started elsewhere but remain only here.  Truly enjoying this park involves a willingness to set aside disbelief and embrace the fictional worlds Disney has designed. Kids can do this instinctively, and in many respects, the best way to experience the Magic Kingdom is through the eyes of a child. The rides here are largely designed for kids, many of them painfully so, but adults with open minds (or young hearts) can have plenty of fun even without a child in tow.  Fastpass queues are available for the Barnstormer, Big Thunder Mountain Railroad, Buzz Lightyears Space Ranger Spin, Dumbo, Enchanted Tales with Belle, Jungle Cruise, Peter Pans Flight, Princess Fairytale Hall, Space Mountain, Splash Mountain, Town Square Theater, Voyage of the Little Mermaid, and Winnie the Pooh. These are all very busy attractions; in particular, Space Mountain and Splash Mountain have been known to have wait times of over three hours during peak seasons. Several of these attractions are adjacent to another, so one option (if theyre crowded) is to get a Fastpass for one of them and wait in line at the other; by the time youre done with that ride, hopefully your Fastpass time has arrived for the first one.  For parade, fireworks, and stage show performance times, which change daily, please see the Guide Map and the Times Guide youll receive when you enter the park. You can also check the Wait Times Board at the north end of Main Street, which lists current wait times for rides and show times for shows, as well as the current Fastpass return times.   The  15px  denotes rides with safety restrictions. See  Stay safe  in the main Walt Disney World article for more information.</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">63757</field>
		<field name="title">Walt Disney World/Downtown Disney</field>
		<field name="main">see and do</field>
		<field name="name">DisneyQuest</field>
		<field name="content">A five-floor indoor theme park, filled with interactive virtual-reality thrills for the whole family.  This is where the kids are going to want to go when you drag them to Downtown Disney, although the exterior is rather unassuming and you might get off easy if they dont know whats inside.  Once inside, though, good luck dragging them out.</field>
		<field name="directions">West Side</field>
		<field name="phone">+1 407 828-4600</field>
		<field name="price">Admission to the water park counts as one of your Fun Visits if youve added the Water Park Fun More option to your Magic Your Way tickets. Otherwise: ages 3-9 $38, ages 10+ $44</field>
		<field name="hours">Su-Th 11:30AM-10PM; F Sa 11:30AM-11PM</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">63758</field>
		<field name="title">Moorhead</field>
		<field name="main">see and do</field>
		<field name="name">Minnesota State University Moorhead</field>
		<field name="content">A public University with a variety of well-developed academic programs and a proud tradition in NCAA Division II athletics</field>
		<field name="phone">+1 800 593-7246</field>
		<field name="address">1104 Seventh Ave S</field>
		<field name="url">http://www.mnstate.edu/home/</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">63759</field>
		<field name="title">Moorhead</field>
		<field name="main">see and do</field>
		<field name="name">Drag Racing at Interstate Dragways</field>
		<field name="content">Heads up, brackets, and open track time is scheduled throughout the summer. The track has RV parking and a playground for children.</field>
		<field name="phone">+1 218 236-9461</field>
		<field name="url">http://www.interstatedragways.com</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">63760</field>
		<field name="title">Disneyland</field>
		<field name="main">see and do</field>
		<field name="name">see and do</field>
		<field name="content">:"I think what I want Disneyland to be most of all is a happy place, a place where adults and children can experience together some of the wonders of life, of adventure, and feel better because of it." -- Walt Disney</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">63761</field>
		<field name="title">Walt Disney World/Downtown Disney</field>
		<field name="main">see and do</field>
		<field name="name">Characters in Flight</field>
		<field name="content">The only literal "ride" in Downtown Disney, but its the tallest one on the entire property. This tethered hot-air balloon lifts you 400 feet in the air for a breathtaking birds-eye view of Walt Disney World.</field>
		<field name="directions">West Side</field>
		<field name="price">Ages 3-9 $12, ages 10+ $18; $10 before 10:30AM</field>
		<field name="hours">9AM-midnight, weather permitting</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">63762</field>
		<field name="title">Walt Disney World/Downtown Disney</field>
		<field name="main">see and do</field>
		<field name="name">AMC Pleasure Island 24</field>
		<field name="content">Okay, so youre on vacation in Florida, with four theme parks, two water parks, and a host of recreational activities to choose from; why would you spend ten bucks to sit inside and watch a movie you could see just as easily back home?  Good question.  Admittedly, this is a very nice multiplex; all 24 theaters have stadium seating, surround sound, and digital projection, and theater one is the first "ETX" auditorium in the United States (providing enhanced audio, a bigger screen, and other improvements).  And the air conditioning can be attractive on a hot day.  Or maybe you just need a break from Disney.  Whatever your reason, this is pretty much everything you could ask for in a multiplex.  New in 2011: AMCs Dine-In Theatre concept has come to 6 of the 24 auditoriums; you can order food and drinks (including beer, wine, and cocktails) right from your seat while you watch a film.</field>
		<field name="directions">West Side</field>
		<field name="phone">+1 407 827-1308</field>
		<field name="price">$8-10 (ETX $2 more)</field>
		<field name="hours">10AM-2AM</field>
		<field name="url">http://www.amcentertainment.com/PleasureIsland/</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">63763</field>
		<field name="title">Moorhead</field>
		<field name="main">see and do</field>
		<field name="name">Concordia College</field>
		<field name="content">A prestigious school with high standards and a tradition of success and prosperity</field>
		<field name="phone">+1 218 299-4000</field>
		<field name="address">901 Eighth Street S,</field>
		<field name="url">http://www.cord.edu/</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">63764</field>
		<field name="title">Moorhead</field>
		<field name="main">see and do</field>
		<field name="name">Comstock House</field>
		<field name="content">Guided tours, antique furniture and tapestries enlighten visitors to Moorheads first mansion, the home of Solomon Comstock.</field>
		<field name="phone">+1 218 291-4211</field>
		<field name="address">560 Eighth Street S</field>
		<field name="email">comstock@mnhs.org</field>
		<field name="url">http://www.mnhs.org/places/sites/ch/</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">63765</field>
		<field name="title">Walt Disney World/Animal Kingdom</field>
		<field name="main">see and do</field>
		<field name="name">see and do</field>
		<field name="content">Animal Kingdom has a broad mix of attractions, from simply looking at the many animals on display, to tuneful stage shows, to high-energy thrill rides.  Theres a little something for everyone here, but families with divergent tastes may want to split up, so Grandma and Grandpa can take a stroll through the animal enclosures while the kids go on Expedition Everest for the third time.   No fences, no wires, just beautiful open savanna as far as you can see   Theres one very important thing to keep in mind if you want to get good views of the animals.  Remember that it can get very hot during the day, and its not just tourists who seek shade when the sun beats down.  The animals will be more active and more visible first thing in the morning and at the end of the day, and that means closer looks and better pictures for you.  As you walk around, you may spot an animal handler exhibiting one or two small animals up close to a small crowd of guestsmdash;these encounters occur randomly throughout the day at a variety of locations, so keep your eyes peeled.  There are also several character greeting locations; these will be marked on your guide map and schedules will be listed in your Times Guide.  Fastpass queues are available for Dinosaur, Expedition Everest, Kali River Rapids, Kilimanjaro Safaris, and Primeval Whirl.  Expedition Everest is easily the most popular of these rides, but if you take the Fastpass, youll miss some of the storyline found in the detailed standby queue.  For parade and stage show performance times, which change daily, please see the Guide Map and the Times Guide youll receive when you enter the park.  You can also check the Wait Times Board on Discovery Island, which lists current wait times for rides and show times for shows.  The  15px  denotes rides with safety restrictions. See  Stay safe  in the main Walt Disney World article for more information.</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">63766</field>
		<field name="title">Lake Havasu City</field>
		<field name="main">see and do</field>
		<field name="name">see and do</field>
		<field name="content">London Bridge   There are some great sunsets to see in this area in the summer as the sun goes down over the surrounding hills. There are many places to do watersports on the lake with this a popular destination for boating holidays. There is also a golf range near one of the hotels.</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">63767</field>
		<field name="title">Walt Disney World/Epcot</field>
		<field name="main">see and do</field>
		<field name="name">see and do</field>
		<field name="content">When it opened, Epcot had no thrill rides at all. Although thats been changing, youll find that the majority of attractions are still fairly sedate dark rides or straightforward films. Thats not to say theyre not worth doing, but youre in the wrong park if you just want to get your adrenaline pumping. Epcot does have two high-octane thrill rides, Test Track and Mission: SPACE, while the Maelstrom and Soarin offer excitement in smaller doses.  FastPass queues are available for Living with the Land, The Maelstrom, Mission: SPACE, Soarin, and Test Track. Soarin is very popular, possibly the most popular ride in the park; FastPasses are highly recommended. Test Track and Mission: SPACE are adjacent to each other, so your best bet there (if theyre crowded) is to get a FastPass for one of them and wait in line at the other; by the time youre done with that ride, hopefully your FastPass time has arrived for the first one.  For parade and stage show performance times, which change daily, please see the Guide Map and the Times Guide youll receive when you enter the park. You can also check the Wait Times Board in Innoventions Plaza, which lists current wait times for rides and show times for shows, as well as the current Fastpass return times.   The  15px  denotes rides with safety restrictions. See  Stay safe  in the main Walt Disney World article for more information.</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">63768</field>
		<field name="title">Walt Disney World/Hollywood Studios</field>
		<field name="main">see and do</field>
		<field name="name">see and do</field>
		<field name="content">The unfortunate façade of the Hollywood Tower Hotel. If someone offers you a ride to the thirteenth floor in the elevator, you may be in for a ... let-down.     Hollywood Studios attractions separate into one of two camps: sedate but fun stage shows and up-tempo thrill rides.  Theres very little in-between; even The Great Movie Ride is more like a theater production than a ride.  Toy Story Mania! may be the first attraction that could be said to bridge that gap.  Fastpass queues are available for the Indiana Jones Epic Stunt Spectacular, Rock n Roller Coaster, Star Tours, Tower of Terror, Toy Story Mania, and Voyage of The Little Mermaid.  Toy Story Mania in particular is incredibly popular; a Fastpass is highly recommended.  Rock n Roller Coaster and the Tower of Terror are adjacent to each other, so your best bet there is to get a Fastpass for one of them and wait in line at the other; by the time youre done with that ride, hopefully your Fastpass time has arrived for the first one.  For parade and stage show performance times, which change daily, please see the Guide Map and the Times Guide youll receive when you enter the park.  You can also check the Wait Times Board at the corner of Hollywood and Sunset Boulevards, which lists current wait times for rides and show times for shows.   The  15px  denotes rides with safety restrictions. See  Stay safe  in the main Walt Disney World article for more information.</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">63769</field>
		<field name="title">Walt Disney World/Downtown Disney</field>
		<field name="main">see and do</field>
		<field name="name">Capn Jacks Marina</field>
		<field name="content">Rent a canopy boat, a pontoon boat, or a "water mouse" and explore Village Lake and the Sassagoula River.  Bass fishing tours are also available from here.  Call Disney Recreation at +1 407 WDW-PLAY (939-7529) for reservations.</field>
		<field name="directions">Marketplace</field>
		<field name="price">$20+</field>
		<field name="hours">opens at 10AM (closing time varies seasonally)</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">63770</field>
		<field name="title">Childs</field>
		<field name="main">see and do</field>
		<field name="name">Cobblestone Museum Complex</field>
		<field name="content">The Cobblestone Museum is the main attraction in the hamlet.  It also happens to be the only attraction.  The Cobblestone Society was formed in 1960 to preserve the First Universalist Church, which was in danger of permanent deterioration.  The church, schoolhouse, and the Ward Housemdash;the first three components of the complexmdash;together constitute a National Historic Landmark, the Cobblestone Historic District.  The other buildings were added over time but are equally worth visiting.</field>
		<field name="directions">parking behind the church, east of Rt 98</field>
		<field name="phone">+1 585 589-9013</field>
		<field name="price">Adults $8, seniors $6</field>
		<field name="address">14393 Ridge Rd, Albion</field>
		<field name="email">info@cobblestonemuseum.org</field>
		<field name="hours">Jun 23 - Sep 2: Su 1PM-5PM, Tu-Sa 11AM-5PM; Sep 3 - Oct: Su 1PM-5PM; last tour leaves at 4PM</field>
		<field name="url">http://www.cobblestonemuseum.org/</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">63771</field>
		<field name="title">Walt Disney World/Downtown Disney</field>
		<field name="main">see and do</field>
		<field name="name">Splitsville</field>
		<field name="content">This growing chain of bowling centers seems like a perfect fit for the nightlife-and-entertainment atmosphere of the West Side—and with thirty lanes spread over two floors, this is the largest Splitsville ever built.  Far more than just a bowling alley, Splitsville features bowling concierges who bring your shoes, balls, and food right to your lane; an extensive restaurant menu with both casual and innovative cuisine; a full bar; and live music every night.  With so much to do, even people who dont bowl can have a great time.</field>
		<field name="directions">West Side</field>
		<field name="hours">opens December 19</field>
		<field name="alt">bowling</field>
		<field name="url">http://www.splitsvillelanes.com</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">63772</field>
		<field name="title">Walt Disney World</field>
		<field name="main">see and do</field>
		<field name="name">see and do</field>
		<field name="content">:"Here in Florida, we have something special we never enjoyed at Disneyland mdash; the blessing of size. Theres enough land here to hold all the ideas and plans we can possibly imagine." mdash; Walt Disney   There is a lot to do at Walt Disney World, and only some of it involves standing in lines or meeting Mickey Mouse.  In fact, theres so much to do that you simply cant do it all; dont even try!  Instead, prioritize.  Of course you have to visit the theme parks, but not necessarily every day.  Leave time for shopping, boating, dining, swimming, golfing, and relaxing.  The people who really enjoy Walt Disney World, the ones who return like clockwork, know how to balance time in the parks with time outside the parks.  And both can be equally magical.</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">63773</field>
		<field name="title">Walt Disney World/Downtown Disney</field>
		<field name="main">see and do</field>
		<field name="name">see and do</field>
		<field name="content">La Noubas massive home on Downtown Disneys West Side.   You may have come for the shopping or for the food, but you shouldnt overlook the other attractions of Downtown Disney.  You can go to the movies, rent a boat, see a show, or even take a trip on the tallest attraction at Walt Disney World.  Youll also find live entertainmentmdash;music and comedymdash;at various venues throughout the complex, especially at night.  (For example, look for Nova Era, a chamber trio playing classical music with a modern twist, Thursdays through Sundays outside Fultons Crab House.)  And dont miss DisneyQuest, a theme-park-in-a-box that kids will love.           Aladdins Magic Carpet Ride (second floor). A stationary unit uses a head-mounted display to let you pilot a flying carpet through the streets of Agrabah.  Buzz Lightyears AstroBlaster (third floor). You and a friend climb into special bumper vehicles, from which you can fire soft "asteroids" at other players, disabling their vehicles for a short time and scoring points.  Chaotic but fun.  CyberSpace Mountain (second floor). First, Bill Nye the Science Guy walks you through creating a fantastical roller coaster layout.  Then you and a friend can climb into a pitch-and-roll simulation pod and ride your creation from start to finish!  Invasion! An ExtraTERRORestrial Alien Encounter (fifth floor). Team up with friends to ride through an alien landscape and try to rescue colonists from evil aliens.  Mighty Ducks Pinball Slam (third floor). Compete with 11 other players on a pinball-like board, controlling your ball by rocking back and forth on a platform.  Pirates of the Caribbean: Battle for Buccaneer Gold (first floor). In many ways a prototype for "Toy Story Mania!", this attraction puts you on the deck of a pirate ship.  3D headsets let you see the enemy ships; one player steers while up to four others fire the cannons.  Can you plunder enough gold to defeat the powerful ghost ship?  Great fun for groups, as cooperation is required and the action is fast and furious.  Ride the Comix (fourth and fifth floors). Head-mounted displays let up to six players enter a comic-book-like world and use a laser sword to fight enemies.  Virtual Jungle Cruise (first floor). Climb into a raft with your friends and paddle down a dangerous jungle river.  The Create Zone on the second floor is a grouping of several attractions that allow participants to exercise their creativity.  These attractions include Animation Academy, Living Easels, Radio Disney Song Maker, and Sids Create-A-Toy.  Many of these are good for younger kids because they can see and (in the case of Sids Create-A-Toy) hold the products of their imaginations.  Songs and toys are available for purchase after creation.  On the third floor youll find video game arcades, one with modern video games and one with classic arcade games, all free to play with admission.</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">63774</field>
		<field name="title">Moorhead</field>
		<field name="main">see and do</field>
		<field name="name">see and do</field>
		<field name="content">In addition, theres a variety of fun activities and interesting landmarks across the river in  Fargo .  These include many restaurants, shopping, professional minor-league baseball, museums, and more.</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">63775</field>
		<field name="title">Walt Disney World/Downtown Disney</field>
		<field name="main">see and do</field>
		<field name="name">La Nouba</field>
		<field name="content">Famed contemporary circus company Cirque du Soleil created "La Nouba" especially for Downtown Disney, and Disney created the distinctive round tent-like theater just for them.  Unlike a traditional circus, there are no animal performers, just an awe-inspiring troupe of athletes, acrobats, and clowns, performing specific characters in an overarching storyline.  Youll have to see it to believe it.</field>
		<field name="directions">West Side</field>
		<field name="phone">+1 407 934-9200</field>
		<field name="price">Ages 3-9 $62-109, ages 10+ $78-136</field>
		<field name="hours">Tu-Sa 6PM 9PM</field>
		<field name="alt">Cirque du Soleil</field>
		<field name="url">http://www.cirquedusoleil.com/en/shows/lanouba/</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">63776</field>
		<field name="title">Lake Havasu City</field>
		<field name="main">see and do</field>
		<field name="name">London Bridge</field>
		<field name="content">Built in 1831 over the River Thames in London (replacing an earlier bridge from the 13th century), the bridge was dismantled in 1967 and shipped in pieces to Lake Havasu City, where it was carefully reconstructed.</field>
		<field name="store">34.47159,-114.34751</field>
		<field name="address">McCulloch Blvd over the Bridgewater Channel Canal</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
</add>