<add>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">87505</field>
		<field name="title">Wellsboro</field>
		<field name="main">see/do</field>
		<field name="name">festivals</field>
		<field name="content">Mountain Laurel Flower  Pennsylvania State Laurel Festival: The Pennsylvania State Laurel Festival is held in Wellsboro every year for 9 days starting the second Saturday of  June. (2011s June 11-19). The festival is held to celebrate the community of Wellsboro, to promote the Pennsylvania Grand Canyon, and the Pennsylvania State Flower, the Mountain Laurel. Numerous events are held during this week and include a pet parade, craft fair, bike race, carnival, 10K and 2-mile runs, various concerts, and the Laurel Parade(3rd Saturday of June). Over the years upwards of 80 ladies around PA represented their high schools in the Laurel Queen pageant.  28 young women from around the keystone state competed in 2011. If youre visiting Wellsboro during the Laurel Festival, a tradition since the 1930s is definitely something worth checking out.  Dickens of a Christmas: Held the first Friday and Saturday of December annually brings local and regional crafters to Wellsboro, who set up on the sidewalks in front of local merchants for Saturdays festivities. All vendors and merchants along with community players dress in Victorian-era costumes ala Charles Dickens A Christmas Carol. Main Street is shut off from early Saturday morning through roughly 4PM to allow the thousands of visitors the opportunity to cross among the shops unhindered by traffic. Horse-drawn wagon rides are given up and down the gas-lit and Christmas tree decorated boulevards. Various musicians stroll around town, and the community Mens Womens Choruses give performances. Some churches and community halls also have crafters on hand. The event is wrapped up with a candle-light peace walk from Packer Park to "The Green" where the community Christmas tree is lit and St.Nick usually arrives on a fire truck.</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">87506</field>
		<field name="title">Glenrio</field>
		<field name="main">see/do</field>
		<field name="name">Brownlee Diner/Little Juarez Café</field>
		<field name="content">Constructed in 1952 in art moderne architectural style, this building becomes part of the abandoned "Glenn Rio Motel" complex and a museum site in Pixars 2006 film "Cars".</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">87507</field>
		<field name="title">Boardman</field>
		<field name="main">see/do</field>
		<field name="name">see/do</field>
		<field name="content">The Boardman Marina Park    is perhaps the largest attraction that the town of Boardman has to offer.  It is located along the Columbia River and individuals have the opportunity to camp along the waters of the Columbia and enjoy beautiful sunsets.  During the summer these waters are full of life.  It is not uncommon to see many individuals participating in things such as boating, jet skiing or wakeboarding.  Also, Boarman hosts a couple fishing tournaments every year so it is apparent that fishing is one of the more plentiful events that takes place in this area.  For individuals who would rather stay on dry land, there are other forms of entertainment that are available. There are many paved walking and biking trails located along the rivers edge.  Also, there is a playground area for those who bring their children as well as a specified swimming area.  As far as recreational games are concerned, there are 2 softball fields, a basketball court and several horseshoe pits.  Boardman is probably most known for it annual fourth of July festivities.  Individuals from many surrounding towns come to join the festivities.  The day usually starts with an early morning marathon, continues with a parade and eventually ends with a beautiful firework show.  There are many other activities that take place throughout the day as well.  The most entertaining of these events would probably have to either be the lip sync contest or the annual softball tournament in which the winner receives a rather impressive trophy.   For those who are looking for things to do that are not related to the Park, the Boardman Willow Run golf course is a great place to relax on a nice sunny day.  Also, with so much wildlife area surrounding it, Boardman is a great place to go on horseback rides.</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">87508</field>
		<field name="title">Glenrio</field>
		<field name="main">see/do</field>
		<field name="name">Joseph Brownlee House</field>
		<field name="content">Constructed in Amarillo in 1930 and moved to Glenrio in 1950, this was one of the last Glenrio buildings to be abandoned after the town was bypassed.</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">87509</field>
		<field name="title">Glenrio</field>
		<field name="main">see/do</field>
		<field name="name">First / Last Motel in Texas</field>
		<field name="content">Opened in 1953 as State Line Café and Gas Station; its 1955 Texas Longhorn Motel closed in 1976. Signage proclaimed "First Motel in Texas" to eastbound motorists and "Last Motel in Texas" to westbound traffic.</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">87510</field>
		<field name="title">North Pole (New York)</field>
		<field name="main">see/do</field>
		<field name="name">Santas Workshop</field>
		<field name="content">Santa and Christmas theme park with entertainment, rides and shops. Many rides have a maximum 75 lbs. weight, 48" height limit as these are intended for small children.</field>
		<field name="phone">+1 518 946-2211</field>
		<field name="price">$18-20/person</field>
		<field name="address">324 Whiteface Memorial Highway</field>
		<field name="wikipedia">Santas Workshop (amusement park)</field>
		<field name="tollfree">+1-800-806-0215</field>
		<field name="url">http://www.northpoleny.com</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">87511</field>
		<field name="title">Adrian (Texas)</field>
		<field name="main">see/do</field>
		<field name="name">Bent Door Café</field>
		<field name="content">Former roadside café and trading post built in 1947 from World War II surplus, incorporates portions of a decommissioned wartime air traffic control tower. The tower windows originally slanted toward the runway so the door is bent to match.</field>
		<field name="hours">closed, under renovation</field>
		<field name="url">http://bentdoor.wordpress.com</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">87512</field>
		<field name="title">Adrian (Texas)</field>
		<field name="main">see/do</field>
		<field name="name">Julians Bivins Museum</field>
		<field name="content">Former courthouse converted into a museum that features the history of Oldham County.</field>
		<field name="price">Free</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">87513</field>
		<field name="title">Adrian (Texas)</field>
		<field name="main">see/do</field>
		<field name="name">Adrian Lions Antique Museum</field>
		<field name="content">Antique farming and ranching equipment.</field>
		<field name="price">Free</field>
		<field name="address">Old Route 66</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">87514</field>
		<field name="title">Deadhorse</field>
		<field name="main">see/do</field>
		<field name="name">see/do</field>
		<field name="content">The Dalton Highway ends just a few miles inland of the Arctic Ocean and only private, restricted roads extend to the ocean. Fortunately, tours can be booked through the hotels in the town which not only take you to the ocean and its gravel beach (where you can take a frigid dip, joining the "Polar Bear Club") but also include a tour of the oilfield and operations. The ocean is ice-free from late July to October.</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">87515</field>
		<field name="title">Wellsboro</field>
		<field name="main">see/do</field>
		<field name="name">see/do</field>
		<field name="content">Outdoor Adventures  Pennsylvania Grand Canyon: Wellsboro is home to Pine Creek Gorge or better known as the Grand Canyon of  Pennsylvania Grand Canyon Pennsylvania. It only takes approximately 15 minutes to get to the Pennsylvania Grand Canyon from the town of Wellsboro. The Pennsylvania Grand Canyon offers hiking and biking trails as well as area parks for fishing, swimming, or kayaking.    Tioga Trail Rides:  Take a horseback ride while enjoying the beautiful scenery of Pennsylvanias countryside. Tioga Trail Rides provides guided tours that meet the needs of everyone. The price is $23 per person for 1 hour and $46 per person for 2 hours. Special trail rides such as the Sunset Ride ($46 per person), the Campfire Rid ($51 per person), and the Supper Ride ($61 per person) are also available. Reservations are required for all horseback rides. Call (570) 724-6592 to book reservations.  Tyoga Country Club:  http://www.tyogacc.com/fees.htm  The Tyoga Country Club is a four star golf course. It is located 2 miles west of Wellsboro on Rt660/Old Pine Creek Road. You do not have to be a member in order to play a round of golf at this country club. The price per round is $58 per person during the week and $63 on weekends. Both of these prices include golf carts. There is also a Clubhouse that serves lunch and dinner. The facility also hosts many weddings and wedding receptions!  For more information call (570) 724-1653 ext. 3  Tioga-Hammond Lakes: http://www.nab.usace.army.mil/recreation/tioga.htm  The Tioga-Hammond Lakes are located on Route 15 12 miles north of Wellsboro. The lakes offer a variety of outdoor family activities include swimming, boating, fishing, hunting, hiking, and picnicking. Overnight facilities are also provided for those who wish to spend more than one day exploring the lakes. For more information call (877) 444-6777  Animaland Zoological Park:  http://www.animalandzoo.com  It only takes a few minutes to get from Wellsboro to Animaland Zoological Park. The zoo houses over 200 domestic, exotic, and wild animals within 12 acres. You can walk through the 2-mile walk-thru at your own pace. The zoo is handicap accessible. The entry price is $7 for Students (13+) and Senior Citizens (65+), $8 for Adults, $5 for Children (3-12), and free for Children 2 and under. For more information call (570) 724-4546.   Ski Denton: http://www.skidenton.com/  If you are planning your visit to Wellsboro in the winter and love to ski Ski Denton  is a great place to go. Ski Denton is open year-round because it now provides planned and guided bike routes and trips.  It is located west of town along Rt 6, 11 miles before getting to Coudersport, PA and takes approximately 30 minutes to get to from Wellsboro. Chalets are available for those who wish to spend more than one day there. Ski Denton provides reasonable prices: $25 for adults 9AM-4PM and $15 for any 4 hour time frame; $15 for youth 9AM-4PM and $10 for any 4 hour time frame. For more information call (814) 435-2115.  Indoor Activities  Tioga Central Railroad  	 The Arcadia Theatre: http://www.arcadiawellsboro.com/  If youre bored one night and dont know what else to do go to the Arcadia Theatre and catch up on some of the latest movies. The Arcadia Theatre is a 4-screen theater located on 50 Main Street in Wellsboro. Admission is Night Shows: $6.50 for adults and $4 for children 12 under. Matinees: $5.50 for adults and $4 for children 12 under. The theatre offers a Tuesday night special where adults can see a movie for only $5. For more information call (570) 724-4957.   Tioga Central Railroad: http://www.tiogacentral.com/  The Tioga Central Railroad provides various different types of train  tours. It also provides seasonal tours in addition to the regular tours such as the Foliage Express that allows you to view the leaves changing colors and the Oktoberfest Dinner Train. Each train provides an open observation car that allows you to take in the full view of the scenery. For more information call (570) 724-0990.</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">87516</field>
		<field name="title">Glenrio</field>
		<field name="main">see/do</field>
		<field name="name">see/do</field>
		<field name="content">Abandoned diner</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">87517</field>
		<field name="title">Galena (Kansas)</field>
		<field name="main">see/do</field>
		<field name="name">Galena Mining Historical Museum</field>
		<field name="content">Mining museum in relocated Missouri-Texas-Kansas railroad depot. Mineral specimens, mining equipment and a model of the Grand Central Mine formerly east of Galena. Collection of oil paintings titled "Abandoned Mine Scenes" by a local artist.</field>
		<field name="phone">+1 620 783-2192</field>
		<field name="price">free</field>
		<field name="address">319 W. 7th</field>
		<field name="hours">9-11AM 1-3:30PM, closed Sun, reduced hours off-season</field>
		<field name="url">http://www.kansastravel.org/galenaminingmuseum.htm</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">87518</field>
		<field name="title">San Jon</field>
		<field name="main">see/do</field>
		<field name="name">Caprock Amphitheatre</field>
		<field name="content">Former 955-seat outdoor amphitheatre with concession stand, bleachers and stage north of Clovis NM. Presented live theatre (including 1985 outdoor drama "Billy the Kid") for ten years before closing due to declining audience size. Empty and abandoned by 1997, the village of San Jon proposed to take over the site in 2007. As of 2008, the pavilion and seating areas has been gated off but the remainder of the site was open as rugged terrain for hiking.</field>
		<field name="address">10 mi. S of San Jon</field>
		<field name="alt">Nature Walk</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">87519</field>
		<field name="title">North Pole (New York)</field>
		<field name="main">see/do</field>
		<field name="name">see/do</field>
		<field name="content">Santas Workshop</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
</add>