<add>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">87759</field>
		<field name="title">Noblesville</field>
		<field name="main">shop</field>
		<field name="name">shop</field>
		<field name="content">Hamilton Town Center  3901 Town Center Blvd. The newest Simon Mall property opened in spring 2008 features a mix of retail, restaurants and entertainment in the now popular open-air mall concept.  A 16-screen movie theater is anchored by an IMAX 3D. Milwaukee restaurateur Johnny Vassallo opened one of two Mo’s Irish Pubs on the property.  Historic Noblesville Square Between 8th and Logan Street and 9th and Conner Street. The Noblesvlle commercial historic district sits at the center of the community, literally and figuratively.  It combines historic architecture and embraces its small town character to its advantage.  Stores include furniture, art, wine, antiques, clothing and even children’s books. A few shops are listed in more detail below.   J’Ann Co.  930 Logan St. 1-317-776-4088. A lady’s boutique and bridal shop.  The Faux Flower Gift Shop 84 S. 9th St. 1-317-770-0088. Specializes in custom, botanically correct “fake” flower design and arrangement.  Also sell home décor, gifts and collectables.  Strawtown Pottery Antiques 12738 Strawtown Ave. 1-317-984-5080. They have been creating stoneware here since 1983.  Also sell antiques and pottery accessories.   Carriage House Antiques Uniques  1091 Conner Street 1-317-770-3970 Specialty shop featuring antiques, unique gift items, garden art and interior design.   Old Picket Fence  894 Logan Street 1-317-774-1800 Old Picket Fence represents antique and vintage items of quality, material and craftsmanship as well as newer items for todays blend of comfort and style.  Artists on the Square Gallery 853 Conner Street 1-317-716-3998 The Artists on the Square Gallery offers one-of-a-kind artwork created locally and ranging from traditional to modern art. The work is moderately priced and ready to enjoy.   Bundy Decoy Company, Inc.  16506 Strawtown Avenue 1-317-770-5280 Duck Decoys are one of the few forms of truly American folk art. Native Americans were the first to use a decoy for the purpose of luring a game bird from the sky. The oldest decoys ever found were Canvasbacks made from reeds and feathers and date back over 1400 years ago. Over the centuries decoys evolved into wooden carvings. Each decoy carver developed his own distinct style. While the decoys are not used for hunting, they are American folk art and we carve them with craftsmanship and pride, one of a kind, one at a time. No two Bundy Decoys are alike, which is partly why they are so collectable. The one you purchase will be one of a kind. While there are all kinds of gift items in todays world, there are very few that are still made from real wood and even fewer that are made right from the log. Each decoy is handled 28 times and requires many hours of hand labor per piece.   A Corner Cottage   895 Conner Street 1-317-770-7577 A small shop located at the corner of 9th and Conner in Noblesville. They carry a wide array of gifts, favors, and greeting cards, home decor garden items, Signature Pottery, vintage, and antique items, and many surprises.   Eleanor Rozellas  982 Loagan Street 1-317-774-8393 Upscale girly-girl boutique with 3.5 wonderful levels of great merchandise - Vera Bradley, Colts items, home decor, jewelry, Toms Shoes, clothing and gourmet foods.   Garden Thyme at the Old Schoolhouse  14520 SR 38 E. 1-317-714-3273 Garden Thyme at the Old Schoolhouse is all about the garden and what goes into it. Beautiful plants, garden treasures, to architectural salvage surround the lovely 1898 schoolhouse. Your purchases help restore it!   Linden Tree Unique Gifts  856 Logan Street 1-317-773-3238 Linden Tree has a longstanding tradition of providing unique, specialty products and gifts at reasonable prices. Linden Tree offers home accent pieces including rugs, lamps and wall art. Interior designers are on site or available by appointment to help with selections.Free gift wrapping is available.   Logan Village Mall  977 Logan Street 1-317-776-9999 Over 40 charming shops under one roof. This former newspaper building is a unique village offering antiques, vintage and new gifts, home decor and more.  Martha Janes 50 N. 9th Street 1-317-773-3803 Ladies boutique featuring jewelry, purses and fashion - accessories for everyone; including everyday, trendy and special occasion pieces. Come pamper yourself!  Noblesville Clock Company 996 Conner Street 1-317-776-9270 We welcome you to visit our showroom located at 996 Conner street in historical downtown Noblesville. We have a very large selection of wall clocks, mantle clocks Cuckoo clocks, Grandfather clocks, Neon signs, candles and much much more.   The Wild  884 Logan Street 1-317-773-0920 The Wild Bookstore is the first independent bookstore located on the Historic Noblesville Square. Specializing in the next generation of bookworms, offering childrens books, games, toys and puzzles.</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">87760</field>
		<field name="title">Marshfield (Massachusetts)</field>
		<field name="main">shop</field>
		<field name="name">shop</field>
		<field name="content">Bikeway, Marshfield Plaza, Phone: +1 781-837-2453.  Brant Rock Fish Market, 267 Ocean St., Phone: +1 781-834-6231.  Webster Square Shopping Plaza, Marshalls, Radio Shack, The Job Lot, Star Market and Family Dollar.   CVS, 1880 Ocean Street 781-837-5381   Rite Aid 1900 Ocean Street, 781-319-0012  Shore Things, 263 Ocean St Phone: 781-834-4877. Full Time hours memorial day-labor day. Year round Sat Sun 1-4. This is a boutique like beach shop that sells beach accessories, jewelry, gifts, t shirts, etc.  Mono Mono, 1871A Ocean St. Phone: 781-837-6565 Open Wed-Sat 11am-6pm. Boutique/gift shop, Special occasion gifts. Very cute moderately priced accessories, jewelry, etc.</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">87761</field>
		<field name="title">Westchester County</field>
		<field name="main">shop</field>
		<field name="name">shop</field>
		<field name="content">The Westchester Mall Located in  White Plains , upscale shopping mall.  The Galleria Located in  White Plains .  Cross County Shopping Center Newly renovated outdoor mall located in  Yonkers .  Jefferson Valley Mall Located in  Yorktown Heights  in northern Westchester.</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">87762</field>
		<field name="title">Rome (Georgia)</field>
		<field name="main">shop</field>
		<field name="name">shop</field>
		<field name="content">Mel Mimis  Alexs  Blue Sky Outfitters  Elysium Inc Sterling Silver Jewelry</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">87763</field>
		<field name="title">Sycamore</field>
		<field name="main">shop</field>
		<field name="name">shop</field>
		<field name="content">Discover Sycamore members are local businesses and organizations that invest in the community. These members are active in making Sycamore an exceptional place to live,work and visit. Please consider using Discover Members as frequently as possible. For a complete list of members check our website.</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">87764</field>
		<field name="title">Landisville</field>
		<field name="main">shop</field>
		<field name="name">shop</field>
		<field name="content">There are a lot of great places to shop near Landisville. Inside Landisville you have your common shopping places like CVS/Pharmacy, grocery stores, and Kmart.  If you are looking to do some actual shopping, it is only a short car ride to a variety of different stores.  - Park City Mall- Park City offers a very wide variety of shopping that will satisfy everyone. Stores range from While House, Black Market and William Sanoma to Game Stop and Justice. Park City does not just offer stores, but it also has bunch of food places in the food court, around the inside of the mall, and on the outskirts of the parking lot. Food stops are, but definitly not limited to, Auntie Annies, Burger King, TGI Fridays, Olive Garden and Long Horn Steak House.     - Rockvale Outlets - The Rockvale Outlets are located about a 30 minute drive from Landisville. The shops included in these outlets will also satisfy everyone in the family with shops including Pottery Barn, Gold Toe, Under Amour, and much, much more. There are also food stops close by including AppleBees and Fudruckers.  - Tanger Outlets - The Tanger Outlets are also located about a 30 minute drive from Landisville. These shops include Coach, American Eagle, Zumiez, and of course a lot more. Food stops near the Tanger Outlets include Sonic, Arbys and Subway. If you cannot decide which outlet store you want to go to...DONT WORRY! The two are only about 5 minutes apart from each other, and Park City Mall is located on Route 30, and you pass it on the way to the two outlet centers.</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">87765</field>
		<field name="title">Corydon</field>
		<field name="main">shop</field>
		<field name="name">shop</field>
		<field name="content">Cellar on the Square, 110 Elm Street, (812) 968-5510,   . Beer wine making supplies equipment, old fashion candy. Colokial, 117 W Walnut St. (812) 738-1320,   . Handmade Items from around the world. Handbags, Home decor, Jewelry, Religious items</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">87766</field>
		<field name="title">Dubuque</field>
		<field name="main">shop</field>
		<field name="name">shop</field>
		<field name="content">Asbury Plaza Corner of Asbury Rd and Northwest Arterial. Outdoor shopping complex in the West End. Home to Kohls, Sams Club, Hy-Vee, and Star Cinemas.   Kennedy Mall 555 Kennedy Rd, 563.556.1994    Iowas first enclosed shopping mall has recently undergone renovations. Home to Mindframe Theaters, Dubuques independent cinema, as well as anchors Sears, Younkers, and JC Penney.</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">87767</field>
		<field name="title">Mission Viejo</field>
		<field name="main">shop</field>
		<field name="name">shop</field>
		<field name="content">Irvine Spectrum (not in MV itself, but near enough that many Mission Viejans consider it part of their home territory)   Shops at Mission Viejo   , a luxurious shopping mall.</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">87768</field>
		<field name="title">Michigan</field>
		<field name="main">shop</field>
		<field name="name">shop</field>
		<field name="content">Michigan has a draw to shopping based on the many unique coastal towns and the look and feel of its tourist areas and attractions. Michigan has a fixed 6% sales tax which is rarely included in the advertised price (like the rest of the United States). Most groceries and many personal items are not taxed.  Antiques Markets, Shops and Shows are a big attraction in the Great Lakes Area.  Below is a list of cities, shops and events, in alphabetical order:  Shops (Open Year Round)   TBD  Markets Shows(Regularly Recurring Large Events)    Allegan Antiques Market .  Six Shows every season.  Last Sunday of every month, April through September.  Visit the web site for exact dates each season, directions and contact information.</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
</add>