<add>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">64804</field>
		<field name="title">New Jersey</field>
		<field name="main">talk</field>
		<field name="name">philadelphia influence on south jersey accent</field>
		<field name="content">wooder: water  caw-fee: coffee</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">64805</field>
		<field name="title">New Jersey</field>
		<field name="main">talk</field>
		<field name="name">new york influence on north jersey accent</field>
		<field name="content">(Note: Most people do not speak this dramatically, but many do to one degree or another)  "Ah" sounds become "Aw" Ex: Coffee=Cawfee, Dog=Dawg  "g"s in "ing"s are dropped Ex: Talking=Tawkin, Eating=Eatin  "Or" becomes "Ahr" Ex: Orange=Ah-runge, Forest(For-ust)=Fahrest(Far-ust)</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">64806</field>
		<field name="title">New Jersey</field>
		<field name="main">talk</field>
		<field name="name">etiquette</field>
		<field name="content">Disparaging references to a "New Joisey" accent, "guidos" (working class Italian-Americans), the popular HBO series The Sopranos, or any part of the states appearance are not recommended.  Such characterizations are unwarranted and may be resented by residents.</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">64807</field>
		<field name="title">Colorado</field>
		<field name="main">talk</field>
		<field name="name">talk</field>
		<field name="content">While English is, of course, the main language of Colorado,  Spanish  is also widely spoken (20% of the population speaks it). There are large Latino populations in Denver, Pueblo and  in the San Luis Valley.</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">64808</field>
		<field name="title">Ohio</field>
		<field name="main">talk</field>
		<field name="name">talk</field>
		<field name="content">Despite what you may have heard, Ohio is very diverse with regional dialects. In the middle of the state, especially Dayton and Columbus, many people speak what is commonly known as General American Dialect, or Standard Midwestern Dialect.  Around Cleveland and Toledo people speak with what is known as the Northern Cities Vowel shift of same dialect, sounding way more like a Chicagoan (think Da Bears from Saturday Night Live for a really exaggerated example).  In the  Amish Country  between Cleveland and Columbus English is actually a second language for the Amish populations with Pennsylvania Dutch, their first.  Pretty much all Amish speak English outside of the home but with a distinct accent.  In inner cities of Cincinnati, Cleveland, and Columbus there are hundreds of thousands of African-Americans who speak what is called Black English Vernacular. As you move South and Southeast, you may encounter those who speak Southern American English-- especially in the Greater Cincinnati Metropolitan Area.  White non Appalachian populations in the Greater Cincinnati area have a slight dialect differences influenced by their heavily German population with a few local colloquialisms like “Pony Keg” for Convenience Store, and using “Please?” instead of “What?” when asking someone to repeat themselves.</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">64809</field>
		<field name="title">Big Island</field>
		<field name="main">talk</field>
		<field name="name">talk</field>
		<field name="content">Locals refer to elders as "Auntie" or "Uncle" instead of "sir" or "maam," and flip-flops are called "slippers." People in Hawaii are very friendly and always looking forward to talking about their island, their history and its culture.</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">64810</field>
		<field name="title">Salem County</field>
		<field name="main">talk</field>
		<field name="name">talk</field>
		<field name="content">Like a person from South Jersey. The "wurdur" on the "ruff" is near the "chimbley" and that can be "baed"</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">64811</field>
		<field name="title">South (United States of America)</field>
		<field name="main">talk</field>
		<field name="name">talk</field>
		<field name="content">One of the most important identifiers of the cultural South is the dialect with which its people speak. Southerners from the  Eastern Shore (Maryland)  to  North Florida , and as far west as  Texas  speak with a very distinct accent that is different from the rest of the  United States .  The accent is typically described as having a "drawl" or "twang".   Visitors might note that there is some sub-regional variation in the Southern accent and dialect. In general, the local accent/dialect changes as one passes through geographical regions (i.e., mountain dwellers speak a different dialect than those on the coast). Also, generally speaking, accents tend to be much heavier in rural areas.  While Americans tend to speak about a single "Southern" dialect, there are actually a variety of dialects. Visitors (especially non-native English speakers) might have trouble understanding heavier accents or local terminology.   The pronoun "yall" (a contraction of "you all") is a well-known identifier of the Southern dialect.  Though often ridiculed in popular culture, it is quite useful in ordinary speech: it represents the second-person plural (equivalent to "vosotros" in Spanish, "vous" in French, or "ihr" in German). It is used frequently in casual conversation, but is usually excluded from formal speech.  Though you might hear the word frequently, it is best to be careful if you attempt using it when visiting as you may appear mildly condescending toward the locals.    It is generally considered very rude to joke about the dialect unless you are from the area.  There is a perception among people from the area that people from other regions look down on them as unintelligent and the southern drawl is sometimes held symbolic of this.  In general, they are very proud of their accent and appreciate when it is spoken of positively.</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">64812</field>
		<field name="title">Virginia</field>
		<field name="main">talk</field>
		<field name="name">talk</field>
		<field name="content">English is spoken by most residents. In rural areas and farther south, you may experience what is commonly known as “Southern accent”. This accent generally does not stop fluent English speakers from understanding the person, but non-native English speakers may experience problems. Most people can deliberately speak in non-accented English upon request but find it difficult to do so for extended length of time. As with all places, locals may have nonstandard words to refer to places, actions and people. Locals are understanding of tourists who do not know these words and will clarify upon request.</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">64813</field>
		<field name="title">Tuolumne County</field>
		<field name="main">talk</field>
		<field name="name">talk</field>
		<field name="content">Communication in Tuolumne County is pretty much exclusively English.  It is fortunate that the many European tourists passing through on their way to Yosemite have good English skills.  Tuolumne County historically had a significant Mexican and Chinese population, but there are relatively few such people here today. People of other races or ethnic backgrounds should have no hesitation in visiting Tuolumne County.  Some may be embarassed by living in such a nearly white-only environment that they are extremely friendly and welcoming to visitors of other races and backgrounds. People of color, especially Mexicans, living in Tuolumne County find prejudice still rampant. The only significant minority in the county are Native Americans, mostly members of the Tuolumne Band of Mi-Wuk Indians.  The whites and Indians have worked at maintaining a good relationship.  When a state highway project uncovered what appeared to be Indian burial grounds, a member of the County Board of Supervisors asked the state to immediately halt the project, saying that he was not at all interested in disturbing any sacred Indian burial grounds.  (The project was eventually completed, with everyone happy.)</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">64814</field>
		<field name="title">Finger Lakes</field>
		<field name="main">talk</field>
		<field name="name">talk</field>
		<field name="content">English is universal in this region, with the dialect resembling that of the  Midwest  more than  New York City  or  New England .  Small pockets of German-speakers, mostly the older generation, can still be found.  Place names are heavily influenced by Iroquois languages; some are veritable tongue-twisters.  Give pronunciation your best shot and youll get a friendly correction, if needed.</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">64815</field>
		<field name="title">New York (state)</field>
		<field name="main">talk</field>
		<field name="name">talk</field>
		<field name="content">English is spoken throughout the state, as expected.  Other languages can be found with varying degrees of regularity in scattered pockets across the state, particularly German, Italian, and Polish.  French is sometimes heard in the North Country, due to proximity to Canada, and Spanish is common wherever Hispanics live.</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">64816</field>
		<field name="title">Los Angeles</field>
		<field name="main">talk</field>
		<field name="name">talk</field>
		<field name="content">As an American city, Los Angeless dominant language is English. However, like much of the rest of California and any American state that borders Mexico, Spanish is also widely spoken. Even Los Angeles name is a Spanish phrase meaning "The Angels." The city has one of the largest Spanish speaking populations in the world, with many business store signs and billboards in some parts of the city printed in both English and Spanish.  According to the U.S. Census, roughly 70% of the citys population speaks English either as their first or second language, and roughly 44% speak Spanish as a first or second language. With a large immigrant population, many other languages are widely spoken such as Armenian, Chinese, Japanese, Tagalog, Russian, Vietnamese, and Farsi.</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">64817</field>
		<field name="title">New Hampshire</field>
		<field name="main">talk</field>
		<field name="name">talk</field>
		<field name="content">Not a big surprise, but the main language is English.  Because of the immigration of French Canadians, some French speakers can be found in the northern part of the state, especially in the Berlin area.  The southern regions have a growing Spanish speaking population, especially Manchester and Nashua, but it is a small percentage when compared to larger US cities</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">64818</field>
		<field name="title">Mississippi Delta</field>
		<field name="main">talk</field>
		<field name="name">talk</field>
		<field name="content">The Delta accent is about as thick as an American accent gets. If youre from another country, good luck!</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">64819</field>
		<field name="title">Ozarks</field>
		<field name="main">talk</field>
		<field name="name">talk</field>
		<field name="content">The people of the Ozarks have their own way of talking and a set of terms that you might not hear outside the region. For example some of the common terms are; "Frog Strangler" or "Gully Warsher" both of which mean a heavy rain. You might hear some way say "You look mighty peakid, are you a-fixen to be sick?" Others are "Rosanears" is corn on the cob, "yourn" is yours "Is that yourn?", a "krick" is a creek, "pritnear" is almost like ""Im pritnear done with this". The hill people of the Ozarks are affectionately called Hillbillies.</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">64820</field>
		<field name="title">San Juan Islands</field>
		<field name="main">talk</field>
		<field name="name">talk</field>
		<field name="content">Almost all Americans speak English. Most people in Washington speak English with a Pacific Northwest accent. This accent is considered very similar to general American standard accent (native to the Midwest), popularized in the 20th century by radio, TV and movies. Washingtonians generally have little to no problem understanding different accents of the English language.   Americans often admire foreign accents and most will approximate the standard accent to help you understand them, or try to speak your language if they can.  The San Juan Islands attract tourists from around the world and it is common to hear many foreign languages being spoken in public in major tourist areas.  Even so, visitors are generally expected to speak and understand English. While many Americans study a foreign language in school (usually Spanish, French or German), few achieve or retain fluency into adulthood. The end result is that many Americans know only a few words at best of a foreign language, even if they studied that language in school. A growing number of popular tourist sites have signs in other languages, but only English is certain to be available at any given location.  Many of the Islands names come from early Spanish explorers or in the case of  Lummi Island s name which comes from the Native American Tribe in that area.</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">64821</field>
		<field name="title">North America</field>
		<field name="main">talk</field>
		<field name="name">talk</field>
		<field name="content">The three major languages of North America are English, Spanish and French.  The United States and the majority of Canada are majority English speaking countries and is by far the best language for getting around these vast countries. English is also spoken in many Caribbean nations and the small country of Belize. Mexico and the majority of Central America and portions of the Caribbean are majority Spanish speaking, making it an important North American language as well. Spanish is spoken as a second language in many parts of the United States. French plays a substantial role in Canada, (including Quebec, Ontario, Manitoba, and New Brunswick), and a role in other places, namely the Caribbean. Dutch is spoken in the southern Caribbean. Several indigenous languages are spoken by Native Americans and the Inuit peoples of North America including Greenland. Danish is also spoken in Greenland. Other important immigrant languages spoken in many ethnic neighborhoods of North America are Cantonese and Mandarin and Tagalog. German is still spoken in some rural communities in United States and Canada.</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">64822</field>
		<field name="title">North Coast (California)</field>
		<field name="main">talk</field>
		<field name="name">talk</field>
		<field name="content">English is widely spoken and understood. Spanish is a minority language but not spoken as much as in the rest of the state.</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">64823</field>
		<field name="title">Twin Falls</field>
		<field name="main">talk</field>
		<field name="name">talk</field>
		<field name="content">Although English is the undoubtedly the primary language in Twin Falls, a significant Hispanic community as well as refugees brought in by the local community college give the city an added multicultural element. It is not at all unusual to hear Spanish, Bosnian and Russian - among other languages - spoken in the city. That said, dont expect too much linguistic diversity; as in the rest of Idaho, English is still by far your best bet with Spanish a distant second.</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">64824</field>
		<field name="title">Missouri</field>
		<field name="main">talk</field>
		<field name="name">talk</field>
		<field name="content">Most areas of Missouri use the traditional Midwestern dialect of English.  In the boot-heel region, mainly from Sikeston south, the accent of the people has a southern drawl to it.    English is the official language of state business in Missouri by law.  A few town pronunciations:   Rolla (Raw-Luh)  Japan (Jay-Pan)  Hayti (Hay-Tie)  Nevada (Nuh-VAY-Duh)  Versailles (Ver-Sales)</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">64825</field>
		<field name="title">Shenandoah Valley</field>
		<field name="main">talk</field>
		<field name="name">talk</field>
		<field name="content">Most residents of the Shenandoah Valley speak only English. There is a local dialect to the valley. It ranges from an Appalachian (apple-ATCH-in) twang to a southern drawl.</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">64826</field>
		<field name="title">Iowa</field>
		<field name="main">talk</field>
		<field name="name">talk</field>
		<field name="content">You should find Midwestern English quite easy to understand.</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">64827</field>
		<field name="title">Rio Grande Valley</field>
		<field name="main">talk</field>
		<field name="name">talk</field>
		<field name="content">The two major languages you will find in The Valley are Spanish and English.  If you are fluent in either of these languages you will get along just fine.  Understand that 80% to 90% of The Valleys population is Mexican American.  Additionally there are large numbers of Mexican visitors in the Valley at all times.  So its not uncommon to meet people whos English is either limited or non-existent.  A knowledge of Spanish is helpful, but not necessary.  You will find that most Valley natives are bilingual and can quickly switch from English to Spanish, sometimes in the same sentence.  Since this is a border area there is a blending of American and Mexican cultures in this region.  Its quite common to encounter people speaking Spanglish.</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">64828</field>
		<field name="title">Northern Arizona</field>
		<field name="main">talk</field>
		<field name="name">talk</field>
		<field name="content">English in the state of Arizona represents a blend of North Midland and South Midland dialects without clear regional differences. Although English is the primary language of Arizona, many primary and secondary Spanish speakers are prevalent due to the states proximity to Mexico. Much of the regional language and place-names are directly influenced by Spanish and the local Native American languages. With the possible exception of the Navajo word hogan (earthand-timber dwelling), the linguistic influence of Arizonas Yuma, Papago(Tohono Oodham), Pima(Akimel Oodham), Hiaki (Yaqui), Apache, Navajo(Dine), and Hopi tribes is strongly limited to place-names, including Arizona itself, Yuma, Havasu, Tucson, and Oraibi.</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">64829</field>
		<field name="title">Ashtabula County</field>
		<field name="main">talk</field>
		<field name="name">talk</field>
		<field name="content">People in Northeast Ohio will usually relate distance by how long it will take to drive somewhere. Cleveland wont be 53 miles west, it will be about an hour west.  Temperature in the winter is measured by windchill usually blowing from Lake Erie. The air temperature may be 30 degrees F, but with windchill 18 degrees F.</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">64830</field>
		<field name="title">Rochester (New York)</field>
		<field name="main">talk</field>
		<field name="name">talk</field>
		<field name="content">Rochester is part of the "Inland North" dialect region of the United States, with only a few minor local variations.  There is, though, one language issue that separates Rochester from the rest of the Finger Lakes region: American Sign Language.  Rochester has one of the highest populations of deaf people (per capita) in the United States, and as such sign language is not an uncommon sight around the city.  Its not a given that youll see ASL being used if you visit Rochestermdash;unless you drop by the Rochester School for the Deaf, or the National Technical Institute for the Deaf at Rochester Institute of Technologymdash;but you never know.  For deaf people, few cities in the world are as accommodating as Rochester.  Most businesses, especially in Henrietta and Brighton, are accustomed to working with deaf customers and often have teletype machines and dedicated TTY phone numbers.  Open-captioned films are regularly shown at the local multiplexes (in particular, at Regal Henrietta), and many major events will be interpreted.  At RIT, nearly all events have both captioning and interpreters.  Wherever the event is held, a quick phone call is often all that is needed to ensure the presence of an interpreter.  If you encounter a deaf person but dont know sign language, do not shout.  You can raise your voice slightly, but its most important to speak clearly and directly, being careful not to hide your mouth with your hand.  If all else fails, find a piece of paper and write back and forth.  If an interpreter is available, be sure to address the deaf person, not the interpreter.  The deaf person will watch the interpreter, but you should be looking at the deaf person and listening to the interpreter.</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">64831</field>
		<field name="title">Crawford County</field>
		<field name="main">talk</field>
		<field name="name">talk</field>
		<field name="content">Crawford County is a real "melting pot of ethnic backgrounds from all over the USA and world, somewhat due to the rail road history in the area. Most speak English, few speak Spanish and fewer other languages. In most cases, you will find the local population having good patience and understanding with non-English speaking visitors. If you need translation, the first place to visit would be a local library, which can be found in all cities and most villages.</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">64832</field>
		<field name="title">San Diego County</field>
		<field name="main">talk</field>
		<field name="name">talk</field>
		<field name="content">Like much of California, English and Spanish are the dominant languages in San Diego County.  Typically, most businesses have at least a few employees that are bilingual in English and Spanish, and some people will be bilingual in English and Tagalog (mostly spoken by San Diegos large Filipino population).  It is also common to see store signs printed in both English and Spanish, especially in neighborhoods with large Hispanic populations.</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">64833</field>
		<field name="title">North Carolina</field>
		<field name="main">talk</field>
		<field name="name">talk</field>
		<field name="content">English, the states official language, is almost universally spoken.   The Southern dialect is commonly found in North Carolina and is usually easily understood by most people.  Being in the Northern South or "Upper South" the dialect of North Carolina is somewhat different than the stereotypical southern accent, which is often more of the dialect found in the "Deep South". The standard dialect in most parts of the state, especially in the Piedmont and Eastern parts of the state borrows from the Virginia Piedmont accent, which is derived from the Virginia Tobacco Planters of the colonial era. The difference may be trivial to the untrained ear, but in some people with thicker accents it may sound a bit strange at first with some words sounding more British than in other parts of the South. The Southern dialect varies within the state, though, with the mountainous western portions having a dialect shared with most areas of the Appalachian Mountains in the South. Due to years of isolation, some residents of parts of the  Outer Banks  speak in a distinct "brogue" that in many cases sounds more like British English and Irish than any American dialect. This brogue can be difficult to understand at first, but not impossible to comprehend.  Spanish is spoken by a sizable minority population in some areas, and as a second-language throughout the state.  Cherokee is spoken by 15,000 to 20,000 people in western North Carolina, along with a number of other Native American languages.  In the cities of Charlotte and Raleigh you will also find a wide variety of languages spoken due to these cities high immigrant populations.</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">64834</field>
		<field name="title">Punxsutawney</field>
		<field name="main">talk</field>
		<field name="name">talk</field>
		<field name="content">Time to brush up on your Pittsburghese   !  Rest assured, the Groundhog Day Ceremonies will be conducted in English, though likely in an accented, regional dialect.  Punxsutawney, known as Punxy to the locals, is situated in Western Pennsylvania, where the majority of residents speak American English with a Pittsburgh regional accent.</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">64835</field>
		<field name="title">Central Florida</field>
		<field name="main">talk</field>
		<field name="name">talk</field>
		<field name="content">English is the official language of the state. However, the  Spanish language  is making inroads throughout the state. Native-born Floridians will usually speak in a southern accent. However, after the migration of millions of Americans from other states to Florida, the southern dialect is becoming diluted with other accents.</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">64836</field>
		<field name="title">Lancaster County</field>
		<field name="main">talk</field>
		<field name="name">talk</field>
		<field name="content">Amish have some of their own vocabulary, related to German (Pennsylvania Deutsch). Non-Amish Americans are called "English".</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">64837</field>
		<field name="title">Vermont</field>
		<field name="main">talk</field>
		<field name="name">talk</field>
		<field name="content">The Vermont dialect uses broad “a” and “e” sounds for vowels. Also, words that end with “r” get an “uh” sound, and one-syllable words are turned into two syllables. Here are some examples of Vermont speak: that is “tha-at”, there would sound like “they-uh” and idea is “oi-dea”. If you are not a native Vermonter, you will likely be called a “flatlander”.  Visitors to Vermont may also be called a "white plater," a reference to the states green license plates compared with the white license plates of surrounding states.  Native Vermonters are also known as "woodchucks." In most of the state, its unlikely you will come across someone with a strong Vermont accent except for seniors, but it is still possible in the Northeast Kingdom.</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">64838</field>
		<field name="title">Texas</field>
		<field name="main">talk</field>
		<field name="name">talk</field>
		<field name="content">Texas has no official language.  However, as with the rest of the United States, English is the predominant language of the state.  Spanish is also widely spoken by approximately one-third of the population.  (Dont assume that all people of Mexican origin speak Spanish; some families have been in Texas for longer than Texas has been part of the U.S.) Texas also has small numbers of Chinese, Tagalog, and Vietnamese speakers as well.  Dont assume that the majority of people are going to have a "Texan" accent.  While you will run into many that do, the majority of Texans, especially in the cities, lack the "Texan twang" one associates with the states residents.</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">64839</field>
		<field name="title">Buffalo</field>
		<field name="main">talk</field>
		<field name="name">talk</field>
		<field name="content">English is spoken in Buffalo and the surrounding area on a virtually universal basis. Though the West Side is well-known as the home of the citys Hispanic community (mainly Puerto Ricans and Dominicans), the majority of Buffalos Latinos are able to speak English as well as Spanish. Also on the West Side, there is a diverse collection of communities of first-generation immigrants centered around the Grant-Ferry neighborhood, most of whom speak some degree of English in addition to their native languages (Arabic, Vietnamese, Burmese and Taiwanese are prominent). In any event, visitors to the West Side will have no significant issues with regard to language.  Those who venture into  Canada  will note that, despite that countrys officially bilingual status, the only place the French language is usually encountered in the parts of Canada near Buffalo is on official signs and documents at the border crossings. Though Buffalos neighborhoods include many vibrant ethnic enclaves, very few residents of these districts (other than perhaps a few elderly individuals) can speak more than a word or phrase or two of their respective ancestral languages.  The regional dialect of English spoken in Buffalo—especially among Italians and Poles of the working class—falls within the framework of  Inland Northern American English , with the hard, nasally, slightly pinched-nose vowel sound in words like "car" and "stop" and the defricativization of the hard "th" sound (whereby "this" and "that" become "dis" and "dat") that will be instantly familiar to those who remember the recurring Saturday Night Live sketch, "Bill Swerskis Superfans". Nonetheless, Buffalos twist on the Inland Northern American dialect involves some unique features such as the devoicing of voiced word-final plosives ("cold" becomes "colt", "rug" becomes "ruck"), and a habit of ending sentences with the word "there" (pronounced "dare") in much the same way Canadians use "eh?"—two speech patterns that are notoriously prevalent among Buffalos Polish community.   For a somewhat outdated but quite accurate description of the particular phonetics and vocabulary of the area, see  The Guide to Buffalo English .</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">64840</field>
		<field name="title">Nevada</field>
		<field name="main">talk</field>
		<field name="name">talk</field>
		<field name="content">English is the official language of Nevada.  Spanish is also widely spoken in Nevada, and like much of the southwest Nevada is heavily influenced by the language, Hispanic culture, and history under Spanish and Mexican rule.  Tagalog is also spoken among Filipino populations.</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">64841</field>
		<field name="title">North Shore (Minnesota)</field>
		<field name="main">talk</field>
		<field name="name">talk</field>
		<field name="content">Lake Superior is one of the worlds largest inland lakes.  While it is located in the middle of the United States, the lake is accesible to the Atlantic ocean.  As a result, cargo ships from around the world can be seen on Lake Superior carrying wheat, iron ore, and other cargo.</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">64842</field>
		<field name="title">Washington (state)</field>
		<field name="main">talk</field>
		<field name="name">talk</field>
		<field name="content">The Pacific Northwest accent spoken in Washington State is considered very similar to the General American standard accent (native to the Midwest), popularized in the 20th century by radio, TV and movies. People in the area generally have little to no problem understanding different accents of the English language. The Pacific Northwest attracts tourists from around the world, and it is common to hear many foreign languages being spoken in public in major tourist areas.   There are ethnically diverse neighborhoods in some of the larger cities where many languages are spoken, including Seattles large International District where many Asian languages are spoken.  Washington is the thirteenth most populated state for example, but by comparison has the fourth highest Asian population.  Spanish is spoken by the majority in some smaller pockets in eastern Washington and Oregon.  Seattles 98118 zip code centered around the Columbia City neighborhood in South Seattle is considered the most ethnically diverse zip code in the country by the US Census bureau with 59 different languages regularly being spoken.  Chinook Jargon was a pidgin or trade language established among indigenous inhabitants of the region. After contact with Europeans, French, English, and Cree words entered the language, and "eventually Chinook became the lingua franca for as many as 250,000 people along the Pacific Slope from Alaska to Oregon." Chinook Jargon reached its height of usage in the 19th century though remained common in resource and wilderness areas, particularly but not exclusively by Native Americans and Canadian First Nations people, well into the 20th century.  Chinook Jargon was still in use in Seattle until roughly the eve of World War II, making Seattle the last city where the language was widely used. Today its influence is felt mostly in place names and a handful of localized slang terms.  Pronunciation of some of these terms is difficult and often separates the visitor from the local.  Many of the area names from Native American culture and may be difficult for outsiders to pronounce including Alki, Seattle, Kitsap, Yakima, Duwamish and Lummi.  While still other areas were named by early Spanish and English explorers.</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">64843</field>
		<field name="title">Arctic Alaska</field>
		<field name="main">talk</field>
		<field name="name">talk</field>
		<field name="content">Native Inuit languages are spoken in many small towns. However, English is the primary language, spoken by most Inuits except perhaps most elderly. There are only a handful of persons fluent in any other languages.</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">64844</field>
		<field name="title">Kansas</field>
		<field name="main">talk</field>
		<field name="name">talk</field>
		<field name="content">Most residents of Kansas speak a neutral American Standard English. However, in the southeastern region there is a faint southern influence – both in accent and word choice. This dates back to Civil War era, many pro-slavery citizens moved into this part of the state to land grab and sway elections. Many of the communities in the area still have connections to southwest Missouri and northeast Arkansas communities.  The farther west you go you may run into pockets of communities with German, Russian, or even Swedish accents. This due to the large number of immigrants that settled in Kansas during the late 1800s</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">64845</field>
		<field name="title">Oakland County</field>
		<field name="main">talk</field>
		<field name="name">talk</field>
		<field name="content">English is the predominant language in and around Oakland county, and there are no strange dialects unique to this area.</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">64846</field>
		<field name="title">South Central Arizona</field>
		<field name="main">talk</field>
		<field name="name">talk</field>
		<field name="content">English is the primary language although Spanish is widely understood and spoken, with many residents being bilingual.</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">64847</field>
		<field name="title">South Carolina</field>
		<field name="main">talk</field>
		<field name="name">talk</field>
		<field name="content">English is official.  Gullah is spoken on the Sea Islands.</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">64848</field>
		<field name="title">Sangre de Cristo Mountains</field>
		<field name="main">talk</field>
		<field name="name">talk</field>
		<field name="content">English really is the usual language in this area, despite rumors to the contrary.  However, its not necessarily an inhabitants first language.  Many residents speak Spanish not just at home but in public, in a dialect that has significant ties to seventeenth-century Spain as well as a number of distinctive regional quirks.  The Spanish-speaking visitor may find it interesting to listen and learn, but no knowledge of Spanish is required to get around.</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">64849</field>
		<field name="title">Alabama</field>
		<field name="main">talk</field>
		<field name="name">talk</field>
		<field name="content">Many (though certainly not all) Alabamians speak with thick local accents so non-native English speakers may have difficulty understanding them. Within the two major urban areas of Huntsville and Birmingham one will find that most accents are of a General American variety while in the other two major urban areas of Mobile and Montgomery local accents are still widely prevalent. Visitors to North Alabama (Birmingham and north) will experience accents that are more "country" in nature (Senator Richard Shelby is one example) while visitors to South Alabama (south of Birmingham) will experience accents that are more closely reminiscent of those from the 1939 film Gone With the Wind and the 1994 film Forrest Gump, which takes place in Southern Alabama. Former governor Fob James is a textbook example of a southern Alabama accent.</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">64850</field>
		<field name="title">Buncombe County</field>
		<field name="main">talk</field>
		<field name="name">talk</field>
		<field name="content">English will be more than enough. Be sure to speak in the native dialect. Crick means creek, polecat is skunk, sniffing apple butter means engaging in unprotected anal sex.</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">64851</field>
		<field name="title">Orange County (California)</field>
		<field name="main">talk</field>
		<field name="name">talk</field>
		<field name="content">English and Spanish are the two most common languages spoken in Orange County. Most government agencies will have someone available who speaks Spanish.  In North Orange County, many businesses will have someone who speaks Spanish on staff; however the further south one travels, Spanish speaking staff can be less common, though someone nearby who speaks Spanish is likely and will usually help translate if asked.  Because of the ethnic diversity of Southern California, there are many neighborhoods where other languages are dominant, mostly from Asian countries.   The third most-spoken language, Vietnamese, is widely spoken in Westminster and Garden Grove, and to a lesser extent, in Fountain Valley and Santa Ana. In Garden Grove and Fullerton, Korean is widely spoken.  Japanese is more commonly spoken in Costa Mesa.</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">64852</field>
		<field name="title">Maui</field>
		<field name="main">talk</field>
		<field name="name">talk</field>
		<field name="content">See  Talk  in the  Hawaii  section.</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">64853</field>
		<field name="title">Inland Empire</field>
		<field name="main">talk</field>
		<field name="name">talk</field>
		<field name="content">Like the rest of California and the nation, English is the main language spoken. But like many American regions that border Mexico, Spanish is widely spoken by some residents as well as some employees at restaurants, stores, and businesses. That being said, there are certainly many parts of the region where knowing some basic Spanish will go a long way in helping you receive better service at restaurants and businesses. Some residents, however, advocate the opposite, feeling that those who speak only Spanish can give and receive better service by learning some basic English.  The Inland Empire is highly populated, containing 4.2 million residents. However, the area isnt as totally self-sufficient in the regard that many residents still commute to their jobs in the adjacent Los Angeles metropolitan area of Los Angeles and Orange counties. Inland Empire residents also tend to travel to Los Angeles and its immediate environs for activities such as zoos, aquariums, theme parks, planetariums, higher-rated museums, and such. This isnt to say the Inland Empire is without its own attractions as its has some good theatres, nearby mountains, lakes, and enjoyable restaurants and malls. But it does show that the Inland Empire is not just a stand alone metropolitan area, but also an integrated part of the Greater Los Angeles area.</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">64854</field>
		<field name="title">Front Range</field>
		<field name="main">talk</field>
		<field name="name">talk</field>
		<field name="content">English, although you may find all manner of languages spoken at the ski resorts.  Interpretive materials in several other languages are available at Rocky Mountain National Park.</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">64855</field>
		<field name="title">Four Corners</field>
		<field name="main">talk</field>
		<field name="name">talk</field>
		<field name="content">You may run into the occasional Native American who speaks only Navajo, but this should not present an insurmountable language barrier. The vast majority of the vendors speak English.</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">64856</field>
		<field name="title">Erie Region</field>
		<field name="main">talk</field>
		<field name="name">talk</field>
		<field name="content">Great Lakes dialect has a strong presence in northwestern Pennsylvania. One would be hard-pressed to distinguish between those who live in western upstate New York (Rochester, Buffalo) and those who live in Erie. Many Os become As ("mam" instead of "mom," for example).</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">64857</field>
		<field name="title">Providence County</field>
		<field name="main">talk</field>
		<field name="name">talk</field>
		<field name="content">The Blackstone Valley becomes a place where history and culture are embraced in each city. The resources of the valley are sufficient enough to provide a high level quality of life for residents all over the its cities. It is inspiring to know how communities had built around the valley between the 18th and 19th century. So take advantage of being in New England and grasp the history and culture by visiting Blackstone valley.You can discover the beauty of its nature by visiting the Blackstone Valley Scenic Railway Tours or Samuel Slater Canal Boat.Think about preparing your family for fun day at Slater Park in Pawtucket. It has all kinds of different activities.</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">64858</field>
		<field name="title">Pennsylvania</field>
		<field name="main">talk</field>
		<field name="name">talk</field>
		<field name="content">Most Pennsylvanians speak American English, although many subtle regional accents and dialects do exist. There are large Latino, Spanish-speaking populations in Reading, Allentown, and Philadelphia, and Philadelphia and Pittsburgh have their share of Asian, European, and other languages. There will be no problem communicating with people who live in Pennsylvania, except, of course, if they resort to the famous Pennsylvania Dutch "Pennsilfaanisch Deitsch" dialect of German. Although widescale non-Amish use of the language faded circa 1950, there are pockets of young people who are learning the language as a way to preserve their heritage.  The Pittsburgh area and the anthracite coal region of northeast Pennsylvania are known for their colorful regional accents.</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">64859</field>
		<field name="title">New England</field>
		<field name="main">talk</field>
		<field name="name">talk</field>
		<field name="content">English is, as with the rest of the US, the de facto official language. Some areas with large Hispanic populations might have a majority speaking Spanish, but most have at least basic English skills (and these are off the tourist path). French is also spoken in Vermont and Northern Maine, near the Quebec/New Brunswick borders. There is a rich French-Canadian heritage in Biddeford, Maine, and Manchester, New Hampshires largest city. Though the demographics are changing, it is still possible to find shops that cater to French speakers and churches that conduct Mass in French.  In truth, though, not much is done to accommodate visitors who do not speak English.  Along with Southerners, New Englanders have a reputation for a distinct flavor of English speech.  This is an overly broad generalization.  The accents of Senators Kennedy and Kerry are rarely heard.  The typical "pahk the cah in Hahvahd Yahd" Boston accent prevails in eastern  Massachusetts , but is losing ground even there.  There are some distinctive vocabulary words.  "Bubbler" refers to a drinking fountain.  Carbonated sweet drinks called "pop" in other parts of the  United States  and  Canada  are called "tonic" or "soda" in New England.  "Wicked", an adjective interchangeable with "very", is frequently used by young New Englanders, though the once-common phrase "wicked pissah", meaning "excellent", has faded considerably and is used primarily by either the older generation or misled tourists.  A relatively common New England traffic intersection not encountered much elsewhere in the  United States  would be called a "roundabout" in the  United Kingdom , but is called a "rotary" in New England.  When given directions on how to exit a "rotary" the driver would be instructed to "bang a right" in Boston.  Large clams are called "quahaugs" in southern New England.  In  Maine  an inland vacation home is called a "camp" while one on the coast is called a "cottage."  Mainers also add the definite article "the" to the official names of roads, but not streets or avenues; and the tree that others might call an aspen is called a "popple" by Mainers.</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">64860</field>
		<field name="title">Martin County (Florida)</field>
		<field name="main">talk</field>
		<field name="name">talk</field>
		<field name="content">English is spoken everywhere.</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">64861</field>
		<field name="title">Connecticut</field>
		<field name="main">talk</field>
		<field name="name">talk</field>
		<field name="content">New Britain, Connecticut is well known for its large Polish community. Large cities in Connecticut, such as Bridgeport, Hartford, New Haven and Waterbury have significant Hispanic populations.  Bridgeport also has a small Brazilian area. New Havens Chinatown caters to Mandarin speakers, and Wooster St serves as the citys "Little Italy."  Many people in Fairfield County have a New York accent with the countys proximity to New York City, while some people in Northern Connecticut have a Boston accent.</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">64862</field>
		<field name="title">Imperial Beach</field>
		<field name="main">talk</field>
		<field name="name">talk</field>
		<field name="content">English is the dominant language spoken in Imperial Beach and you should have no trouble making it around only speaking this language. Spanish is spoken mostly by the Hispanic residents of the City. Youre likely to hear some Spanish in this City due mostly to its proximity to the United States-Mexico Border.</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">64863</field>
		<field name="title">Imperial County</field>
		<field name="main">talk</field>
		<field name="name">talk</field>
		<field name="content">A large portion of the population is Mexican immigrants, so while English is more common, many transactions take place entirely in Spanish.</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">64864</field>
		<field name="title">Illinois</field>
		<field name="main">talk</field>
		<field name="name">talk</field>
		<field name="content">English is the dominant language in the state of Illinois.  Spanish is widely spoken in the Chicago Metropolitan area by its large Hispanic population, though not well understood outside of  Chicagoland .  Polish and Chinese are the third and fourth most spoken languages within the state, but only within Chicago and its suburbs.</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">64865</field>
		<field name="title">Willamette Valley</field>
		<field name="main">talk</field>
		<field name="name">talk</field>
		<field name="content">Standard American English is the predominant language, but Spanish is not uncommon throughout the Valley due to a growing Hispanic population. Outside of the urban immigrant communities, there is a colony of Russian speakers in the Woodburn-Gervais area in northern Marion County, the Old Believers, who continue a unique religious culture.</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">64866</field>
		<field name="title">New Mexico</field>
		<field name="main">talk</field>
		<field name="name">talk</field>
		<field name="content">New Mexico is very much like the rest of the U.S. in that English is almost universally spoken.  New Mexico Magazine , the states tourist magazines (and a better-than-average read by the standards of such things), carries a regular column called "One of our Fifty Is Missing" that describes the many humorous misconceptions (the polite word) that the state and its residents experience at the hands of those seemingly unaware that New Mexico is part of the United States; linguistic misunderstandings are among the more frequent anecdotes appearing there.  English will do just fine, although particularly in the North Central and Northwest regions, youll have a good chance of running into people for whom English is a second, or even third, language, behind Spanish and/or a tribal language.  Albuquerque, Las Cruces, Los Alamos and Santa Fe all have notably diverse populations that include native speakers of most of the worlds major languages.  Its common (if unexpected, given the towns historic secrecy) to walk into a store or restaurant in Los Alamos and hear a conversation between storekeeper and patron in Russian or Chinese, or even Polish or Korean.  This said, when you encounter an apparently Spanish place name or surname, as you will in almost all parts of the state, its wise to pronounce it as Spanish.  Anglicizing the pronunciation may be acceptable in some parts of the United States, but is likely to be considered rude here.  The Wikivoyage  Spanish phrasebook  can help with this; particular things to be on the alert for are "ñ" (e.g.  Española  and other place names), double "ll" (e.g.  Valles Caldera National Preserve ), and double "rr" (e.g. Rio Arriba County in the North Central region, which incidentally is a particularly good place in which to avoid Anglicized Spanish).</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">64867</field>
		<field name="title">Charleston (South Carolina)</field>
		<field name="main">talk</field>
		<field name="name">talk</field>
		<field name="content">The dialect here varies from standard American English, having a  "Southern Coastal Accent" that contains British influences. For those who learned Standard English, some speech may be difficult to comprehend here. Generally speaking, one can easily get by with Standard American or British English, though. The inhabitants of Charleston are, to a large degree, transient (due to several military installations, port labor, rail labor, and other factors), and therefore many other languages are inherent in a minority role.  A minority dialect spoken here is Gullah, a dialect of English almost incomprehensible to most English Speakers. If you are familiar with "Porgy and Bess", you are familiar with Gullah. Gullah has West-African influences mixed with pidjin French and English. The dialect originated around Johns Island. If you travel south of the city (to the islands, or towards Ravenel), the dialect becomes somewhat more prevalent (although still in a minority context).  Alternate languages include Spanish and Portuguese, brought to the city and its outskirts by its large Latin American population. One may encounter "Spanglish" here, which is an odd combination of Spanish and English.  Place names in and around Charleston are often very Americanized versions of French (Lagare Street, for example, is pronounced luh-GREE) or other languages.</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">64868</field>
		<field name="title">Walworth County</field>
		<field name="main">talk</field>
		<field name="name">talk</field>
		<field name="content">As with most of the  Midwest , English is by far the most common language spoken in the area.  Spanish is an increasingly common language, especially in Walworth and Delavan.</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">64869</field>
		<field name="title">Southern California</field>
		<field name="main">talk</field>
		<field name="name">talk</field>
		<field name="content">English is the official language of California and is the predominant language in Southern California.  However, Spanish is also spoken by large Hispanic populations and it is not uncommon in Southern California to see store and street signs written in both English and Spanish. Armenian, Farsi, Chinese, Tagalog, Japanese, Hindi, Korean, Vietnamese, and Cambodian are also spoken by various immigrant groups.</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">64870</field>
		<field name="title">United States of America</field>
		<field name="main">talk</field>
		<field name="name">talk</field>
		<field name="content">Almost all Americans speak English. They generally use a standard accent (native to the Midwest), popularized in the 20th century by radio, TV and movies. In many areas, especially the South and Texas, in New England, in New York City, and in the upper Midwest, youll find distinctive regional accents and dialects. Nowhere should this pose any problem to a visitor, as Americans often admire foreign accents and most will approximate the standard accent to help you understand them, or try to speak your language if they can.  Even so, visitors are generally expected to speak and understand English. While many Americans study a foreign language in school (usually  Spanish ,  French  or  German ), few achieve or retain fluency into adulthood. The end result is that many Americans know only a few words at best of a foreign language, even if they studied that language in school. A growing number of popular tourist sites have signs in other languages, but only English is certain to be available at any given location.  Due primarily to immigration from Latin America, the United States has the fifth-largest Spanish speaking population in the world. Spanish is the primary second language in many parts of the United States such as California, the Southwest, Texas, Florida, and the metropolitan areas of Chicago and New York City. Many of these areas have Spanish-language radio and television stations, with local, national and Mexican programs.  Spanish is the first language of Puerto Rico and a large minority of residents on the mainland, particularly in the western states. Spanish speakers in the United States are primarily Puerto Ricans, or first- and second-generation immigrants from Latin America. As a result, the Spanish spoken is almost invariably a Latin American or Puerto Rican dialect. Although its rare to be in areas where no one speaks English, a good handle on Spanish can make communication easier in some areas.  French is the primary second language in rural areas near the border with  Quebec , in some areas of Louisiana, and among West African immigrants, but is not widespread elsewhere. In southern Florida, Haitian immigrants primarily speak  Haitian Creole , a separate language derived from French, as their second language, although a substantial number also speak French.  Thanks to the North American Free Trade Agreement, some products now have trilingual packaging in English, Spanish, and French for sale throughout the entire trade bloc, especially household cleaning products and small electric appliances.  However, the vast majority of consumer products are labeled only in English, meaning that a rudimentary grasp of English is essential for shopping.   Hawaiian  is the native language of  Hawaii , although English is the most widely spoken language and  Japanese  is also widely spoken there. In the various Chinatowns in major cities,  Cantonese  and  Mandarin  are common. Smaller immigrant groups also sometimes form their own pockets of shared language, including Russian, Italian, Greek, Arabic, Tagalog, Korean, Vietnamese, and others. Chicago, for instance, is the city with the second largest ethnic Polish population in the world, behind  Warsaw . The Amish, who have lived in Pennsylvania and Ohio for generations, speak a dialect of German.  Some Native Americans speak their respective native languages, especially on reservations in the west. However despite efforts to revive them many Native American languages are endangered, and people who speak them as their first language are few and far between. Navajo speakers in Arizona and New Mexico are an exception to this, but even a clear majority among them speak and understand English too.  Bottom line: unless youre certain youll be in an area populated with recent immigrants, traveling in the United States without a firm grasp of English is a significant challenge.  American Sign Language, or ASL is the dominant sign language in the United States. When events are interpreted, they will be interpreted in ASL. Users of French Sign Language and other related languages may find ASL intelligible, as they share much vocabulary, but users of Japanese Sign Language, British Sign Language, or Auslan will not. Closed-captioning on television is widespread, but far from ubiquitous. Many theaters offer FM loops or other assistive listening devices, but captioning and interpreters are rarer.  For the blind, many signs and displays include Braille transcriptions of the printed English. Larger restaurant chains, museums, and parks may offer Braille menus and guidebooks, but youll likely have to ask for them.</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">64871</field>
		<field name="title">Las Vegas (New Mexico)</field>
		<field name="main">talk</field>
		<field name="name">talk</field>
		<field name="content">Las Vegas, NM is  not to be confused with the far larger and better known major city of the  same name  in  Nevada . Within the confines of the northern New Mexico references to Las Vegas or Vegas are understood to refer to the local community. To avoid being considered rude, refer to the other Las Vegas as Las Vegas, Nevada. As the population is 83% Hispanic, expect to overhear Spanish frequently as many people are bilingual.</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">64872</field>
		<field name="title">San Fernando Valley</field>
		<field name="main">talk</field>
		<field name="name">talk</field>
		<field name="content">The stereotypical "Valley Girl" speak is actually prevelant among most teenage girls influenced by pop culture all over the USA, and not just limited to the San Fernando Valley. San Fernando Valley residents are diverse with Spanish, Korean, Thai, Armenian, Hebrew, Persian, Russian, Tagalog, Vietnamese, Hindi, and many other languages being common besides English.</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">64873</field>
		<field name="title">Rhode Island</field>
		<field name="main">talk</field>
		<field name="name">talk</field>
		<field name="content">Rhode Islanders talk with a distinctly eastern-New-England accent, similar to Bostons famous broad a and dropped r. Natives also have a habit of adding r to the end of a word. For example, some people may say idear instead of idea. Some words you might hear while visiting: "bubbler" (water fountain), "grinder" (submarine sandwich), and "cabinet" (milkshake).    Rhode Islanders will affectionately complain that if they have to drive anywhere and it takes longer than a half hour, then it is too far.   Natives also have names for certain landmarks, sometimes with a historical aspect with it.  For instance, the Henderson Bridge, which is a mini-freeway/bridge in the Providence area, is affectionately known as the "little red bridge" because before the present bridge was built, a red wooden bridge stood there.  Central Falls and East Providence will be known, especially in newspapers, as CF and EP respectively.  Barrington will sometimes be called Borington because there are no liquor stores there (it is prohibited by a town ordinance).  Rhode Islands local pastime is politics, which can get very emotional here.  Rhode Island has the only surviving parliamentary democracy in the US.  Combine that with an "everybody knows everybody" state of mind and youve got Rhode Island politics in a nutshell.</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">64874</field>
		<field name="title">California</field>
		<field name="main">talk</field>
		<field name="name">talk</field>
		<field name="content">The California Constitution states that English is the official language of the state of California, but in reality, this rule is treated as a floor rather than a ceiling, and one should regard California as a multilingual state.  American English is the main language and Spanish is the de facto second language, and a knowledge of even rudimentary Spanish is useful in most cities from Sacramento to San Diego. Los Angeles has some of the largest Hispanic populations north of Mexico.  The state is highly influenced by Spanish culture, as California was one part of the Spanish empire until 1821, and then to Mexico for a short while after until ceded to the USA in 1848. In fact, some of its residents declared it an independent country for about a month (The Bear Flag Republic) in the midst of the Mexican-American War 1846-1848,  and many of Californias cities were named after saints or phrases in Spanish (such as  Los Angeles ,  San Diego ,  San Francisco ,  Sacramento , and  San Jose ).  Store and street signs are sometimes written in both English and Spanish in major metropolitan areas, and "Spanglish" (a mixture of English and Spanish) is often used and heard throughout the state.  Most businesses in California have at least a few employees that are bilingual in English and Spanish.  Chinese is also spoken throughout California, and areas with a large number of Chinese residents or businesses have Chinese signage. Japanese, Tagalog, Korean, Vietnamese, Hindi, Punjabi, and Khmer are also spoken among Asian Californian populations.</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">64875</field>
		<field name="title">Volusia County</field>
		<field name="main">talk</field>
		<field name="name">talk</field>
		<field name="content">English is the official language of the state. However, the  Spanish language  is making inroads throughout the state.   Native-born Floridians will usually speak in a southern accent. However, after the migration of millions of Americans from other states to Florida, the southern dialect is becoming diluted with other American-English accents.</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">64876</field>
		<field name="title">San Angelo</field>
		<field name="main">talk</field>
		<field name="name">talk</field>
		<field name="content">English is the dominant language spoken here and with Spanish growing more. While many people may have a stereotypical Texas or "country" accent, many others do not, and that includes military members and locals.</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">64877</field>
		<field name="title">Green County</field>
		<field name="main">talk</field>
		<field name="name">talk</field>
		<field name="content">The vast majority of the County speaks English as a primary language.  The Midwestern accent is by far the most common accent in the County and within southwest Wisconsin.  Some families may still speak German, though they would be bilingual.</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">64878</field>
		<field name="title">Upper Peninsula</field>
		<field name="main">talk</field>
		<field name="name">talk</field>
		<field name="content">"Say ya to da UP, eh?"  This is the UPs answer to the state tourism offices slogan "Say Yes to Michigan!"  Yoopers (inhabitants of Upper Michigan) have an accent with a Canada-meets-the-Midwest flavor.  "Ya" and "eh" are the most well-known of the colloquial slang.  Youll hear "Eh" (ay) appended to statements, as a rhetorical stand-in for "Isnt It?", in a manner very similar to that of Canadians in Ontario and elsewhere.  In Finnish, the expression of "ey" means "no" in much the same sense as the English appendage "isnt it?" or the general-purpose French "nest-ce pas?"  Dont exaggerate the ay sound when saying "Eh" yourself, or youll be tagged instantly as a visitor.   In the middle and western U.P., the accent is a blend of Scandinavian (particularly Finnish), French, and Canadian influences. Youll hear more substitution of d for t and th.  Also, some Yoopers tend to drop their prepositions; the Finnish language doesnt use them.  So, to ask if we are going to  Green Bay , Wisconsin, for example, it is rendered in the vernacular as "We go Green Bay, eh?"  This speech pattern is becoming less frequent, as speaking Finnish at home becomes less and less common.  Many of the town names have a wonderfully Native American lilt to them, such as Escanaba (ES kuh NAH bah), Ishpeming (ISH peh ming), or Ontonagon (ON tuh NAH gun).   Youll also see many French place names: Marquette, (mar KET), Epofuette, Au Train, LAnse (lAHNS), Sault Ste. Marie, (soo saynt muhREE) or Manistique (man ihs TEEK).</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">64879</field>
		<field name="title">Metro Detroit</field>
		<field name="main">talk</field>
		<field name="name">talk</field>
		<field name="content">English is the major language spoken in Metro Detroit. However, there are business travelers and residents in the metro area from all over the world so residents and businesses are accustomed to communicating with those who have difficulty speaking English.</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">64880</field>
		<field name="title">Antelope Valley</field>
		<field name="main">talk</field>
		<field name="name">talk</field>
		<field name="content">English is the dominant language; in some neighborhoods Spanish is spoken but an English speaker is usually easy to find there.</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">64881</field>
		<field name="title">El Paso</field>
		<field name="main">talk</field>
		<field name="name">talk</field>
		<field name="content">El Paso is a diverse community featuring many different kinds of people. The largest language spoken at home is Spanish, followed by English. Many older El Pasoans speak Spanish regularly in public and it is helpful, although usually not necessary, to understand the language.</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">64882</field>
		<field name="title">Southeast Arizona</field>
		<field name="main">talk</field>
		<field name="name">talk</field>
		<field name="content">English is the primary language spoken here, although Spanish is widely understood and spoken, particularly along the Mexican border.</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">64883</field>
		<field name="title">Utah</field>
		<field name="main">talk</field>
		<field name="name">talk</field>
		<field name="content">English. On top of the Latino population that speaks Spanish, there are a surprising number of non-native Spanish speakers, especially in Salt Lake City and Provo, since the LDS church actively proselytizes in Latin America. "No hablo inglés" doesnt work anymore when these guys knock at your door.  The universities also have a large number of foreign speakers, particularly Chinese.</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">64884</field>
		<field name="title">Mecklenburg County (North Carolina)</field>
		<field name="main">talk</field>
		<field name="name">talk</field>
		<field name="content">The dominant language is English, although some  Spanish  would not hurt. Charlotte also has a high  Vietnamese  population.</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">64885</field>
		<field name="title">Louisiana</field>
		<field name="main">talk</field>
		<field name="name">talk</field>
		<field name="content">While both English and  French  are the two de facto official languages of the state, English is the more dominant language. Parts of the south of the state and New Orleans have a long French-speaking history; however, in the early 20th century, French was discouraged by the state school system in favor of English. Today, English is spoken by nearly all; however, it is not uncommon to hear conversations in French in the southern and rural parts of the state, and a small number of elderly people in those parts of the state can speak French only.  In honor of the states French heritage, local street signs in the French Quarter of New Orleans and many downtowns of cities in the Acadiana region are bilingual in French and English, with French being more visibly prominent in the latter. However, locals will often refer to a street by its English name rather than French name. As of 2013, the Louisiana legislature has also approved of a bill requiring highway signs to be bilingual in both French and English.  Unlike northern and central Louisiana, the Southern "drawl" is very rare in the southern part of the state.  The native English accent in Acadiana has many distinct sounds due to the peoples collective French heritage. In addition, the accent of New Orleans is similar to that of  Brooklyn .</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">64886</field>
		<field name="title">Arkansas</field>
		<field name="main">talk</field>
		<field name="name">talk</field>
		<field name="content">English is the prevalent language in virtually the entire state - although Spanish has become much more apparent in Northwestern Arkansas in recent years. Many rural (and quite a few urban) Arkansans have distinctive dialects, which is generally a source of pride. Speakers of English as a second language may face difficulty with some speakers - and relatively few Arkansans are truly bilingual, and menus, signs, and other information is rarely presented in a language other than English.</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">64887</field>
		<field name="title">Nassau County</field>
		<field name="main">talk</field>
		<field name="name">talk</field>
		<field name="content">English is the main language. Hempstead, Uniondale, New Cassel, Westbury and Freeport have large Spanish-speaking populations.</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">64888</field>
		<field name="title">Antioch (California)</field>
		<field name="main">talk</field>
		<field name="name">talk</field>
		<field name="content">English is the dominant language spoken here and with Spanish growing more. There is no accent to say of just normal English is spoken here</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">64889</field>
		<field name="title">Smith Island</field>
		<field name="main">talk</field>
		<field name="name">talk</field>
		<field name="content">The most notable feature of the island is the local dialect which is like the dialect of the West Country of England. The dialect contains some relict features indicative of its origins but is not, as is often claimed, a surviving pocket of Shakespearean era English. This dialect is like the Ocracoke Brogue, sometimes referred to as the Outer Banks Brogue off the coast of  North Carolina .  Because of recent exposure to the neighboring  Eastern Shore (Maryland) , the dialect has become more southern in sound, than its other isolated neighbor,  Tangier Island .</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">64890</field>
		<field name="title">San Diego</field>
		<field name="main">talk</field>
		<field name="name">talk</field>
		<field name="content">Like much of California and the Southwestern United States, English is the predominant language with Spanish the second most widely spoken. Store signs are written in English or both languages, and many businesses have bilingual employees that speak both English and Spanish.</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">64891</field>
		<field name="title">Tennessee</field>
		<field name="main">talk</field>
		<field name="name">talk</field>
		<field name="content">Many native Tennesseans speak in the dialect of the American South.  This dialect changes slightly as you cross through each region, and will be especially pronounced in rural areas   Generally speaking, it is accepted that people in the South speak more slowly, and carefully than those from the North. In particular, visitors from larger cities will have to adjust to the different pace of speech if they visit Tennessees smaller mountain towns; speaking quickly and bluntly can be perceived as inconsiderate and may gather a negative response.  Some Tennesseans in especially rural or mountainous areas may be difficult to understand by those not familiar with American South or Appalachian colloquialisms, slurring or speech cadence.</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">64892</field>
		<field name="title">Highlands (Maine)</field>
		<field name="main">talk</field>
		<field name="name">talk</field>
		<field name="content">Everyone that isnt from Maine talks real funny.</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">64893</field>
		<field name="title">New Jersey</field>
		<field name="main">talk</field>
		<field name="name">talk</field>
		<field name="content">People flock to New Jersey from all over, especially from New York City and Philadelphia, making it difficult to isolate the New Jersey accent. North Jerseys accent is strongly influenced by New York, and South Jerseys accent is strongly influenced by Philadelphia. The true New Jersey accent is evident in native speakers like politician-turned-broadcaster Steve Adubato, United States Supreme Court Justice Samuel Alito, and Louis Freeh, the former director of the Federal Bureau of Investigation.</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">64894</field>
		<field name="title">Arizona</field>
		<field name="main">talk</field>
		<field name="name">talk</field>
		<field name="content">As with all states in the U.S., the primary spoken language in Arizona is English.  However, due to the states history and its proximity to Mexico, Arizona is home to a large population of Mexican-Americans as well as populations from several other Hispanic countries who typically speak the Spanish language (with some Hispanic cultures using a country-specific dialect) in addition to English.  Most of the 22 Native American Tribes also have their own distinct language, however it is usually spoken between tribal members.</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">64895</field>
		<field name="title">Houston</field>
		<field name="main">talk</field>
		<field name="name">talk</field>
		<field name="content">Houston is home to more than 100 languages. Signs can be found in Spanish, Vietnamese and Chinese, among others, but English is the lingua franca. Knowing some Spanish may help in certain neighborhoods, but most people will speak English.</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">64896</field>
		<field name="title">West Virginia</field>
		<field name="main">talk</field>
		<field name="name">talk</field>
		<field name="content">Given its position as a boundary state between the North and the South, your perception of the West Virginia dialect will probably depend on where youre from. People from the North think that West Virginians have a Southern accent, whereas people from the South perceive them as speaking a more Northern dialect. Nevertheless, most West Virginians do have at least a bit of a Southern twang, particularly if you venture into the more remote mountain communities.  There is no single West Virginia dialect. In areas of the state which border Ohio and Pennsylvania, the pronunciations tend to be more northern, with the primary marker being the long "I" sound. Some will voice the diphthong "aye" in the northern style, while others make the "ah" sound. Those in the interior of the state speak in a manner more like people from Kentucky or southern Virginia. In the southern counties particularly, you will find a very pronounced southern twang.  Variations in dialects can be traced to immigration patterns. The coal fields of the southeastern part of the state were the destination of miners immigrating from Ireland, Scotland and Wales. In the more industrialized areas along the Ohio River, the immigrant population was comprised of large numbers of eastern European immigrants.  In the most southern part of the state, there are communities which are almost entirely African-American. During the mine wars of the late 1800s, mine owners hired former slaves from the southern states to replace striking miners. Because these communities tend to be segregated (by choice), the dialects of the southern slaves live on in their speech.</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">64897</field>
		<field name="title">Delaware Valley</field>
		<field name="main">talk</field>
		<field name="name">talk</field>
		<field name="content">Dialect in the Delaware Valley sounds much like its New York City counterpart to the north. Many rs are dropped. In Philadelphia, "water" is pronounced as "wooder" or "whudder." Words like "kawfee" and "hawt" with an exaggerated "o" sound have been borrowed by denizens of the New York City area. "Hoagies" refer to sub sandwiches and "steak" may refer to the cheesesteak sandwich.</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">64898</field>
		<field name="title">Appalachia</field>
		<field name="main">talk</field>
		<field name="name">talk</field>
		<field name="content">Appalachia is English-speaking for a large majority.  The Appalachian English dialect is found through the Southern mountains, known for its many colorful phrases.  Other European and Asian languages can be found in small minority communities.  Native American languages are also spoken in Appalachian Native American communities.  The word "Appalachia" comes from the Apalachee nation.  "Appalachia" is often pronounced "ah-pah-lah-chah" (with a silent "i") by Appalachians (from Apalachee, "ah-pah-lah-chee"), but the pronunciation of "ah-pah-lay-shuh" is also correct.</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">64899</field>
		<field name="title">Union City (New Jersey)</field>
		<field name="main">talk</field>
		<field name="name">talk</field>
		<field name="content">Since most residents in Union City are hispanic, the predominant language spoken is  Spanish , though most Spanish speakers also speak English.  Additionally, there is a Hasidim enclave in uptown Union City.</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">64900</field>
		<field name="title">Panhandle (Nebraska)</field>
		<field name="main">talk</field>
		<field name="name">talk</field>
		<field name="content">There is a small but sizable minority of Hispanic people moving to the area yet not enough for a knowledge of the Spanish language would be required. The Oglala Lakota are a prominent Native American tribe in the region so you may be inclined to know some of their language and customs if you plan on visiting Pine Ridge. Also, at one time there was a large influx of Scandinavian and German immigrants to the region, though extremely uncommon there are still some areas that have elderly speakers of their native tongue.</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">64901</field>
		<field name="title">Walt Disney World</field>
		<field name="main">talk</field>
		<field name="name">talk</field>
		<field name="content">As in most places in the United States, English is the default language throughout the Walt Disney World Resort.  The cast members at World Showcase in Epcot are largely citizens of the featured countries, and so will be fluent in their native tongues as well as English.  Other cast members throughout the property may also be bi- or tri-lingual; any such cast members can be identified by language signs on their name tags, representing the languages they speak . Spanish is also very common in Florida, and the US as a whole. Spanish speakers will not have any problems navigating the resort.  All four theme parks have an information center known as Guest Relations, near the main entrance. Cast members at those locations, who are often multilingual, can answer any questions you may have.  Disneys Ears to the World is an audio headset that provides foreign-language translations of the dialogues of selected attractions in French, German, Japanese, Portuguese, or Spanish.  It may be rented at Guest Relations, but there are a limited number of them available; a $25 deposit will be collected and refunded upon return.  For guests with visual disabilities, linguistic services are in the form of audiocassette tour guides and Braille guidebooks, also available for rent at Guest Relations.   For hearing-impaired guests, assistive listening devices and captioning (handheld, reflective, or video) are available for selected attractions. Cast Members with knowledge of American Sign Language can be identified by the appropriate symbol on their name tags, and interpreters are available by appointment.</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">64902</field>
		<field name="title">Nebraska</field>
		<field name="main">talk</field>
		<field name="name">talk</field>
		<field name="content">The vast majority of Nebraskans speak American English with a neutral "Standard Midwestern" accent.  In some rural areas of the state, people speak with a slight accent best described as "country twang"; this accent is also easy to understand.  Nebraska is largely devoid of unusual terms for everyday items, with a few exceptions:  Carbonated drinks are nearly universally referred to as pop.  Beer served from a keg at a bar is a draw; a half beer/half tomato juice drink in rural areas is a red draw.  The town of Norfolk is pronounced Norfork and the town of Beatrice is pronounced Bee-at-riss  The town of Papillion is pronounced Pap-pill-yun.  The town of Plattsmouth is pronounced Platts-myth.  Nebraska has a fast-growing Hispanic population, largely concentrated in its medium-sized cities and Omaha.  In these areas, governments, businesses, and community organizations often provide services in Spanish.</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">64903</field>
		<field name="title">Eastern Shore (Maryland)</field>
		<field name="main">talk</field>
		<field name="name">talk</field>
		<field name="content">The Eastern Shore, because of its proximity to Virginia and historic isolation from the Western Shore, maintains a Southern accent akin to the Tidewater region of Virginia. This is especially true of the four counties on the "Lower Shore" or counties nearest Virgina: Wicomico, Dorchester, Somerset, and Worcester. In addition, are interesting dialects to be found in the isolated island communities of the Chesapeake Bay, where Victoria-era British accents have been near-perfectly preserved.</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">64904</field>
		<field name="title">Prince of Wales Island</field>
		<field name="main">talk</field>
		<field name="name">talk</field>
		<field name="content">English is the common language used.</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">64905</field>
		<field name="title">Catskills</field>
		<field name="main">talk</field>
		<field name="name">talk</field>
		<field name="content">The Gunks: Colloquial term for the Shawangunk Ridge (see below), in particular the popular climbing cliffs on the east near New Paltz. The mountaintop: Local term for the Tannersville–Haines Falls area in Greene County, not because its on an actual mountaintop but rather from being one of the highest-elevation settlements in the state (Tannersville is New Yorks highest incorporated municipality; Haines Falls is its second-highest hamlet after the Southern Tier community of Knapp Creek). Quickway: Older term for Route 17, from original name at planning stage. Began dropping from use even before conversion to I-86 Shawangunk: The ridge, town and stream are pronounced as spelled by visitors but SHONG-gum by locals.</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">64906</field>
		<field name="title">Ellijay</field>
		<field name="main">talk</field>
		<field name="name">talk</field>
		<field name="content">Ellijay people talk like they are from the south but some locals (not from Atlanta) talk with many expressions and strange words to newcomers.</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">64907</field>
		<field name="title">Delaware</field>
		<field name="main">talk</field>
		<field name="name">talk</field>
		<field name="content">Due to its location as a border state lying between the North and South, people from Delaware have American English accents which vary accordingly based upon location and environment.  Southern accents begin to be encountered below the CD Canal, and increase in volume the further south you go.</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">64908</field>
		<field name="title">Phoenix</field>
		<field name="main">talk</field>
		<field name="name">talk</field>
		<field name="content">English is the dominant language in Phoenix. However, like much of the  Southwest  with a large Hispanic population, Spanish is very widely spoken in Phoenix.  Spanish is a language often used for day-to-day discourse in many places, although English is the language of preference, especially when dealing with businesses and government.</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">64909</field>
		<field name="title">Oklahoma</field>
		<field name="main">talk</field>
		<field name="name">talk</field>
		<field name="content">The Coastal Southern drawl is rare.  The South Midlands accent is more common.  This accent ranges from Kentucky, Tennessee, Arkansas, Oklahoma, and into Texas.  Cherokee is common in Tahlequah but English is dominant even there.  The Indian tribes are completely integrated in Oklahoma and Indian languages are seldom heard outside Indian events.  It is also very common to hear a "twangy" accent in most parts of the state.  It sounds very similar to a Texas accent, but with a flair.  A trained ear can distinguish between the Texas and Oklahoma accents.  There is also a difference in accent between inhabitants of the larger cities and those of the smaller towns and rural areas.</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">64910</field>
		<field name="title">Poconos and Endless Mountains</field>
		<field name="main">talk</field>
		<field name="name">talk</field>
		<field name="content">To people in the western half of the united states, the accent of this subregion is often confused for the New York accent whereas within the region, New Yorkers would consider the residents to speak with a backwater/rural inflection.  Massive gentrification from New England makes the English spoken here indicative of a sort of "pan-Northeast"ern accent, a hodge podge of other NE accents prevails here.</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">64911</field>
		<field name="title">Florida</field>
		<field name="main">talk</field>
		<field name="name">talk</field>
		<field name="content">English is the official language of the state. However,  Spanish  is the native language of approximately 20% of Florida residents. In some parts of  South Florida , Spanish is the preferred language in everyday activities. Miami is most notable, where nearly 80% of residents do not speak English as a native language and 30% do not speak any English. Tampa also has a sizable Spanish speaking population, and areas where it is almost exclusively spoken.  Native-born Floridians will usually speak in a southern accent. However, after the migration of millions of Americans from other states to Florida, the southern dialect is becoming diluted with other accents.</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">64912</field>
		<field name="title">Minnesota</field>
		<field name="main">talk</field>
		<field name="name">talk</field>
		<field name="content">The stereotypical Minnesotan dialect as popularized in the film  Fargo  is more prevalent in northern (Iron Range) and rural parts of the state than it is in the Twin Cities metropolitan area. In fact, in the metropolitan area, the accent is rarely noticed by visitors, much less the locals. The dialect is characterized by long vowels and a slight inflection (especially Os as found in the word "boat"). The sing-songy intonation is less common with each generation removed from the Scandinavian ancestors. Native Americans (primarily Ojibwe) have an accent of their own.  In addition to a unique dialect, Minnesota also has several phrases and colloquial expressions that can be overheard somewhat frequently. These are most frequently heard in the northern parts of the state, and are rarely heard in urban areas. These include: Uff-da (Norwegian exclamation meaning "Off it!"  Typically used as a response to surprising or exasperating circumstances. You betcha (You bet/of course) Yah sure (I agree.  Sometimes used in conjunction with "You betcha".  "Yah sure you betcha".) Don-cha-no (Meaning "Dont you know". Used at the end of sentences as a sort of emphatic phrase. "Sure is cold outside, don-cha-no!".) Hot dish (Casserole) Oh yah (Yes) Lutefisk (A traditional Scandinavian food of dried white fish soaked in lye.) Choppers (leather mittens with wool inserts, used for the really cold days) Twenty below (shorthand for 20 degrees below zero (Fahrenheit), or -30C (without windchill), which is when choppers start becoming necessary) Tuque  "Tuke"  or Stocking cap (Knitted winter hat) Sorels (brand name of preferred winter boots, leather/rubber exterior, felt inserts) boughten (adjective for a store-bought item, as opposed to home-made, as in boughten bread) sled (slang term for a snowmobile) popple (aspen or poplar tree, one of the most common trees in northern Minnesota and important part of the logging industry) a forty (40 acres (about 16 hectares), or quarter-mile by quarter-mile of land, a derivative of the Public Land Survey (PLS) system) Acrost (Scandinavian influenced regional pronunciation of "across") Up north (Usually refers to anywhere that is north of the Twin Cities or where the person is at that time. ex.- Up north to Ely  in Duluth ) Parka (A very warm winter coat) Whipping Shitties (Breaking suddenly in an icy parking lot while the steering wheel is turned sharply causing the vehicle to spin) Skol (Originally from the Swedish term skål, a common drinking phrase used when clinking glasses together, such as "Cheers", "Salud", or "Chin Chin." Also used in their song for the Minnesota Vikings American football team, "Skol Vikings." Snus (A Swedish word for wet snuff, a tobacco variety common in the North) schnort ("would you like a schnort?) an extra splash or shot of whatever your drinking, schnapps, whiskey, rum. usually hard alcohol. The Cities (the Twin Cities of Minneapolis/St. Paul.  For those living outside "the Cities" it is rare to refer to Minneapolis or St. Paul individually.  Instead, the collective name is typically used.) A soft drink is typically called pop, rarely soda - even in newspaper advertisements. If you ask for a "coke" you will receive a regular Coca-Cola, you will not be asked "What kind?".</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">64913</field>
		<field name="title">Miami</field>
		<field name="main">talk</field>
		<field name="name">talk</field>
		<field name="content">Little Havana   Miami has the largest Latin American population outside of Latin America, with nearly 65% of its population either from Latin America or of Latin American ancestry. Spanish is a language often used for day-to-day discourse in many places, although English is the language of preference, especially when dealing with business and government. Many locals do not speak English, but this is usually centered among shops and restaurants in residential communities and rarely the case in large tourist areas or the downtown district. Even when encountering a local who does not speak English, you can easily find another local to help with translation if needed, since most of the population is fluently bilingual. In certain neighborhoods, such as Little Havana and  Hialeah , most locals will address a person first in Spanish and then in English. "Spanglish", a mixture of English and Spanish, is a somewhat common occurrence (but less so than in the  American Southwest ), with bilingual locals switching between English and Spanish mid-sentence and occasionally replacing a common English word for its Spanish equivalent.   Haitian Creole  is another language heard primarily in northern Miami. It is common for a person to hear a conversation in Creole when riding public transportation or sitting at a restaurant. Many signs and public announcements are in English, Spanish and Creole because of Miamis diverse immigrant population. Unlike Spanish, Haitian Creole is generally centered among the Haitian neighborhoods in northern Miami. Most Haitians are more adapted to English than their Hispanic neighbors.  Portuguese  and  French  are other languages that may be encountered in Miami. These languages tend to be spoken mainly around tourist areas. Most speakers of these languages speak English as well.  The simplest way to get a response in English is to use the "approach rule," where most locals will respond only in the language spoken to unless they are not able to speak it. This rule can be used on anyone whether or not their first language is Spanish, English or any other language.</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">64914</field>
		<field name="title">Wayne County (Ohio)</field>
		<field name="main">talk</field>
		<field name="name">talk</field>
		<field name="content">English is spoken by almost all the residents, English (non-Amish) and Amish, in Wayne County; however the Amish do have their own dialect they speak called Pennsylvania Duetsch.   Like most all other areas within Northeast Ohio, residents in Wayne County may refer to distance in the time spent to reach a location by vehicle. Not 30 miles, but 45 minutes.</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">64915</field>
		<field name="title">Acadiana</field>
		<field name="main">talk</field>
		<field name="name">talk</field>
		<field name="content">Acadiana is home to the majority of Louisianas Francophones.  The vast majority of people in Acadiana can speak English, though some older Cadiens in rural areas may only speak French. While most can speak English, many Cajuns are bilingual, and around 30% of Acadiana residents can speak French (as opposed to 7% in Louisiana).  Visitors from other English or French speaking regions may struggle with stronger local accents.    The local English accent incorporates many basic French words and unique pronunciations.  The dialect of French spoken by the francophones of Acadiana is essentially the same as the one spoken in  New Brunswick  and other Acadian areas of  Canada . Communication in French between Cajuns and residents of  France  or  Quebec  usually requires some effort.</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">64916</field>
		<field name="title">Washtenaw County</field>
		<field name="main">talk</field>
		<field name="name">talk</field>
		<field name="content">Ann Arbor  (along with its neighbor  Ypsilanti ) is a university town with a large number of international students. This means a lot of international restaurants, ethnic grocery stores, and lots of non-native speakers of English. There are several language schools in the heart of downtown, so as youre walking down the street, youre highly likely to encounter groups of people speaking Korean, Mandarin, Spanish, Arabic, or one of dozens of other languages. Of course, there are also native speakers from all over the country, and the rest of the English-speaking world, so youre liable to hear a wide variety of accents as well. For a small town, theres a surprising amount of cultural diversity.  Also recognize that youre not far from  Dearborn , home to the largest Middle Eastern population in the United States. While the Arabic population of Ann Arbor isnt nearly as visible as its Asian (particularly Korean) population, you may have the opportunity to meet visitors from Arab countries or locals of Arab descent.  As for the native English speakers in the area, Michigan is situated in the middle of the Northern Cities vowel shift, which in some ways has made the local accents more similar to a Canadian accent. In particular, youre likely to notice a difference in the low front vowel a (as in "hat" and "ramp"), which is raised and highly nasalized, and the close-mid back vowel o (as in row and soap), which is fronted such that it resembles a Minnesota accent.</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">64917</field>
		<field name="title">Alleghenies and Susquehanna Valley</field>
		<field name="main">talk</field>
		<field name="name">talk</field>
		<field name="content">The Susquehanna Valley region of Pennsylvania draws its dialect both from the local Amish "Pennsylvania Dutch" dialect and the Eastern Pennsylvania / Philadelphia dialect. While terms like "water ice" and "youse" are not uncommon here, the Pennsylvania Dutch "yuns" is also north of Harrisburg.</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">64918</field>
		<field name="title">Holmes County (Ohio)</field>
		<field name="main">talk</field>
		<field name="name">talk</field>
		<field name="content">Being in the center of Ohios Amish Country, the worlds largest Amish settlement, much of the population is bi-lingual, speaking both English and a dialect of German called "Pennsylvania Dutch." Smaller children speak only this dialect until starting school. The name "Pennsylvania Dutch" is actually a mispronunciation of "Deutsch" or German. Church services are held in "high German," as opposed to the dialect.</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">64919</field>
		<field name="title">Idaho</field>
		<field name="main">talk</field>
		<field name="name">talk</field>
		<field name="content">English is almost universally spoken and understood, except that potatoes are sometimes called "spuds" and theres a bit of a rural twang as you get out to the logging and farming areas.  Spanish is not as widely spoken as a second language, although it is prevalent in each of the major cities</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">64920</field>
		<field name="title">Quad Cities</field>
		<field name="main">talk</field>
		<field name="name">talk</field>
		<field name="content">English is the predominate language spoken in the Quad Cities and all signage in the area is in English as well.  Increasingly Spanish is spoken more widely and many places, especially in major retail establishments, will have bi-lingual signage as well as bi-lingual employees.  Because the area has a modest Vietnamese population there are services provided in that language, especially in health care.  While the area was largely settled by Germans and other Northern European people in the 19th century their languages are rarely spoken in the Quad Cities anymore.</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
</add>