<add>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">87730</field>
		<field name="title">McAllen</field>
		<field name="main">things to do</field>
		<field name="name">things to do</field>
		<field name="content">Art Walk - The McAllen Art Walk is a self-guided tour of art galleries along Main Street between Business 83 to the south and Pecan Avenue to the north.  These events take place on the first Friday of every month from September to May from 6PM - 10PM.  In addition to viewing the galleries visitors will find vendors selling food and other items, and live street performances.  The Art Walk is free and open to the public.    Birdwatching - McAllen and the rest of the Rio Grande Valley are great places to enjoy birdwatching.  528 species of birds have been spotted in the area, making it the most productive and popular birding destination in the country.  Visit South Texas Nature Marketing    and the World Birding Center websites   to find great birdwatching locations, and visit the McAllen Chamber of Commerce    at 1200 Ash Avenue for free brochures, maps and other birding information.  BorderFest - This is an annual celebration which takes place during the month of March at the Dodge Arena in nearby Hidalgo, TX.  There are live performances, car shows, amusement rides, food and drinks.  Each year there is a different theme for BorderFest.  In 2008 the theme was Celebrate China.     PalmFest - This is am annual festival that celebrates the unique culture and history of Deep South Texas.  Takes place every October at the McAllen Convention Center.  Texas Citrus Festival takes place every January in nearby Mission, TX.  Celebrates the areas citrus crops.  Contact the Mission Chamber of Commerce for more details (800) 580-2700  Valley Symphony Orchestra Chorale has concerts throughout the year.  Concerts usually held at the McAllen Convention Center.  http://www.valleyorchestra.org/]  McAllen International Travel Show the first week in January, with booths from around the world, live entertainment.   .  Music After Hours- free outdoor music concert series featuring local talent. Held in Archer Park every first Friday September through May, and in Bill Schupp Park second Fridays during summers.     Candlelight Posada- Annual Christmas celebration held the first weekend in December. Live music, food booths, special areas for children and for teens, Christmas parade, official City Christmas Tree lighting, traditional "posada"- a live reinactment of Mary and Josephs search for an inn.</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
</add>