<add>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">63167</field>
		<field name="title">Disneyland</field>
		<field name="main">tickets</field>
		<field name="name">tickets</field>
		<field name="content">Visiting Disneyland is an expensive affair. Tickets are sold at several levels: the base ticket is the Single-Day Theme Park Ticket which enables admission to only one of the two parks for a full day. By contrast, the 1-Day Park Hopper allows you to see both parks on the same day, and to move back and forth between the parks. Park Hopper tickets are also sold in increments of 2, 3, 4, and 5 days; while the ticket price increases with each day, the price per day actually decreases with each day. Multi-day Park Hopper tickets do not have to be used on consecutive days, but will expire 14 days after the first day they are used, or January 13th, 2015, whichever occurs first. The value of the Park Hopper ticket options should not be underestimated. All 3, 4, or 5 day tickets come with Magic Morning, which provides access into one park an hour before general opening one time during the ticket validity period. The park which this perk available at switches each day.  Note, only 1 and 2 day ticket options, Annual Passes, along with the Southern California CityPASS are sold at the Disneyland Resort Main Ticket Windows.  To buy the longer tickets (3 to 5 days), you need to buy them in advance, such as Disneyland.com/tickets, a travel agent, or selected tickets can be bought at a local Hotel or Disney Desk.   The prices below are effective as of June 2013, and there is no tax charged:   Children under age 3 are admitted free.  Discounts are hard to find, but California residents (bring a drivers license or utility bill to prove residency) will sometimes receive a small discount.  AAA occasionally offers its members discounts, and seasonal discounts such as the "buy a day, get a seasonal pass" offer occur during non-peak seasons.  If youre planning a multi-day vacation to Southern California with visits to multiple attractions including Disneyland, you can save a lot by using the  Southern California CityPass . For $319 for adults (ages 10+), $279 for ages 3-9, youll receive a 3-day Park Hopper ticket, which covers admission to Disneyland, Disney California Adventure, and 1 day each at Universal Studios Hollywood and SeaWorld San Diego. This makes for a wonderful week long vacation and a very attractive price with about $100 off standard prices. As an added bonus to purchasing the CityPass online (instead of in person at the park ticket counters), youll also get your choice of either the San Diego Zoo or the San Diego Safari Park (if your schedule allows you only one day in San Diego, choose to visit the San Diego Zoo instead of the Safari Park, since its much closer to SeaWorld).  And heres something even better: visiting both Disneyland and Walt Disney World in the same year is now easier with the  Disney Premier Passport . For $979, the Passport gives an entire year of unlimited admission to all eight theme and  water parks  in both California and Florida, plus  DisneyQuest ,  ESPN Wide World of Sports , and the  Oak Trail Golf Course . The Passport may be purchased at the theme park ticket booths.</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">63168</field>
		<field name="title">Walt Disney World</field>
		<field name="main">tickets</field>
		<field name="name">tickets</field>
		<field name="content">Visiting Walt Disney World is a very expensive affair. Tickets are sold at several levels: the Magic Your Way base tickets cover the cost of visiting one of the four theme parks a day for each day of the ticket. On top of this, you can add the Park Hopper option, which allows you to enter multiple theme parks on the same day as many times as you like. You can also add the Water Park Fun More option, which grants admission to the two Disney water parks as well as other attractions.  Each of those add-on options costs $59 (or $84 for both) above the cost of your tickets, regardless of how many days are on your tickets.  Neither one is likely worth it if you buy only a one-day ticket, but their value goes up sharply as you add more days.  The Park Hopper option in particular is often overlooked, but its strongly recommended because of the flexibility it offers.  Without it, you could be stuck with nowhere else to go after doing everything you want to do at one park; or you could run out of time to do one last attraction and be unable to come back another day to pick it up.  If you have seven-day tickets, it costs less than $9 per ticket per day to add this option; the value of being able to visit one park in the morning and another in the evening should not be underestimated.  With the Water Park Fun More option, you receive a number of admissions to attractions outside the four main parks.  The number is equal to the number of days on your Magic Your Way ticket (or two admissions for one-day tickets), though they can be used anytime.  You can use these admissions at  Typhoon Lagoon ,  Blizzard Beach ,  DisneyQuest ,  ESPN Wide World of Sports , and the nine-hole  Oak Trail  golf course. You can also use an admission for a round of golf at the  Fantasia Gardens  or  Winter Summerland  miniature golf courses, but only before 4PM.  Depending on which attractions you visit, the cost of the option may be covered by the money you save on admission after just two visits.  Multi-day tickets do not have to be used on consecutive days. However, these tickets will expire 14 days after they are first used, so be sure to use all the days purchased prior to that. A no-expiration option can be added to any multi-day ticket with at least one day remaining; with this option, the ticket expires when the last purchased day is used, which can be months or even years after the initial use. A side benefit of this option is locking in your admission price for your next visit(s). The price for this option is variable ($35ndash;$325), based on the number of days remaining on the ticket.  The best feature of a Disney admission ticket is its flexibility. Options can be added even if the ticket has already been used at least once. For example, a base ticket (no park-hopping) can be upgraded to include park-hopping by paying the $59 cost for the option. Or, if a change in travel plans will not allow the user to utilize all purchased days prior to the tickets expiration date, the "no-expiration" option can be purchased for the remaining days. These changes may be made at any ticket window or at the Guest Relations office inside each theme park as well as the Concierge desk at Disney Resort Hotels.  Any ticket upgrades must be made within 14 days of the first date of use, and you have to still have some remaining value on the ticket.    The prices below were accurate as of June 2013 (6.5% Florida sales tax not included):    Children under age three are admitted for free.  There are Magic Your Way Premium and Magic Your Way Platinum packages available as well; they add some interesting luxury options to your vacation package.  They both include the Deluxe Dining Plan, preferred fireworks viewing, unlimited access to select recreational activities, tours, and a portrait session.  The Platinum package adds to that a spa treatment, a fireworks cruise, and more.  If youre sure youre going to use the benefits these packages provide, they may just be worth the extra cost.  Purchasing these packages does require booking and staying at a Disney owned resort hotel.  Florida residents who provide proof of residence get discounts of varying degrees, but they cant purchase beyond a 7-day ticket (meaning that Florida residents who ask for the discount cant purchase 8-, 9-, or 10-day tickets).  Annual passes are also available for frequent visitors or residents.  Disney resort guests (those staying on-site at Disney hotels) are usually best served by getting package deals that include both lodging and admission.</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
</add>