<add>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">63464</field>
		<field name="title">New Orleans/Carrollton</field>
		<field name="main">to do and see</field>
		<field name="name">live music</field>
		<field name="content">Carrollton Station, 8140 Willow Street, at Dublin a block up from Carrollton  Maple Leaf Bar, 8316 Oak, tel. 866-9359    : Contemporary New Orleans brass bands like Rebirth, (who play here every Tuesday night when they are not traveling); also RB, Cajun, Zydeco, and more at this funky legendary local music venue -- includes the college crowd when school is in; dancing; late-night shows; casual; funky.  (Despite the name, remember its on Oak Street, 3 blocks up from Carrollton, not Maple).</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">63465</field>
		<field name="title">New Orleans/Carrollton</field>
		<field name="main">to do and see</field>
		<field name="name">to do and see</field>
		<field name="content">Walk around enjoying the Victorian residential architecture and plentiful flowering plants, sip coffee or eat a meal at an outdoor table on Carrollton Avenue while the old streetcars rumble by.     The Maple Leaf Bar is a popular live music venue   Anthony Bean Community Theater 1333 S. Carrollton Ave    Check website for show schedule.  Old Carrollton City Hall. The neoclassical building on Carrollton between Maple an Hampson is now a school. John Kennedy Tooles House: Fans of the novel "A Confederacy of Dunces" can take a walk by the Pulitzer Prize winning authors former home on Hampson at the downtown river corner of Adams. Theres a historic marker out front. Look from the sidewalk; its still a private home. Palmer Park, at Carrollton Claiborne Avenues and the end of the streetcar line. The last Saturday of each month it hosts the  Arts Market of New Orleans  from 10a to 4p, with tents of arts and crafts vendors, refreshments, and free live music. Occasionally hosts other events and concerts.</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">63466</field>
		<field name="title">New Orleans/Carrollton</field>
		<field name="main">to do and see</field>
		<field name="name">Po-Boy Festival</field>
		<field name="content">Big one day festival each November; Oak Street and the surrounding area is lined with food vendors, featuring great po-boy sandwiches and other local treats. Also free live bands and other special events.</field>
		<field name="url">http://www.poboyfest.com/</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
</add>