<add>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">64937</field>
		<field name="title">Morgantown</field>
		<field name="main">west virginia university</field>
		<field name="name">west virginia university</field>
		<field name="content">West Virginia University    is home to more than 30,000 students. The annual tuition for residential students is about $5,500 versus an out of state student whose tuition is approximately $17,000. WVU has 13 colleges and schools offering over 190 degrees. There are three campuses within WVU: Downtown, Evansdale, and The Health Sciences. They also offer a study abroad program for students who are interested. The football and basketball teams promote a lot of school spirit to their fellow "mountaineers" when they are playing.    Mountainlair Student Union , 1550 University Avenue. Monday-Thursday 7am-12am, Friday 7am-2am, Saturday 9am-2am, Sunday 2pm-12am. (304)-293-2702. The Mountainlair, or "Lair" as students like to call it, gives students the opportunity to gather in a controlled environment in order to study, chat, or have a bite to eat. The Mountainlair houses a convenient store and more than 10 different eateries, some of which include: Burger King, Freshens, Quiznos, Hatfields, and Sbarro. The Mountainlair also has a bowling alley and billiard tables on the ground floor.   Student Recreation Center  is a gym-like facility for students to use at their own leisure. The center includes a swimming pool, gym equipment, running track, basketball and volleyball courts, climbing wall, and provides other fitness services and classes.   West Virginia Universitys Creative Arts Center . Is home to the College of Creative Arts. Our College is comprised of the Divisions of Art, Music, and Theatre and Dance, three professionally accredited and nationally recognized programs in the Arts. There are also 4 theatres and 1 performance hall. An exhibition by current graduate students in the WVU Division of Arts Bachelor of Fine Arts program will be available June 2nd and 3rd. Gallery hours are Friday, 12 Noon to 9 p.m.; Saturday, 1 p.m. to 9 p.m. All exhibitions, lectures, and receptions are free and open to the public. (304)-293-4841.</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
</add>