<add>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">98212</field>
		<field name="title">Williston (North Dakota)</field>
		<field name="main">work</field>
		<field name="name">oil-field jobs</field>
		<field name="content">Halliburton:  420 Halliburton Drive Williston, ND 58801.  (701) 774-3963 Schlumberger:  12 East Dakota Parkway Williston, ND 58801.  (701) 523-3850 Hess:  113 4th Street East Williston, ND 58801.  (701) 774-9000 Sanjel:  511 22nd Street East Williston, ND 58801.  (701) 774-8699 Wisco:  4903 2nd Avenue West Williston, ND 58801.  (701) 572-2135 National Oilwell:  2203 2nd Avenue West Williston, ND 58801.  (701) 572-3781 Nabors Drilling:  5121 141st Avenue Northwest Williston, ND 58801.  (701) 572-1075 Black Hills Trucking:  1008 58th Street West Williston, ND 58801.  (701) 774-0011 Stallion Oilfield Services:  14070 49th St NW Williston, ND 58801.  (701) 774-3824</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">98213</field>
		<field name="title">Williston (North Dakota)</field>
		<field name="main">work</field>
		<field name="name">other</field>
		<field name="content">McCody Concrete:  PO Box 4005 Williston, ND 58801.  701-572-5300 Basin Tools:  2619 University Avenue Williston, ND 58801.  (701)774-0059 Four Seasons Equipment: 5033 Jackson St Williston, ND 58801. (701)651-4150</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">98214</field>
		<field name="title">Ann Arbor</field>
		<field name="main">work</field>
		<field name="name">Barracuda Networks</field>
		<field name="content">Barracuda Networks, Inc. is a privately held company providing security, networking and storage products based on network appliances and cloud services.  In June, 2012, Barracuda signed a lease to occupy the 45,000 square foot office complex previously used as the Borders headquarters on Maynard St in downtown Ann Arbor, announcing it is expecting to grow the office to 400 employees in the next five years.</field>
		<field name="address">317 Maynard St</field>
		<field name="url">https://www.barracuda.com/</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">98215</field>
		<field name="title">Galveston</field>
		<field name="main">work</field>
		<field name="name">work</field>
		<field name="content">The two largest employers on the island are UTMB (University of Texas Medical Branch) and ANICO (American National Insurance Company)</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">98216</field>
		<field name="title">Allentown</field>
		<field name="main">work</field>
		<field name="name">work</field>
		<field name="content">The largest employer in Allentown is Lehigh Valley Hospital, with over 7,800 workers. Other companies headquartered here are Air Products Chemicals, LSI, St. Lukes Hospital, Blue Cross and PPL.  Allentown was once an important manufacturing center in the region.  Today, small scale manufacturing is still an important part of the local economy.  Allentown is the county seat for Lehigh County.  Downtown Allentown is an important employment center with approximately 15,000 people working there.</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">98217</field>
		<field name="title">Chicago</field>
		<field name="main">work</field>
		<field name="name">work</field>
		<field name="content">the Loop ]] Chicago still loves Carl Sandburg and his poems, but the city shucked off the hog butchers apron a long time ago. In terms of industry, theres little that distinguishes Chicago from any other major city in America, save for size. The  Chicago Board of Trade  and  Chicago Mercantile Exchange  are among the biggest employers, with stables of traders and stock wizards.  Boeing  moved its headquarters to Chicago amid much fanfare a few years ago;  United Airlines  is another international company with headquarters in town.  Abbott Labs , just outside city limits, is the biggest employer of foreign nationals in scientific fields. The Big Five consulting firms all have one or more offices in the  Loop . And theres always construction work in Chicago, but with a strong union presence in the city, its not easy for a newcomer to break into without an introduction.  For younger workers, the museums in the  Loop  and the  Near South  are always looking for low-paid, high-enthusiasm guides, and the retail outlets on the  Magnificent Mile  also need seasonal help. And with so many colleges and universities in the city, study abroad opportunities abound.  In Chicago, business is politics, and theres one word in Chicago politics: clout. The principal measure of clout is how many jobs you can arrange for your friends. Hence, if you want to work in Chicago, start asking around — email someone from your countrys embassy or consulate and see if they have any leads, or figure out if there is a cultural association that might be able to help you. Its no coincidence that the  Mayors Office  employs scores of  Irish  workers every summer. If you happen to contact somebody who met the right person at a fundraiser a few days ago, you might fall into a cushy job or a dream internship; its worth a try.</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">98218</field>
		<field name="title">Omaha</field>
		<field name="main">work</field>
		<field name="name">work</field>
		<field name="content">Omaha has a thriving employment market in finance, healthcare, and IT. Omaha is home to the headquarters of no fewer than five Fortune 500 companies: Berkshire Hathaway Union Pacific ConAgra Foods Peter Kiewit Sons Mutual of Omaha Insurance  Other major employers in the area include TD Ameritrade, First National Bank of Omaha, Blue Cross and Blue Shield of Nebraska, and the University of Nebraska Medical Center.</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">98219</field>
		<field name="title">Cape May</field>
		<field name="main">work</field>
		<field name="name">work</field>
		<field name="content">Restaurants, bars hotels are undeniably the largest employers on the island.  Much work available here is seasonal only.</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">98220</field>
		<field name="title">Milwaukee</field>
		<field name="main">work</field>
		<field name="name">work</field>
		<field name="content">Milwaukee is home to several Fortune 500 companies; in fact, the metropolitan region (defined as the Milwaukee-West Allis-Waukesha area) was "ranked number five in the nation when measuring the number of Fortune 500 companies as a share of the population - just behind the number four Minneapolis-St. Paul region in Minnesota"    .  The area has a wide employment base, with companies ranging from high-tech and specialty manufacturing firms (GE Medical, Harley Davidson) to retail and finance corporations (Kohls, Northwestern Mutual).  Milwaukee Area Fortune 1000 Companies (As of 2004 ranking)   Johnson Controls     Northwestern Mutual     Manpower     Kohls     Harley-Davidson     Roundys     Rockwell Automation     Wisconsin Energy     Fiserv     Marshall Ilsley Corp.     Briggs Stratton     A.O. Smith     MGIC Investment     Joy Global     Toshiba International Corporation     The Milwaukee-Racine metropolitan area was also rated one of the Top 20 Hot Cities for Entrepreneurs in 2005   .</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">98221</field>
		<field name="title">Houston</field>
		<field name="main">work</field>
		<field name="name">work</field>
		<field name="content">As of the census for 2011, Houston, TX has over 6,200,000 people living there. That being a factor, the city is a great place where you will find jobs of all sorts. Ones from working at the local McDonalds ranging to working in the hospital. The only downfall about the job opportunities is that most people from out of town tend to take them. There are a lot of people that will drive over 2 hours just to get to work everyday in the city of Houston.</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">98222</field>
		<field name="title">Des Moines</field>
		<field name="main">work</field>
		<field name="name">work</field>
		<field name="content">For general information about employment and employers in the area, the Greater Des Moines Parternship    is a good starting place. Also check out Iowa Workforce Development   .  Des Moines—and Iowa in general—has fared quite well despite the realities the 2008 recession brought to several economies in the world. As recently as 2012, however, Forbes ranked the capital city of Iowa only behind the nations capital,  Washington DC , in terms of best cities for jobs.</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">98223</field>
		<field name="title">Newark (New Jersey)</field>
		<field name="main">work</field>
		<field name="name">work</field>
		<field name="content">More than 100,000 people commute to Newark on weekdays, making it New Jerseys largest employment center with many white-collar jobs in insurance, finance, import-export, health-care, and government. As a major courthouse venue including federal, state, and county facilities, it is home to more than 1,000 law firms. The city is also a "college town", with nearly 40,000 students attending the citys universities and medical and law schools. Its port and rail facilities make Newark the busiest transhipment hub on the East Coast in terms of volume. Light manufacturing survives in Newark too.</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">98224</field>
		<field name="title">Akron</field>
		<field name="main">work</field>
		<field name="name">work</field>
		<field name="content">Akron and Summit County boast the headquarters location for the following Fortune 1000 Corporations:   112 Goodyear Tire Rubber Company, Rubber Manufacturing  184 FirstEnergy, Utilities Company covering northern Ohio, various parts of Pennsylvania and New Jersey  839 Jo Ann Stores, Hudson - Specialty Retailer  995 A. Shulman - Chemicals</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">98225</field>
		<field name="title">Overland Park</field>
		<field name="main">work</field>
		<field name="name">work</field>
		<field name="content">Sprint World Headquarters, near 119th Street and Nall Ave.  Overland Park Convention Center, 6000 College Blvd near Nall Ave.</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">98226</field>
		<field name="title">Portland (Oregon)</field>
		<field name="main">work</field>
		<field name="name">work</field>
		<field name="content">Former Oregon Governor Tom McCall (to whom a major riverfront park downtown is dedicated) said in a 1971 speech, somewhat famously, "We want you to visit our State of Excitement often. Come again and again. But for heavens sake, dont move here to live. Or if you do have to move in to live, dont tell any of your neighbors where you are going."  Since then, the Governors request has been widely repeated by people who ignore it, then quote it. In recent years, Portland has been one of the hardest cities in which to find work. The official unemployment rate in the city went over 14% in March 2009. Underemployment is a rampant problem, and wages tend to be artificially low compared to the cost of living. These forces combine to make Portland a tough job market to navigate.</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">98227</field>
		<field name="title">United States of America</field>
		<field name="main">work</field>
		<field name="name">work</field>
		<field name="content">It is better to arrange your work and work visa before you enter the United States. Young people who are full-time students of certain nationalities can apply for a  J1 "Exchange Visitor" visa  which permits paid work as a nanny or summer work for up to 4 months in virtually any type of job. The United States Department of State has full information on applying for this type of visa including the precise categories that qualify.  The H-1B visa allows a limited number of skilled and certain unskilled employees to temporarily work in the United States. It usually requires a tertiary degree and is based on a petition filed by an American employer. The job you wish to apply for should be related to your degree. The most common careers of hard-to-get H-1B visa holders are nurses, mathematics teachers, and computer science professionals. On the other hand, there is the more permanent employment-based immigrant visa which has similar requirements to the H-1B visa. Before an employer can arrange any work visa, he must ensure that nobody within his locale is willing or qualified to do the job before considering you.  Unless you are a permanent resident of the United States (i.e. green card holder), as a foreigner, you will need a work visa to be allowed to work in the United States. Paid work is generally not allowed on a B1/B2 visitor visa or the visa-waiver program. Working unlawfully in the United States runs the very real risk of arrest, deportation, and ineligibility to re-enter the country. Illegal immigrants also run the risk of dangerous work conditions. Foreigners on F1 student visas are allowed to work for up to 20 hours a week on-campus in their respective institutions, but are generally banned from working off-campus unless they have applied for and received special permission in advance. Note that the above restrictions apply to  Canadians  and  Bermudians  as well. The only exceptions to this rule are citizens of  Palau ,  Marshall Islands  and the  Federated States of Micronesia , who are allowed to live and work in the United States indefinitely with only a valid passport. Citizens of U.S. Overseas Territories such as  Guam ,  Puerto Rico ,  American Samoa  and the  U.S. Virgin Islands  are considered to be U.S. citizens and, therefore, may work unrestricted in the United States.  If you are seeking to adjust visa status or to enter the U.S. on a working visa you should first check the official government websites of the  U.S. Department of State , which issues visas abroad, and the  U.S. Citizenship and Immigration Services  which administers immigration programs within the United States.  Unfortunately, con artists both in the U.S. and overseas often prey on peoples desire to travel or work in the U.S. Keep in mind that visa applications do not usually require an attorney or other intermediary, so you should be wary of and verify any "advice" offered by third parties, especially non-lawyers. If in doubt about properly applying for such visas then it is recommended to use a licensed immigration attorney.  Keep in mind that anyone entering under the Visa Waiver Program is not permitted to adjust their status for any reason.</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">98228</field>
		<field name="title">Miami</field>
		<field name="main">work</field>
		<field name="name">work</field>
		<field name="content">If you are not from the U.S., you will need a work visa. If you try to work while holding a tourist visa, you are still considered an illegal immigrant in the U.S. Immigration and Nationalization Services conduct frequent illegal immigrant checks in Miami businesses since Miami has several refugees from Cuba, Haiti and other nearby countries. If you don’t have the right visa, you may not get a job in Miami.  There is an exception to getting work without a visa in Miami, however.  Since yachts and cruise ships sail on international waters, these companies can freely hire any person they like.  Non-US citizens will still require a valid seamans visa, however, to land in US ports.</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">98229</field>
		<field name="title">Ann Arbor</field>
		<field name="main">work</field>
		<field name="name">work</field>
		<field name="content">The University of Michigan and the infrastructure and support services for it are major employers in Ann Arbor.</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">98230</field>
		<field name="title">Charlotte</field>
		<field name="main">work</field>
		<field name="name">work</field>
		<field name="content">Charlotte is a city that thrives on big business (specifically banking and is thus the second leading banking center in the country). Its most visible employers are Wells Fargo/Wachovia (the citys largest employer), Bank of America, Duke Energy, Nucor, Sonic Automotive, Continental Tire NA, SPX, Lowes and Family Dollar. Though the Uptown area has the largest concentration of business offices, the entire metro area has sprouted office and industrial parks. In particular, the gleaming mid rises of SouthPark and Ballantyne are worth noting if youre in those areas. There are several Fortune 500 companies and is regularly listed as one of the U.S.s fastest-growing business areas, as well as one of the best places to do business in the nation.</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">98231</field>
		<field name="title">San Francisco</field>
		<field name="main">work</field>
		<field name="name">work</field>
		<field name="content">While San Francisos economy is linked to it being a world-class tourist attraction, its economy is diversified.  The largest employment sectors are professional services, government, finance, trade, and tourism. Its frequent portrayal in music, films, literature and popular culture has helped make the city and its landmarks known throughout the world. San Francisco has developed a large tourist infrastructure with numerous hotels, restaurants, and top-notch convention facilities.  While its been a long time since people considered Montgomery Street in the  Financial District  to be the "Wall Street of the West", San Francisco remains one of the principal banking and finance centers of the west coast of the United States. Many major financial institutions and banks are based in the city or have set up regional headquarters here.  San Franciscos proximity to Silicon Valley has made the city increasingly attractive for high-tech companies. While most of the large technology companies are in the valley, many tech workers live in San Francisco and commute to work. In recent years, San Francisco has also been making itself a center of biotechnology.</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">98232</field>
		<field name="title">Bellingham (Washington)</field>
		<field name="main">work</field>
		<field name="name">work</field>
		<field name="content">Major employers in Whatcom county represent about 25% of the total jobs in the county. Yet the city encourages small business development and small businesses make up a large percentage of our employment. Top ten employers in the county are: Alcoa Intalco Works Bellingham School District Bellis Fair Mall BP/Cherry Point Refinery Brown Cole, Inc. Georgia-Pacific Corporation Haggen Foods ConocoPhillips Company St. Joseph Hospital Western Washington University</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">98233</field>
		<field name="title">Ann Arbor</field>
		<field name="main">work</field>
		<field name="name">Thomson Reuters</field>
		<field name="content">Thomson Reuters is an information business for professionals. The healthcare division is headquartered in the 777 building as its known locally.  They currently employee over 1500 employees with in Ann Arbor between the heathcare and tax divisions, and are the third largest employer in Washtenaw county.  The Tax and Accounting division headquarters are located 10 minutes west in Dexter, MI.</field>
		<field name="phone">+1 734 913-3000</field>
		<field name="address">777 E. Eisenhower</field>
		<field name="url">http://thomsonreuters.com</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">98234</field>
		<field name="title">Atlanta</field>
		<field name="main">work</field>
		<field name="name">work</field>
		<field name="content">Meet the people of Atlanta while serving alongside them at a  Hands On Atlanta  volunteer project.</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">98235</field>
		<field name="title">Pine City</field>
		<field name="main">work</field>
		<field name="name">4Staffing</field>
		<field name="phone">+1 320 629-3333</field>
		<field name="address">220 4th Avenue SE</field>
		<field name="url">http://www.4staffinginc.com/</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">98236</field>
		<field name="title">Berkeley (California)</field>
		<field name="main">work</field>
		<field name="name">work</field>
		<field name="content">Work-study programs are available through the University of California, Berkeley.  Berkeley Chamber of Commerce . The chamber of commerce provides business resources and events.  Lawrence Berkeley National Laboratory  provides employment to Department of Energy personnel, contractors, and visiting scholars.</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">98237</field>
		<field name="title">Joplin</field>
		<field name="main">work</field>
		<field name="name">work</field>
		<field name="content">Leggett Platt  General Mills  Contract Freighters Inc.</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">98238</field>
		<field name="title">Sacramento</field>
		<field name="main">work</field>
		<field name="name">work</field>
		<field name="content">As the capital of California, many state agencies are located in Sacramento.  The State of California continues to be the largest employer in the Sacramento region.</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">98239</field>
		<field name="title">Philadelphia</field>
		<field name="main">work</field>
		<field name="name">work</field>
		<field name="content">Philadelphias job market is ever-expanding both in the city and in its suburbs. The 975 Comcast Center is a constant reminder of the economic revitalization of Philadelphia and of Comcasts presence in the city. Additionally, a Keystone Opportunity Zone over the Powelton Rail Yards adjacent to 30th St. Station promises a bright future for jobs and new office buildings in the city.</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">98240</field>
		<field name="title">Arlington (Virginia)</field>
		<field name="main">work</field>
		<field name="name">work</field>
		<field name="content">Arlington is a rapidly growing county with a dynamic economy.  The prospects for employment here are excellent, even as the rest of the country goes through recessionary times.  The bedrock of Arlingtons economy remains the Federal government, the military, and companies that directly do business with the government. The process to start a career with the government is considerably longer than the typical entry process in the private sector.  Those seeking Federal government employment in Washington, D.C. or elsewhere can generally apply from their current location, anywhere in the US.    The Pentagon, and its mighty parking lots.   During summertime the Washington, D.C. area fills with ambitious young people completing internships with the government, NGOs, PACs, think tanks, and related organizations.  Such persons would do best to arrange their housing in advance.  While the Arlington rental market is not as tight as, say,  New York City , good apartments can be pricey and hard to find on short notice.  The most sought after neighborhoods in Arlington are those directly along the Metro lines, particularly the Rosslyn to Ballston corridor of the Orange line.</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">98241</field>
		<field name="title">Bismarck</field>
		<field name="main">work</field>
		<field name="name">work</field>
		<field name="content">The average wage in Bismarck is about $31,000</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">98242</field>
		<field name="title">Columbus</field>
		<field name="main">work</field>
		<field name="name">work</field>
		<field name="content">Government - Columbus serves as the capital city of Ohio, and government is one of the citys largest employers. Insurance - Several large insurance companies are headquartered in Columbus, including Nationwide Insurance Company, which is headquartered in downtown Columbus.</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">98243</field>
		<field name="title">Fort Smith</field>
		<field name="main">work</field>
		<field name="name">work</field>
		<field name="content">Judge Parker Gallows, "The Hanging Judge"  There are several major employers in Fort Smith, including Baldor Electric, Whirlpool Corporation, Rheem, Golden Ventures and Arkansas Best Corporation (ABF).</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">98244</field>
		<field name="title">Cincinnati</field>
		<field name="main">work</field>
		<field name="name">work</field>
		<field name="content">The PG Twin Towers (headquarters) are located Downtown. PGs influence and history with the region can be seen throughout downtown.   Cincinnati is home to numerous international corporations that are important employers within the Greater Cincinnati area. The region fares well nationally with 10 Fortune 500 companies and 18 Fortune 1000 companies headquartered in the Cincinnati area. Statistically, Greater Cincinnati ranks sixth in the U.S. with 4.98 Fortune 500 companies per million residents and fourth in the U.S. with 8.96 Fortune 1000 companies per million residents.  A few of Cincinnatis notable businesses include:  Fifth Third Bank ,  Great American Insurance ,  Macys Department Stores ,  Kroger  and  Procter Gamble .  In the summer, restaurants and amusement parks employ large numbers of foreign students with J-1 Visas.  Kings Island in particular is a major employer, hiring several thousand foreign college students.</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">98245</field>
		<field name="title">Ann Arbor</field>
		<field name="main">work</field>
		<field name="name">Google</field>
		<field name="content">Google opened the headquarters of AdWords, their advertising system, in the McKinley Towne Centre building in 2007; currently they employ about 150 sales and customer services representatives, with plans to expand their workforce to between 850 and 1,000 by around 2012.</field>
		<field name="phone">+1 734 332-6500</field>
		<field name="fax">+1 734 332-6501</field>
		<field name="address">112 S Main Street, 2nd floor</field>
		<field name="url">http://www.google.com/</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">98246</field>
		<field name="title">Richmond</field>
		<field name="main">work</field>
		<field name="name">work</field>
		<field name="content">The Greater Richmond area was named the third-best city for business by MarketWatch in September 2007, ranking behind only the Minneapolis and Denver areas and just above Boston. The area is home to six Fortune 500 companies, including: electric utility Dominion Resources; CarMax; Owens Minor; Genworth Financial, the former insurance arm of GE; MeadWestvaco; and Altria Group.   However, only Dominion Resources and MeadWestvaco are headquartered within the city of Richmond; the others are located in the neighboring counties of Henrico and Hanover. In 2008, Altria moved its corporate HQ from New York City to Richmond, adding another Fortune 500 corporation to Richmonds list.Five Fortune 1000 companies also have their headquarters located in the area. These include: Brinks; Massey Energy; Universal Corporation; and Markel. Of these, only Massey Energy and Universal Corporation are headquartered within the city limits. Other Fortune 500 companies, while not headquartered in the area, do have a major presence. These include SunTrust Bank (based in Atlanta), Capital One Financial Corporation (officially based in McLean, Virginia, but founded in Richmond with its operations center and most employees in the Richmond area), and the medical and pharmaceutical giant McKesson (based in San Francisco). Capital One and Altria companys Philip Morris USA are two of the largest private Richmond-area employers. DuPont maintains a production facility in South Richmond known as the Spruance Plant.</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">98247</field>
		<field name="title">Cleveland</field>
		<field name="main">work</field>
		<field name="name">work</field>
		<field name="content">Cleveland Clinic   Five major industries have evolved to become the economic strength of the region: Health Medicine, Science Engineering, Biotechnology Biomedical, Manufacturing and Education. In addition to 12 Fortune 1000 headquarters, more than 150 international companies have a presence here. Site Selection magazine ranked Ohio as first in the U.S. with the most corporate facility projects and expansions in 2007.  Of particular note, the Cleveland Clinic Health System is a world-renowned treatment center that has treated dignitaries from all over the world, most notably King Fahd of Saudi Arabia  Also of note is Quicken Loans and their Cleveland Web Center. This medium size company founded by Dan Gilbert (also owner of the Cleveland Cavaliers) boasts being the fourth largest Veteran Lender in the nation as well as the tenth best place to work for in the entire nation rated by Fortune. Quicken Loans has been listed many times as one of the best places to work at years before as well.</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">98248</field>
		<field name="title">Detroit</field>
		<field name="main">work</field>
		<field name="name">work</field>
		<field name="content">Some of the major companies which have headquarters or a significant presence in metro Detroit include GM, Ford, Chrysler, Volkswagen of America, Comerica, Rock Financial/Quicken Loans, Kelly Services, Borders Group, Dominos, American Axle, DTE Energy, Compuware, Covansys, TRW, BorgWarner, ArvinMeritor, United Auto Group, Pulte Homes, Taubman Centers, Guardian Glass, Lear Seating, Masco, General Dynamics Land Systems, Delphi, ATT, EDS, Microsoft, IBM, Google, Verizon, National City Bank, Delta Air Lines, Bank of America, and Raymond James, PwC, Ernst Young, the FBI, and more. This being said, Detroit has been greatly affected by the nations economic downturn and has an official unemployment rate more than double that of the nations, which in reality may be significantly higher.</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">98249</field>
		<field name="title">Pine City</field>
		<field name="main">work</field>
		<field name="name">work</field>
		<field name="content">Temporary assignments are sometimes available through the following agencies:</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">98250</field>
		<field name="title">Pine City</field>
		<field name="main">work</field>
		<field name="name">Masterson Personnel</field>
		<field name="phone">+1 320 629-4850</field>
		<field name="address">900 Main Street S</field>
		<field name="url">http://mastersonpersonnel.com/</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">98251</field>
		<field name="title">Oxford (Mississippi)</field>
		<field name="main">work</field>
		<field name="name">work</field>
		<field name="content">By far the major employer is the University of Mississippi, but other employers include  FNC, Inc.  (a banking systems and data/analytics management firm) and many local banks.  Oxford is also a regional healthcare center with constantly growing healthcare facilities.  A variety of jobs are may be found at the  Baptist Memorial Hospital - North Mississippi .  The free Daily Mississippian    and the daily Oxford Eagle    have updated help wanted ads.</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">98252</field>
		<field name="title">Cuyahoga County</field>
		<field name="main">work</field>
		<field name="name">work</field>
		<field name="content">Enjoy your visit, but youll probably want to stay. Greater Cleveland today is a global corporate center where national and international corporations grow and develop from the area’s strong, diversified economy. Poised as the leading center of commerce between New York City and Chicago, Greater Cleveland has been ranked by Fortune magazine as the sixth best location in North America to conduct business. Five major industries have evolved to become the economic strength of the region: Health Medicine, Science Engineering, Biotechnology Biomedical, Manufacturing and Education.   Fifteen companies headquartered in Cuyahoga County are on Fortunes 2008 list of the top 1000 U.S. corporations. More than 37% of the Fortune 500 companies are present in Greater Cleveland through corporate headquarters, major divisions, subsidiaries and sales offices. Cleveland is headquarters to 113 companies with revenues of $100 million or more and more than 150 international companies have a presence here.  Cuyahoga County has a diverse mix of business activity, including the following Fortune 1000 Company Headquarters (according to the 2008 list):  175 Progressive Corporation, Mayfield Heights - Insurance  207 Eaton Corporation, Cleveland - Motor Vehicle/Parts  226 National City Corporation, Cleveland - Banking  247 Parker-Hannifin Corporation, Cleveland - Aerospace    316 Sherwin Williams Company, Cleveland - Paint and Coatings    321 KeyCorp, Cleveland - Banking  376 Aleris International, Beachwood - Metals  395 TravelCenters of America, Westlake - Highway Retail  591 Nacco Industries, Cleveland - Industrial Equipment  807 Medical Mutual of Ohio, Cleveland - Health Insurance  820 Lincoln Electric, Cleveland - Arc Welding Equipment  822 Cleveland-Cliffs, Cleveland - Mining Crude Oil  836 Ferro,  Cleveland  - Chemicals  895 Applied Industrial Technologies, Cleveland - Bearings  957 American Greetings, Cleveland - Greeting Cards</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">98253</field>
		<field name="title">Salt Lake City</field>
		<field name="main">work</field>
		<field name="name">work</field>
		<field name="content">For many years, Utah has experienced a very low unemployment rate, however wages are less than the national average and have not kept up with the steady rise in housing and food costs.   Like all US states, Utah is an "employment at will" state where it is legal to fire an employee for any reason unless otherwise stated in a collective bargaining agreement or other written employment contract. In Utah, an Equal Opportunity Employer (EOE) frequently does not include equality for homosexuals. The best employment and job security is with larger national companies which have an active policy of non-discrimination.</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">98254</field>
		<field name="title">Somerville</field>
		<field name="main">work</field>
		<field name="name">work</field>
		<field name="content">Somerville is largely residential, with some retail and professional services, a hospital, and some light industry such as cabinet makers, printing companies, and some very small junkyards. Somerville residents span a wide economic spectrum, and thus hold all sorts of jobs within the greater Boston area.</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">98255</field>
		<field name="title">Big Island</field>
		<field name="main">work</field>
		<field name="name">work</field>
		<field name="content">Hawaiis unemployment rates are among the lowest in the nation, and thus it is impressive that the Big Island boasts one of the lowest unemployment rates in the state.  While tourism, military, and agriculture have typically been the largest employers, recent new job growth has resulted primarily from a residential building boom.  The astronomical observatories are another important group of employers.</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">98256</field>
		<field name="title">Canton (Ohio)</field>
		<field name="main">work</field>
		<field name="name">work</field>
		<field name="content">Canton is home to the Fortune 1000 headquarters of:   417 The Timken Company, bearings and specialty steel manufacturer   671 Diebold, Electronics and ATM manufacturer</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">98257</field>
		<field name="title">Fort Lauderdale</field>
		<field name="main">work</field>
		<field name="name">work</field>
		<field name="content">Once heavily reliant on tourism and the very large marine industry, Fort Lauderdales economy is now diverse and based on many small and medium business.  Several large companies are based in the Fort Lauderdale area including:   AutoNation USA, Citrix Systems, DHL Express, Spirit Airlines, and National Beverage Corp.  Due to its proximity to Miami, Fort Lauderdale is emerging as a location for Latin American headquarters for companies such as Microsoft.  Fort Lauderdale is a major manufacturing and maintenance center for large and expensive private yachts. The boating industry is responsible for over 100,000 jobs in the area.  With its many canals, and proximity to the Bahamas and Caribbean, it is also a popular place to keep a yacht, and a major stop for nautical staging and refitting.  Unfortunately the boating industry is being squeezed out because waterfront property continues to increase in value and this is forcing some marinas and shipyards to sell out or relocate out of the area.  The total number of available boat slips is also declining as marinas are more actively seeking a few large mega-yachts instead of several smaller boats.  Even so, the marine industry continues to grow, catering more and more to the mega yachts. There is now a section of the old State Road 84 that has been renamed Marina Mile where the mega yacht industry is booming.  During the 1970s, the citys tourism was largely driven by younger people, because Fort Lauderdale was infamous for being THE spring break destination for college students. This changed in the late 1980s when there was a crack down on underage drinking. Fort Lauderdale is now less of a college spring break destination and does more year round business with European families and upscale US tourists.  The city also has a booming cruise ships industry: every day there are shiploads of tourists leaving and arriving at the sea port.</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id">98258</field>
		<field name="title">Williston (North Dakota)</field>
		<field name="main">work</field>
		<field name="name">work</field>
		<field name="content">Due to the recent oil boom, labor is needed in Williston.  Jobs are easy to find, wages are the highest in the state, and the companies offer great benefits.  Job Service of ND: 422 1st Ave W Williston, ND 58801.  701-774-7900.</field>
		<field name="weight">1</field>
		<field name="clicks">0</field>
	</doc>
</add>